[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.97,0:01:32.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继大辅之后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.64,0:01:36.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京从装有空的爱心徽章的装甲数码蛋中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.90,0:01:39.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和新诞生出来的麻鹰兽相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.49,0:01:46.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织也同样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.93,0:01:48.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从装有光子郎的知识徽章的装甲数码蛋中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.96,0:01:51.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和诞生的犰狳兽相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.91,0:02:01.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 暴龙改造者那毛骨悚然的微笑并没有消失
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.60,0:02:10.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.54,0:02:37.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.55,0:02:39.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.70,0:02:42.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.90,0:02:44.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 大家还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.57,0:02:46.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:48.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织没有来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.53,0:02:51.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系 他们两人都会来的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.10,0:02:53.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 来了 来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.52,0:02:57.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 我带礼物来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.88,0:03:01.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 京学姐家里开便利超市的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.03,0:03:03.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家里开便利超市真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.94,0:03:06.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样不是一直可以随便吃点心了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.69,0:03:09.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是这样的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.73,0:03:11.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且还会被强迫去帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.34,0:03:14.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是很辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.35,0:03:17.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.46,0:03:18.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吃的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.01,0:03:20.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吃的哦 很好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.36,0:03:25.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃吃看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.70,0:03:33.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.70,0:03:35.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.74,0:03:36.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.71,0:03:37.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.72,0:03:49.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.41,0:03:52.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃 好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.51,0:03:54.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉可以推测出今后会怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.06,0:03:56.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 门打开了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.00,0:03:57.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.78,0:04:01.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打开了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.93,0:04:02.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.39,0:04:05.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 伊织君还没有来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.22,0:04:08.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织？那家伙在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.53,0:04:10.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我去看过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.27,0:04:13.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说是不把饭全部吃完就不回去 正在努力着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.35,0:04:18.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不全部吃掉也没有关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.32,0:04:21.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 还是不能把食物剩下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.38,0:04:23.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过世的父亲也这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:26.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.05,0:04:33.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀 状态真糟糕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.81,0:04:35.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打开电视来等他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.32,0:04:38.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 在播放什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.07,0:04:42.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前几天 有场计算机程序竞赛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:44.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天 我们来介绍一下那场比赛的冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.00,0:04:48.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天才少年一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.06,0:04:51.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样的小孩子居然可以得到冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.43,0:04:53.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真是做梦也没有想到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.45,0:04:54.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是大吃一惊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.88,0:04:59.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后采访一下评审委员城南大学祥月教授
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.20,0:05:02.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 实在是太震惊了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.63,0:05:04.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到是程序竞赛 竟然有小学生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.91,0:05:06.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我简直都无法想象啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.15,0:05:10.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是天才 没有错的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.89,0:05:13.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在前几天举行的国际象棋大会上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.09,0:05:15.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时面队20个对手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.54,0:05:17.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且不只学习和电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.85,0:05:19.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连体育都是万能的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.85,0:05:20.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「一本!」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.58,0:05:23.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在柔道和足球界中大活跃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.17,0:05:28.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好厉害的射门
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.41,0:05:33.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我们来采访一下培养出这位天才少年的双亲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.67,0:05:38.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在培养天才这方面 有什么特别需要注意的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.55,0:05:42.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我们并没有做什么特别的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.20,0:05:47.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么说呢 就说是歹竹出好笋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.38,0:05:51.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 像一乘寺贤这样的人还真的有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.95,0:05:53.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你什么时候来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.88,0:05:54.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 刚才
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.46,0:05:58.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是好厉害 真的是天才
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.86,0:06:04.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 不就是一点点程序吗 我也会写嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.08,0:06:07.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是还说他体育万能哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.72,0:06:09.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.98,0:06:10.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.39,0:06:13.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界怎么样了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.00,0:06:16.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 伊织君也到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.29,0:06:23.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通往数码世界的大门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.09,0:06:26.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.39,0:06:38.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鞋子会脏的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.11,0:06:53.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 妈妈我马上要去百货商店
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.13,0:06:54.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就把点心先放在这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.58,0:07:02.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 学习很忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.28,0:07:20.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在那里 出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.61,0:07:24.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要逃吗 有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.08,0:07:33.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去追从这里逃走的那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.60,0:07:55.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃吧 逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.24,0:08:04.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又被抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.97,0:08:07.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家被那家伙抓住后嵌上项圈的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.03,0:08:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就会变得和之前完全不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.25,0:08:10.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要马上逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.21,0:08:13.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要丢下同伴不管吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.13,0:08:13.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.64,0:08:30.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒下了 又是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.56,0:08:33.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被抓住 强迫同伴之间互相战斗 然后倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.42,0:08:36.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙以看这个为乐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.85,0:08:38.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是可怕的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.65,0:08:54.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明都是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.36,0:09:04.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 小贤这样就满足了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.15,0:09:20.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 恢复原样了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.57,0:09:24.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要回到数码世界就会恢复原样的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.70,0:09:25.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Yeah
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.48,0:09:30.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.44,0:09:31.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:33.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装甲数码蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.23,0:09:36.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在附近就有装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.36,0:09:38.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有其它的装甲数码蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.71,0:09:39.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.79,0:09:41.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之先找找看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.92,0:09:43.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 去找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.27,0:09:51.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是那些家伙吗 真碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.23,0:10:13.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.53,0:10:15.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该就在这附近了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.05,0:10:18.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次会诞生出怎样的数码兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.12,0:10:20.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实在是想像不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.69,0:10:23.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那就是说还有其他被选召的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.04,0:10:25.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这…我们也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.17,0:10:32.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.12,0:10:34.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.21,0:10:35.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.01,0:10:38.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你这混蛋 上次竟然对我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.37,0:10:43.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是立体影象 不是实体
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.68,0:10:45.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你们这样愚蠢的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.25,0:10:48.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么可以自由地出入这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.71,0:10:50.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「为什么」？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.28,0:10:55.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实这里应该是只有被选召的孩子才可以进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.24,0:10:59.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.37,0:11:03.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为我是被选召的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.49,0:11:04.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.57,0:11:06.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也是？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.89,0:11:10.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之你们几个的存在让我很不愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.81,0:11:14.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像是和我得到平等的待遇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.33,0:11:17.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平等的待遇难道不可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.85,0:11:22.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.58,0:11:27.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所谓被选召的孩子应该是指像我这样完美的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.18,0:11:29.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是你们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.75,0:11:31.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「完美的人」？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.89,0:11:33.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为自己算老几啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.07,0:11:37.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个数码世界归我所有 快点滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.12,0:11:39.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.55,0:11:41.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果要妨碍我的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.61,0:11:43.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就要得到于此相对应的待遇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.31,0:11:45.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 巨龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.71,0:11:48.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:50.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发达的两只手臂的攻击 很难对付
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.10,0:11:52.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是「火焰喷射」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.45,0:11:54.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.08,0:11:57.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.33,0:12:00.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上了哦 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.82,0:12:01.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.42,0:12:07.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.55,0:12:17.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽 装甲进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.62,0:12:33.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.24,0:12:35.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.02,0:12:42.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你以为相同的招数还会一直奏效吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.47,0:12:45.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为这个我才讨厌愚蠢的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.52,0:12:47.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是让人火大的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.63,0:12:49.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.59,0:12:55.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接招
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.01,0:12:57.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.48,0:13:02.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.62,0:13:03.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.42,0:13:05.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.31,0:13:10.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.24,0:13:17.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.00,0:13:19.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.47,0:13:24.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.21,0:13:30.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为数量多就了得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.40,0:13:33.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出来吧 我的奴隶们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.66,0:13:38.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.80,0:13:47.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部一共五只
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.12,0:13:49.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.79,0:13:50.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.96,0:13:52.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.81,0:13:58.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.75,0:14:04.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.10,0:14:06.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.70,0:14:08.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我们不能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.89,0:14:10.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也想战斗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.74,0:14:12.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有我这黑暗神圣计划在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.64,0:14:14.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就无法进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.69,0:14:17.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奴隶们 集中攻击那两只
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.80,0:14:18.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.11,0:14:30.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去 我们只不过是绊脚石而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.48,0:14:31.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.28,0:14:39.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们才是对手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.39,0:14:42.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你太卑鄙了 暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.51,0:14:43.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卑鄙？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.85,0:14:45.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在胜负中怎么会有卑鄙可言
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.24,0:14:47.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去无法分出胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.21,0:14:50.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把胜负赌在装甲数码蛋上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.51,0:14:52.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知道是谁的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.08,0:14:54.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能做到的 都试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.80,0:14:59.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 去寻找装甲数码蛋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.12,0:15:01.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.30,0:15:06.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里由我们先来挡住
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.96,0:15:09.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电眼冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.85,0:15:11.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.84,0:15:14.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.64,0:15:25.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,休想逃 追！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.55,0:15:30.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.23,0:15:38.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空气炮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.84,0:15:41.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是先逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.46,0:15:47.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去那个洞穴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.87,0:15:58.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.02,0:16:00.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装甲数码蛋哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.34,0:16:03.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是说把那装甲数码蛋拿起来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.22,0:16:06.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就又有新的数码兽诞生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.58,0:16:08.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是没有被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.84,0:16:10.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是帮不上忙的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.44,0:16:19.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是光明的徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.69,0:16:22.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另一个是希望的徽章哦 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.93,0:16:25.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.80,0:16:28.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这就是小光和阿岳的装甲数码蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.50,0:16:30.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,岳 把装甲数码蛋拿起来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.90,0:16:31.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.67,0:16:33.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算不行也试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.72,0:16:35.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我们是拿不起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.01,0:16:36.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.26,0:16:37.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.59,0:16:46.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣计划在发光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.31,0:16:56.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是和大辅君他们相同的神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.16,0:16:57.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.12,0:17:02.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好轻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:03.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.45,0:17:12.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.29,0:17:28.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.05,0:17:29.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.39,0:17:39.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.02,0:17:56.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.74,0:17:57.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.44,0:18:03.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和迪路兽装甲进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.25,0:18:07.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是我们 原来是我们的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.56,0:18:08.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.84,0:18:09.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.08,0:18:11.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样我们也可以战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.29,0:18:12.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.09,0:18:15.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这样我们就不是绊脚石了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.24,0:18:27.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经要投降了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.79,0:18:28.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.96,0:18:31.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看后面 你们还想逃到哪里去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.04,0:18:37.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.52,0:18:39.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.28,0:18:45.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.09,0:18:49.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于邪恶事物能够发挥绝对力量的圣兽型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.71,0:18:52.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是神圣的光线 「银色光芒」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.58,0:18:54.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.59,0:18:57.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用强力的光芒力量来净化黑暗的圣兽型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.84,0:19:02.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是额头的饰品中放出高热光线的 「女皇之光」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.46,0:19:05.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是应急的进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.71,0:19:08.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别以为这样的东西一直都有用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.22,0:19:10.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰喷射
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.07,0:19:15.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.20,0:19:18.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣阵雨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.03,0:19:20.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼罗宝光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.90,0:19:38.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色魔轮消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.86,0:19:49.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 真是无法原谅那个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.19,0:19:53.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然攻击无法进化的弱小对手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.38,0:19:57.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 我绝对要让他吃大苦头
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.56,0:19:59.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也这么认为吧 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.36,0:20:02.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 无法想像他同样是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.35,0:20:04.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且还说数码世界是自己的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.28,0:20:06.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是不正常了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.28,0:20:11.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说回来 装甲数码蛋根据个人都是不同的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.61,0:20:12.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.34,0:20:16.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅同学和我还有京学姐的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.35,0:20:18.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是从装甲数码蛋中出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.08,0:20:21.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是光学姐和岳学长却不同
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.11,0:20:27.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有诞生新的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.54,0:20:31.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是原本的数码兽倒可以装甲进化了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.86,0:20:38.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 完全没有预料到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.25,0:20:39.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我很高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.90,0:20:41.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙真让人生气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.98,0:20:43.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.78,0:20:45.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个人到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.33,0:20:49.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 那家伙所做的事情无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.49,0:20:49.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.30,0:20:53.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 和他人竞争什么的 一点都不适合我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.27,0:20:57.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好像冒险游戏一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.42,0:20:59.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 一开始还那么害怕的说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.77,0:21:02.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.21,0:21:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.98,0:21:22.07,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.21,0:21:25.02,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.86,0:21:27.96,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.21,0:21:29.63,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.02,0:21:33.93,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.15,0:21:37.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.01,0:21:40.26,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.44,0:21:45.74,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:49.09,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.17,0:21:51.98,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.31,0:21:57.63,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.90,0:22:03.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.13,0:22:09.44,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.82,0:22:18.65,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.48,0:22:28.98,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.21,0:21:19.25,ED,,0,0,0,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.98,0:21:22.07,ED,,0,0,0,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.21,0:21:25.02,ED,,0,0,0,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.86,0:21:27.96,ED,,0,0,0,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.21,0:21:29.63,ED,,0,0,0,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.02,0:21:33.93,ED,,0,0,0,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.15,0:21:37.75,ED,,0,0,0,,だって世の中これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.01,0:21:40.26,ED,,0,0,0,,まるでなってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.44,0:21:45.74,ED,,0,0,0,,だねっ! 気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:49.09,ED,,0,0,0,,今っ! 吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.17,0:21:51.98,ED,,0,0,0,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.31,0:21:57.63,ED,,0,0,0,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.90,0:22:03.97,ED,,0,0,0,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.13,0:22:09.44,ED,,0,0,0,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.82,0:22:18.65,ED,,0,0,0,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.48,0:22:28.98,ED,,0,0,0,,ゴージャスな人生を!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.98,0:22:38.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,传递到阿和那里的SOS
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.08,0:22:42.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是被邪恶力量所鞭打的加布兽悲痛的叫喊声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.11,0:22:44.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那让人毛骨悚然的耸立着的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.06,0:22:47.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,众多的数码兽臣服他的暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.85,0:22:48.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的目的是？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.04,0:22:51.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有新的被选召的孩子的使命是？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.48,0:22:54.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.91,0:22:56.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗之王暴龙改造者」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.11,0:22:59.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.88,0:23:02.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗之王暴龙改造者
