[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.07,0:01:36.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们把暴龙改造者控制的地区分别解放了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.93,0:01:40.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从哥玛兽那里传来了求救信号
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.25,0:01:43.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿丈和大辅他们一起去了数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.88,0:01:48.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和暴龙改造者操控的数码兽经过一场苦战
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.84,0:01:53.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥玛兽进化成了海狮兽  情况逆转  获得胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.58,0:02:00.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是  暴龙改造者控制的地区还在继续扩大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式開始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.55,0:02:10.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,325)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fscx95}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}危险的野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.99,0:02:38.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久没回日本了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.46,0:02:45.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是早上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.31,0:02:46.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.10,0:02:51.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好困哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.79,0:02:56.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.09,0:02:57.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.93,0:03:03.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅  大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.96,0:03:08.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅  大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.11,0:03:13.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅  大辅  大辅  大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.08,0:03:20.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早安  大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.92,0:03:23.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早安  豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.88,0:03:28.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得  肚子  好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.87,0:03:32.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽跑到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.40,0:03:35.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.18,0:03:37.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.86,0:03:39.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.31,0:03:43.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说不能在家里乱跑的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.74,0:03:46.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织的妈妈在做很奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.98,0:03:47.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.45,0:03:52.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是葫芦干卷
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.10,0:03:54.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葫芦干卷？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.55,0:03:56.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是小京姐点名要吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.51,0:03:58.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葫芦干卷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.25,0:04:03.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要进去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.73,0:04:05.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.38,0:04:08.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来  进去进去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.37,0:04:12.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.98,0:04:15.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊  忘了东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.09,0:04:23.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳  你竟然把我忘了  好过份
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:24.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.91,0:04:30.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鲔鱼三个  柴鱼两个  咕嘟咕嘟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.85,0:04:31.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.46,0:04:35.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说了是电脑部的野餐嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.31,0:04:39.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鲔鱼三个  柴鱼两个  咕嘟咕嘟一只
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.63,0:04:41.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才问要去哪里野餐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.14,0:04:43.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有两个红豆面包
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.86,0:04:47.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有决定去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.49,0:04:49.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.54,0:04:51.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.75,0:04:55.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.99,0:04:56.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.18,0:05:00.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.52,0:05:03.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好  钝钝兽  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.15,0:05:07.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  可是请你不要蹦蹦跳跳的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:08.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.99,0:05:11.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么  小京姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.30,0:05:13.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.92,0:05:14.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.99,0:05:19.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.75,0:05:21.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦  终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.21,0:05:23.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全体集合
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.91,0:05:26.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好  去野餐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.55,0:05:27.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.97,0:05:36.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.86,0:05:46.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我身为电脑部员去电脑部还要偷偷摸摸的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.87,0:05:48.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.48,0:05:52.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,学校规定假日禁止使用学校设施的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.22,0:05:55.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安静点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.91,0:05:57.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.07,0:06:00.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.25,0:06:04.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.21,0:06:05.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.05,0:06:08.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们  出动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.58,0:06:21.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.83,0:06:23.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.69,0:06:25.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.32,0:06:28.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳  小光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.04,0:06:29.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.36,0:06:32.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅君  小京姐  伊织君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.11,0:06:37.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这位是以前的被选召的孩子们之一  太刀川美美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.52,0:06:40.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太刀川美美  移民到美国东海岸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.26,0:06:45.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因父母工作忙  由她代表来参加表姐的婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.79,0:06:47.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们听阿空说过你们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.92,0:06:49.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她把我们说得很奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.84,0:06:50.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.90,0:06:52.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.36,0:06:54.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们可是被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.24,0:06:56.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.70,0:06:58.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和迪路兽也很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.90,0:06:59.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.33,0:07:03.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候从美国回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.24,0:07:03.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.10,0:07:05.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才路过台场小学
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.38,0:07:07.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然觉得好怀念
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.48,0:07:10.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就从后门悄悄进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.54,0:07:13.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也是从后门进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.82,0:07:14.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.45,0:07:18.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在正要去数码世界野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.77,0:07:19.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.23,0:07:21.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美也一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.83,0:07:25.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正表姐的婚礼是明天
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.11,0:07:26.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以一起去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.27,0:07:26.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.07,0:07:29.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  你不要一个人随便决定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.48,0:07:30.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎  不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.73,0:07:32.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是无所谓啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.19,0:07:32.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.92,0:07:33.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.58,0:07:34.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.37,0:07:37.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BINGO BINGO BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.04,0:07:40.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们们  出动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.80,0:07:59.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.55,0:08:02.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.00,0:08:05.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.42,0:08:10.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里  确实是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.32,0:08:16.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会不会遇到巴鲁兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.71,0:08:19.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.60,0:08:21.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.00,0:08:25.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他建造黑暗之塔  想要支配数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.83,0:08:32.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这附近没有黑暗之塔  也就是说很安全了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.99,0:08:34.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为很安全所以才来野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.57,0:08:37.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到数码世界来野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.56,0:08:39.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们那时候想都没想过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.17,0:08:41.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在都不一样了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.73,0:08:46.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前也是为了打倒黑暗之塔才来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.45,0:08:48.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过今天是黄金周嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:52.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶然到数码世界玩一玩也无所谓呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.22,0:08:54.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.58,0:08:55.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该吃午饭了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.23,0:08:58.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还很早吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.26,0:09:00.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.87,0:09:04.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们吃午饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.11,0:09:08.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.35,0:09:11.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我家卖的饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.21,0:09:13.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.48,0:09:17.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鲔鱼饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:23.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久没吃了的鲔鱼饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.64,0:09:26.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连做梦都梦到的鲔鱼饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.41,0:09:28.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.76,0:09:30.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.21,0:09:33.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽要吃什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.69,0:09:34.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.67,0:09:36.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想吃那个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.87,0:09:37.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,葫芦干卷吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.26,0:09:38.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.34,0:09:40.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请给我一个葫芦干卷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.19,0:09:43.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.23,0:09:44.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以扔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.31,0:09:48.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的葫芦干卷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.41,0:09:51.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈辛苦做的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.49,0:09:53.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能那样乱扔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.12,0:09:56.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.89,0:10:01.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  麻鹰兽  你们在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.72,0:10:05.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.58,0:10:12.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.48,0:10:12.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:13.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.34,0:10:15.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.10,0:10:17.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.92,0:10:18.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.89,0:10:19.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.63,0:10:20.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.73,0:10:22.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她醒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.27,0:10:22.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.03,0:10:24.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.89,0:10:27.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.77,0:10:29.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看那个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.23,0:10:34.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.46,0:10:38.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是暴龙改造者的领地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.59,0:10:57.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.66,0:10:59.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是蝌蚪兽和青蛙兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.38,0:11:01.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你认识吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.58,0:11:02.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我们是朋友哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.35,0:11:04.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经不是朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.62,0:11:06.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们身上有黑色魔轮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.05,0:11:07.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.12,0:11:42.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.36,0:11:42.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.38,0:11:48.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐姐要被奇怪的青蛙抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.03,0:11:50.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.58,0:11:54.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也会说这种话了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.57,0:12:00.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.20,0:12:02.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.70,0:12:13.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.81,0:12:17.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.05,0:12:21.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美  美美
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.16,0:12:25.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.09,0:12:26.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.65,0:12:27.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.62,0:12:28.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.30,0:12:31.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好像听到巴鲁兽在叫我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.92,0:12:35.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也好像觉得美美来到了数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.21,0:12:38.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是来救我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.62,0:12:39.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是来野餐的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.06,0:12:47.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  我们都得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.53,0:12:51.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这片森林被暴龙改造者控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.93,0:12:55.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蝌蚪兽和青蛙兽也被带上了黑色魔轮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.73,0:12:57.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你却还在野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:00.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.04,0:13:05.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我美美小姐为了蝌蚪兽和青蛙兽也要打倒黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.84,0:13:06.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.35,0:13:08.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只靠美美一个人是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.33,0:13:12.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  请你和大辅他们联系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.32,0:13:12.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.46,0:13:15.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.54,0:13:18.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.57,0:13:19.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.60,0:13:21.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.81,0:13:22.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.75,0:13:25.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  快点注意到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.00,0:13:31.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像是京传来的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.00,0:13:33.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信号好弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.00,0:13:35.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她们到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.49,0:13:38.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是被暴龙改造者妨碍了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.60,0:13:45.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个黄金周可能会很开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.42,0:13:49.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.32,0:13:50.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什  什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.87,0:13:51.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天的攻击该谁去？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.34,0:13:54.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.62,0:13:55.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.94,0:14:01.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.94,0:14:04.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.06,0:14:07.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么唉声叹气的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.12,0:14:10.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要跟我们约会呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.88,0:14:15.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要  蟑螂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.48,0:14:16.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你们乱来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.69,0:14:19.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.74,0:14:22.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有着又黑又亮的身体和顽强的生命力的昆虫型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.20,0:14:24.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行动敏捷    逃跑能力无人能及
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.27,0:14:26.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是梦幻遗骸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.25,0:14:30.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真伤人啦  蟑螂兽哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.45,0:14:31.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事  弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.43,0:14:34.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她们伤了我们  干掉她们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.45,0:14:35.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.37,0:14:38.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是兄弟吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.93,0:14:40.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是蟑螂兽兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.65,0:14:41.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.19,0:14:43.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.79,0:14:46.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就请蟑螂兽哥哥先出招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.57,0:14:47.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不不
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.60,0:14:50.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是蟑螂兽弟弟先出招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.93,0:14:52.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们感情真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.46,0:14:55.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们兄弟感情好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.46,0:14:56.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.74,0:14:57.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.50,0:15:00.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么  哥哥和我一起攻击吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.28,0:15:03.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好主意  弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.10,0:15:05.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梦幻遗骸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.89,0:15:17.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  只是垃圾而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.06,0:15:22.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.44,0:15:31.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不只是垃圾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.19,0:15:35.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.79,0:15:38.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梦幻遗骸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.24,0:15:43.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽  你不能进化吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.99,0:15:46.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不把黑暗之塔破坏掉就不能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.45,0:15:51.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很轻松呢  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.34,0:15:52.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.23,0:15:56.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被套上黑色魔轮感情还这么好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.96,0:15:58.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许会很美的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:16:01.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要是和美美姐也这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.26,0:16:04.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊  美美姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.02,0:16:08.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事  小京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.14,0:16:10.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.28,0:16:13.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.66,0:16:15.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还这么不慌不忙的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.16,0:16:17.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  小京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.96,0:16:20.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.60,0:16:21.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.95,0:16:27.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.44,0:16:37.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽  装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.71,0:16:55.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.77,0:16:59.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.82,0:17:01.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上了  铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.97,0:17:05.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京  好帅呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.33,0:17:09.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.23,0:17:10.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.92,0:17:15.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.99,0:17:17.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.78,0:17:18.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要来真的了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.83,0:17:22.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽兄弟踢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.13,0:17:24.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.25,0:17:27.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽兄弟冲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.52,0:17:33.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.65,0:17:35.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.60,0:17:36.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.07,0:17:41.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们利用蟑螂兽兄弟的攻击破坏黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.58,0:17:43.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐  BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.56,0:17:50.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  站住
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.96,0:17:53.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们来了  铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.45,0:17:53.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.75,0:17:56.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽兄弟飞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.18,0:18:00.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在  巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.71,0:18:01.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.68,0:18:04.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好刺眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.68,0:18:09.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.67,0:18:10.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.08,0:18:25.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.25,0:18:28.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仙人掌兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.44,0:18:32.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.53,0:18:33.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尖尖碰碰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.98,0:18:35.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.95,0:18:37.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.84,0:18:52.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的领地又减少一块
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.35,0:18:55.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个不愉快的黄金周
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.94,0:18:58.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.20,0:19:03.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤  你应该再成熟些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.52,0:19:08.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊  敌人的黑色地区消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.17,0:19:11.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,D-T暴龙机里来了一条消息
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.57,0:19:13.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「我们平安无事 小京」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.54,0:19:16.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真让人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.71,0:19:23.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.14,0:19:24.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.29,0:19:27.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥  你在这里做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.13,0:19:30.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你才是  在这里做什么  弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.78,0:19:34.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥  你把我的巧克力吃掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.54,0:19:37.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  你才是吃了我的麻薯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.36,0:19:39.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么  把我的口香糖还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.86,0:19:41.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  把我的饼干还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.92,0:19:42.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想打架吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.72,0:19:43.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.81,0:19:47.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才感情还那么好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.91,0:19:50.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然吵起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.52,0:19:54.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们被暴龙改造者控制会比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.39,0:19:56.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会是这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.50,0:19:58.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽弟弟踢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.42,0:19:59.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽哥哥冲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.94,0:20:01.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蟑螂兽兄弟合击
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.65,0:20:04.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然会有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.62,0:20:06.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.28,0:20:08.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.14,0:20:14.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的黑色魔轮也摘下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.48,0:20:16.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.99,0:20:17.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.11,0:20:19.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.00,0:20:22.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个地区以后由我来守护
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.73,0:20:24.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.56,0:20:26.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.51,0:20:28.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美的数码兽仙人掌兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.47,0:20:32.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仙人掌兽  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.55,0:20:33.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:36.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里  我会努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.49,0:20:40.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁来帮帮我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:43.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天的野餐到此结束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.43,0:20:50.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊  美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.15,0:20:53.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.49,0:20:56.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能见到美美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.66,0:20:59.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.34,0:21:07.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,BINGO
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集預告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.32,0:22:39.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去的通道被炸掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.00,0:22:43.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅和阿岳想要救出困在数码世界的小光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.38,0:22:46.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是  孩子们面前出现的敌人是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:51.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被暴龙改造者夺走记忆的那个让人怀念的完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.98,0:22:53.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集  数码兽大冒险02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.25,0:22:55.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「小光的记忆」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.99,0:22:58.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在  冒险之门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.16,0:23:04.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}小光的记忆
