[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.12,0:01:34.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与大辅他们为敌的谜之少年暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.51,0:01:39.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被他邪恶力量控制的数码兽攻击了孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.62,0:01:48.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 正当危机之时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.51,0:01:51.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳和小光发现了新的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.22,0:01:54.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并让巴达兽和迪路兽装甲进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.72,0:01:57.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,粉碎了暴龙改造者的阴谋

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式開始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.58,0:02:10.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,325)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fscx95}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}黑暗之王暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.65,0:02:11.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小型火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.31,0:02:14.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔头槌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.55,0:02:15.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.35,0:02:18.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 大家这边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.66,0:02:25.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作战成功
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.98,0:02:27.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很努力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.63,0:02:29.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真想看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.00,0:02:33.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者那家伙知道这件事后会是什么表情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.77,0:02:34.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是好奇怪呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.11,0:02:35.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.13,0:02:40.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,戒备这么松散 而且那家伙并不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.42,0:02:43.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有什么其他目的到别的地方去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.13,0:02:44.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.96,0:02:46.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他一定是害怕我们逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.27,0:02:48.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不对啊 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.04,0:02:52.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…我赞成阿岳的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.72,0:02:57.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 不知道他到底想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.49,0:03:00.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…总之先回学校吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.06,0:03:03.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎和小京一定在担心我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.62,0:03:20.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又有一个地方变成我的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.79,0:03:26.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到那座黑色的塔了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.92,0:03:28.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:31.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,建造有黑暗之塔的地方 全部都是我的地盘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.12,0:03:34.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而你们 都是我的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.26,0:03:35.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.50,0:03:39.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都被那个魔轮控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.60,0:03:46.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么把矿石兽他们也带回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.61,0:03:47.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.24,0:03:51.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为不知道暴龙改造者什么时候会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.60,0:03:52.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.38,0:03:52.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.32,0:03:54.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是被藤山老师发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.11,0:03:56.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么跟他说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.72,0:03:57.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.11,0:04:00.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为此我们已经练习过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.64,0:04:01.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 摆个姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.48,0:04:05.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都像是雕像吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.91,0:04:09.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.39,0:04:11.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能不能把你的神圣计划借给我一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.25,0:04:13.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.97,0:04:17.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们的神圣计划的力量可以打开数码世界大门
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.45,0:04:19.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不怀疑这点了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.48,0:04:22.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 至少我们的就不行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.31,0:04:27.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然大辅他们打开大门时我们可以跟着一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.70,0:04:31.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想研究一下 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.05,0:04:36.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 去下一个区域 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.67,0:04:41.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 那家伙走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.17,0:04:43.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.06,0:04:45.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爆炎火焰弹
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.95,0:04:56.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为你们能逃得掉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.68,0:04:57.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.38,0:04:58.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.39,0:05:02.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖的全熟蔬菜红鼻屎兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.42,0:05:07.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红鼻屎兽 阴险又狡猾的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.98,0:05:11.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是发出强烈臭气的灾难性臭气
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.99,0:05:12.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.34,0:05:15.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,企图逃走是重罪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.28,0:05:15.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了惩罚你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.36,0:05:18.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要打你100下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.73,0:05:20.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,66
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.98,0:05:23.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,67
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.18,0:05:25.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,68
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.79,0:05:26.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,69
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.33,0:05:28.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,70
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.88,0:05:30.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,71
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.98,0:05:31.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,72
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.36,0:05:34.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,73
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.01,0:05:46.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘁 才73下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.25,0:05:49.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过他不可能还活着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.81,0:05:57.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可以死呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.59,0:06:02.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我 我一定要把这件事通知大家 还有阿和…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.84,0:01:29.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.84,0:01:29.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.25,0:06:34.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.35,0:06:39.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要到矿石兽的藏身之处以外的地方找
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.88,0:06:41.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你想不到什么可能的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.25,0:06:43.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这么说我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.67,0:06:44.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以给我签个名吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.18,0:06:45.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.86,0:06:47.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.89,0:06:49.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫 本宫纯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.97,0:06:51.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎 本宫纯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.00,0:06:54.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你是大辅君的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.43,0:06:56.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.45,0:06:58.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.72,0:07:02.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面 我是大辅君的同学
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.20,0:07:04.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 不过你好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.94,0:07:05.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也给我签个名吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.86,0:07:09.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅一点都不可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.92,0:07:12.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要是有像你们这样的弟弟就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.06,0:07:18.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的D终端机也有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.45,0:07:22.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「收到求救信号 快来社团… 小京」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.46,0:07:23.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.38,0:07:25.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道是 加布兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.49,0:07:35.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子 出动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.52,0:07:53.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加布兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.08,0:07:55.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.41,0:07:58.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,振作点 加布兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.29,0:08:01.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我好想你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.87,0:08:03.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.28,0:08:05.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.47,0:08:06.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.36,0:08:10.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我去泉学长家取回我的神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.29,0:08:14.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间 由我来负责联络
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.55,0:08:15.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.87,0:08:16.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.30,0:08:20.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这台电视把求救信号传到那边的世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.25,0:08:24.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽跟太一联络的时候也是用电视
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.73,0:08:26.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.38,0:08:29.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 我知道在什么地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.52,0:08:33.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那个叫桑塔加尼亚的城镇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.93,0:08:35.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来是个和平的城镇
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.51,0:08:39.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是暴龙改造者把数码兽们关了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.94,0:08:41.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那座塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.09,0:08:43.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,矿石兽他们那里也有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.25,0:08:45.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那叫做「黑暗之塔」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.89,0:08:47.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是暴龙改造者建造的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.61,0:08:48.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.56,0:08:48.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.71,0:08:51.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先声明
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.41,0:08:54.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的目的是把被抓起来的数码兽们救出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.32,0:08:56.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.69,0:08:59.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要装甲进化事情就简单了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.42,0:08:59.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.04,0:09:04.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 也许他会把抓到的数码兽当成挡箭牌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.37,0:09:06.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.31,0:09:08.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是去救人质的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.39,0:09:10.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样反而会害了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.41,0:09:13.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,负责看守的是鼻屎兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.09,0:09:15.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它们会用大便攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.59,0:09:18.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红鼻屎兽是什么样的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:19.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.08,0:09:22.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘁 把我们排除在外呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.42,0:09:24.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 很让人生气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.23,0:09:25.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 可以作为参考
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.68,0:09:28.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.88,0:09:31.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 那么我们潜入牢房
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.36,0:09:32.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.01,0:09:34.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也要把小光带去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.20,0:09:38.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我反对 敌人会用大便不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.56,0:09:39.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.07,0:09:43.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大便攻击在以前冒险的时候也遇到过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.43,0:09:43.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.39,0:09:45.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.03,0:09:48.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂得要邻香惜玉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.39,0:09:49.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「邻香惜玉」？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.43,0:09:51.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是「怜香惜玉」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.88,0:09:59.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站住 你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.92,0:10:04.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们把逃走的数码兽和他们的同伴抓回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.60,0:10:06.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把他们带进牢房
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.67,0:10:08.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快点进去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.91,0:10:18.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们没发现这个环是假的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.57,0:10:20.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是这样我们也不能大意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.01,0:10:24.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们现在要进入敌人的据点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.65,0:10:47.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别磨磨蹭蹭的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.72,0:10:51.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们明天每人都要打100下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.76,0:10:54.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.63,0:10:55.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.26,0:10:57.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们也辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.12,0:10:58.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫拳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.11,0:11:05.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.86,0:11:06.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快停下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.64,0:11:10.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狱卒什么时候变这么多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.50,0:11:12.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来该我们出场了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.09,0:11:13.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.99,0:11:17.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想连累我们好不容易救出来的数码兽们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.72,0:11:20.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们到上面去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.70,0:11:22.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要能到那座黑色的塔所在的山丘就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.93,0:11:23.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.62,0:11:28.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.03,0:11:29.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.10,0:11:34.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 大辅君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.83,0:11:36.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今天见到你姐姐了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.25,0:11:38.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.98,0:11:39.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.18,0:11:42.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我姐姐说了我什么坏话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:43.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.00,0:11:45.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 她一定说了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.95,0:11:49.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她好像不跟别人说我坏话就浑身不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.51,0:11:50.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为她讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.26,0:11:53.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过我也讨厌那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.79,0:11:54.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们彼此彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.08,0:11:56.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:57.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.90,0:12:00.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要是我弟弟我绝饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.27,0:12:02.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会揍你一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.64,0:12:03.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.50,0:12:04.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你就试试啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.53,0:12:05.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揍我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.48,0:12:06.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.77,0:12:08.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不会真的揍他吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.30,0:12:09.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不会那么做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.56,0:12:11.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.86,0:12:14.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你要注意你的说话方式
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.93,0:12:17.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个烦人的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.52,0:12:21.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要怎么说那个笨女人是我的自由吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.82,0:12:23.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要说了 大辅君
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.52,0:12:27.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌说自己姐姐坏话的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.06,0:12:28.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.18,0:12:35.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 讨厌 讨厌 最讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.45,0:12:42.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:43.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.83,0:12:46.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我被小光讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.11,0:12:49.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次看到大辅这么沮丧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.30,0:12:51.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我必须让他振作起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.18,0:12:52.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.87,0:12:56.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要从这里下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.40,0:12:58.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太高了 不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.24,0:13:01.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是有绳子什么的就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.54,0:13:03.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回去找找看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.67,0:13:04.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.02,0:13:06.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了感谢你们救我们出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.35,0:13:08.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.75,0:13:09.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.96,0:13:10.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.85,0:13:17.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你们得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.49,0:13:18.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.56,0:13:19.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:23.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙虽然是红色的 但他也是鼻屎兽的同伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.56,0:13:24.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会太强
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.89,0:13:28.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让他见识一下我的厉害 大辅你也要打起精神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.30,0:13:29.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.13,0:13:31.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.07,0:13:31.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.02,0:13:36.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小看我的话可是会受伤的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.78,0:13:38.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红热机关枪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.63,0:13:40.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 好烫 好烫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.69,0:13:44.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.43,0:13:44.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.68,0:13:47.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你们得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.31,0:13:48.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.45,0:13:52.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,灾难性臭气
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.59,0:13:55.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.99,0:13:57.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好刺鼻哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.30,0:13:58.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能动了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.73,0:14:02.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起 各位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.82,0:14:05.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果道歉有用的话就不需要警察了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.04,0:14:09.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.12,0:14:11.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.58,0:14:14.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在要打这家伙100下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.99,0:14:16.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.50,0:14:17.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,1
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.33,0:14:18.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,2
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.85,0:14:19.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,3
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.73,0:14:23.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你很有骨气嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.55,0:14:26.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你能坚持到什么时候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.48,0:14:27.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,4
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.90,0:14:28.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,5
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.16,0:14:29.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,6
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.41,0:14:31.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.08,0:14:33.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们什么都做不了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.32,0:14:35.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.57,0:14:36.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.69,0:14:37.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.62,0:14:43.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,69
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.25,0:14:45.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,70
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.68,0:14:46.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,71
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.59,0:14:48.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,72
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.94,0:14:49.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,73
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.02,0:14:50.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,74
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.95,0:14:51.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,75
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.91,0:14:52.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,76
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.32,0:14:54.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,77
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.62,0:14:56.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,78
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.86,0:14:58.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可以输
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.36,0:15:00.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是我倒下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.16,0:15:03.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅会更沮丧的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.66,0:15:06.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.81,0:15:08.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为我那么沮丧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.10,0:15:10.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽才会为我打气
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.30,0:15:12.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.52,0:15:14.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打就打我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.95,0:15:15.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.08,0:15:19.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜 拜托了 放过Ｖ仔兽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.94,0:15:20.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.44,0:15:23.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美丽的友情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.73,0:15:25.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.76,0:15:28.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打完它下一个就是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.04,0:15:29.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,98
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.04,0:15:29.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停手！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.34,0:15:31.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是我能进化的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.86,0:15:33.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.41,0:15:33.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.06,0:15:34.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,99
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.98,0:15:37.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.77,0:15:39.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能坚持到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.52,0:15:43.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是接下来就是最后一击了 下地狱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.68,0:15:45.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.10,0:16:14.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加布兽进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.90,0:16:19.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加鲁鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.88,0:16:26.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.77,0:16:27.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加布兽他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.93,0:16:28.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.73,0:16:33.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妖狐火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.94,0:16:42.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.28,0:16:52.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.07,0:17:10.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.30,0:17:21.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽熬过敌人的鞭打终于进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.58,0:17:22.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次轮到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.17,0:17:25.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽情地战斗决一胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.30,0:17:27.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.07,0:17:28.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.36,0:17:30.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.42,0:17:40.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没结束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.61,0:17:41.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.31,0:17:45.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 好烫 好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.72,0:17:46.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认输了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.93,0:17:47.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.04,0:17:49.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.43,0:17:53.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加鲁鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.61,0:17:55.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.83,0:17:57.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.56,0:18:00.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那座塔出现裂缝的时候就可以进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.16,0:18:04.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道 把这座塔破坏掉的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.15,0:18:09.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 这种事我比较擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.24,0:18:09.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.14,0:18:15.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.79,0:18:26.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.13,0:18:42.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.86,0:18:47.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.84,0:19:05.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 我在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.58,0:19:08.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 黑色魔轮的效力消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.48,0:19:09.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.75,0:19:12.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.13,0:19:15.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这座塔不止是标志而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.16,0:19:19.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还接收了暴龙改造者的力量并向周围发射
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.21,0:19:22.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有电波塔一样的功能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.18,0:19:25.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 泉学长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.01,0:19:26.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.77,0:19:28.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想你的推理是正确的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.71,0:19:33.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样 被选中的孩子们的目标也明确了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.08,0:19:40.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 把暴龙改造者控制区域的黑暗之塔逐个破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.14,0:19:42.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力的 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.58,0:19:43.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.78,0:19:44.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.56,0:19:46.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要把塔破坏掉进化的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.75,0:19:47.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胜利就是我们的了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.28,0:19:48.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.30,0:19:50.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们到矿石兽的区域去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.95,0:19:52.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我们也一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.08,0:19:56.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里由我们来担负起保护的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.89,0:19:58.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.33,0:20:02.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我不好让你担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.87,0:20:03.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.21,0:20:06.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅也成熟了一点呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.42,0:20:06.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.40,0:20:09.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 请看一下这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.33,0:20:11.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.59,0:20:14.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我研究了一下从小京那里借来的神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.49,0:20:15.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就出来了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.08,0:20:17.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像是数码地图
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.57,0:20:22.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里 刚才还是黑色的现在变成白色了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.69,0:20:25.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说这个区域的塔已经被我们破坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.75,0:20:29.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 数码世界的黑色区域应该还在增加
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.90,0:20:31.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是说前面路还很漫长吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.40,0:20:43.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽也进化成暴龙兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.86,0:20:45.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎 是那些家伙干的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.52,0:20:47.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过算了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.14,0:20:50.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在战略地位上也不是什么重要的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.34,0:20:56.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照这样下去 到完全征服这个世界用不了一年的时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.95,0:21:03.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有的数码兽都要臣服于我 服侍我 恭敬我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集預告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.27,0:22:39.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受伤的哥玛兽和阿丈再会
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.74,0:22:42.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像雪崩一样攻击的雪人兽们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.19,0:22:45.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把钢钻兽拖进海里的龙虾兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.18,0:22:47.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,分散了的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.23,0:22:49.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果哥玛兽可以进化的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.26,0:22:53.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是黑暗之塔仍然耸立着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.68,0:22:55.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.95,0:22:57.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「打倒黑暗之塔」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.83,0:22:59.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.15,0:23:00.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,325)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}打倒黑暗之塔

