[Script Info]
Title:
Original Script:
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.15,0:01:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那年夏天后三年过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.65,0:01:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界面临新的危机
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.69,0:01:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然出现的开始狩猎数码兽的少年 暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.30,0:01:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要解救这个世界需要新的被选中的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.23,0:01:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的搭档数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.70,0:02:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 新的冒险现在正要开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式開始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.55,0:02:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}打开数码世界大门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.96,0:02:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.96,0:02:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电脑教室？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.65,0:02:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你们是从数码世界回来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.92,0:02:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是啊 我们回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.65,0:02:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.77,0:02:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然像恐龙一样的数码兽向我们袭击过来…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.52,0:02:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.55,0:02:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京学姐 今天就算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.82,0:02:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 伊织不想去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.11,0:02:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也是很有兴趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.91,0:02:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是再不回去的话 妈妈要担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.02,0:02:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 今天还是回去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.52,0:02:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得这样比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.34,0:02:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吧 京学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.61,0:02:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太狡猾了 就你们去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.32,0:02:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京学姐 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.32,0:02:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把电源关掉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.87,0:02:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.77,0:02:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大门关上了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.98,0:02:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 阿和 要回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.60,0:03:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件很重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.57,0:03:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.18,0:03:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.03,0:03:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.49,0:03:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家真的是很久没有聚在一起了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.86,0:03:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界 到底是个怎样的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.11,0:03:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天绝对要去数码世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.65,0:03:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小京也一起吃晚饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.60,0:03:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.48,0:03:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙现在怎么样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.61,0:03:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说「装甲进化」？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.80,0:03:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是看都没有看过的进化
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.71,0:03:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽它们明明不能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.95,0:03:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅的数码兽却进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.50,0:03:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足球部的大辅去了数码世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.00,0:03:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同一公寓的京学姐和伊织君也拥有新的神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:04:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说那三人是新的被选中的孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.87,0:04:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个叫暴龙改造者的人\N不分青红皂白地狩猎数码兽的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.22,0:04:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽它们没有事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.61,0:04:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐姐也从美国发了邮件过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.12,0:04:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是担心巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.47,0:04:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也去吧 数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.97,0:04:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我们出房间的时候 大门已经关上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.77,0:04:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.26,0:04:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我想明天再去调查下电脑部的电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.89,0:04:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.17,0:04:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.78,0:04:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.01,0:04:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.82,0:04:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我明天有全国模拟考试
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.53,0:04:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天也翘了乐队的练习呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.76,0:04:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 就包在我们身上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.50,0:04:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是发生了什么 要马上通知我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.79,0:04:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.34,0:05:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大门果然还是关着的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.83,0:05:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 泉学长
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.89,0:05:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了 我有点在意昨天的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.51,0:05:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨晚也没有睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.02,0:05:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天请一定要带我去数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.28,0:05:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大门…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.31,0:05:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 大门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.98,0:05:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.07,0:05:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.21,0:05:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是新的神圣计划？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.62,0:05:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我从装甲数码蛋中拿到的三个神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.12,0:05:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快点去吧 数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.33,0:05:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 数码世界可是一个很可怕的地方哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.17,0:05:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只去过一次而已 不要说得这么得意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.92,0:05:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经做好会遇到危险的心理准备了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.74,0:05:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其它的电脑果然都没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.94,0:05:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像只有这台电脑打开着局部的门
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.32,0:05:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是连续两天大门打开是目前为止所没有的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.99,0:06:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之快点去吧 数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.58,0:06:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.51,0:06:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 这不是八神吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.04,0:06:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.73,0:06:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤山老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.28,0:06:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武之内和泉也在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.84,0:06:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕业生聚集在这里做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.10,0:06:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒…倒是老师来干什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.09,0:06:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是电脑部的顾问
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.30,0:06:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 老师会用电脑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.16,0:06:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.05,0:06:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我有件事想请教老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.30,0:06:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.24,0:06:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近都跟不上初中的课程
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.23,0:06:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里说也不方便
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.46,0:06:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank you 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.31,0:06:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 就趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.11,0:07:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是数码世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.27,0:07:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 衣服变了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.93,0:07:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 很帅的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.29,0:07:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.14,0:07:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普普通通吧 我比较帅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.29,0:07:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是我比较帅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.36,0:07:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.22,0:07:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很与众不同呢 这次被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.04,0:07:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时代的关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.53,0:07:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 请别把自己说的老人家似的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.25,0:07:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.95,0:07:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.42,0:07:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼… 我等了很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.23,0:07:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来开始游戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.74,0:07:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上 螳螂兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.84,0:07:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.53,0:07:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.00,0:07:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.15,0:07:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.83,0:07:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 巴达兽的伙伴们找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.67,0:08:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.60,0:08:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.58,0:08:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.56,0:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎 平安无事比什么都好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.37,0:08:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.39,0:08:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太想你了 阿空
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.03,0:08:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.43,0:08:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿空 卧倒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.22,0:08:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.67,0:08:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气炮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.01,0:08:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞翼闪电
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.89,0:08:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫拳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.74,0:08:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然没有神圣尾环的话 就使不出力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.93,0:08:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 装甲进化了收拾它
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.98,0:08:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 数码之心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.24,0:08:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.88,0:08:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会让你这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.88,0:08:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 钻地兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.33,0:08:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻地兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.27,0:09:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深深栖息于地中的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.82,0:09:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是「毒龙钻」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.00,0:09:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.44,0:09:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 毛人兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.83,0:09:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛人兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.73,0:09:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时住在被雪封闭的深山中的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.82,0:09:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.79,0:09:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骨骨回旋镖
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.31,0:09:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.10,0:09:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 被吸到地面里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.58,0:09:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必…必须要救他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.05,0:09:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先逃离这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.99,0:09:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是大辅学长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.92,0:09:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.45,0:09:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气炮
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.83,0:09:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞翼闪电
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.55,0:09:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是连我们在这里也被抓住的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.44,0:09:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连大辅他们也救不了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.29,0:09:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.84,0:09:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的事…这样的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.68,0:09:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.81,0:10:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.52,0:10:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒过来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.10,0:10:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.44,0:10:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 这么简单就被我抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.38,0:10:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是些更有骨气的家伙 真是太失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.91,0:10:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是暴龙改造者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.63,0:10:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.58,0:10:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是和我一样的小孩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你一样？别开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.06,0:10:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你可是天壤之别的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.05,0:10:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你看证据
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.57,0:10:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.62,0:10:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.82,0:10:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 被抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.46,0:11:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 只要可以装甲进化的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.36,0:11:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的 你们没有这个的话什么也做不了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.69,0:11:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 这是怎么回事 神圣计划有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.84,0:11:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们的神圣计划没有任何反应
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.38,0:11:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.96,0:11:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是因为那个的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.53,0:11:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.77,0:11:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.66,0:11:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.65,0:11:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.45,0:11:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简直就像是玛雅遗迹的金字塔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.47,0:11:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那个 阿空
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.74,0:11:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那是 装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.63,0:11:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这个像蛋一样的东西有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.45,0:11:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是爱心的徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.36,0:11:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是知识的徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.92,0:12:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.14,0:12:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重的拿不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.73,0:12:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没能够拿动的勇气徽章的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.17,0:12:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅轻松地就拿起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.62,0:12:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小京 来试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.44,0:12:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织君也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.64,0:12:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我来？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.15,0:12:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.05,0:12:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.52,0:12:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和大辅那时候一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.42,0:12:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.38,0:12:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彬彬有礼 冷静沉着的成长期鸟型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.38,0:12:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.40,0:12:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从容不迫又可爱的成长期哺乳类型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.82,0:13:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫麻鹰兽 一直等待着你的到来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.98,0:13:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.56,0:13:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得真香 叫醒我的人是你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.62,0:13:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是穿山兽 很感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.82,0:13:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 小京 和我一起战斗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.66,0:13:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啊 我才不会什么战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.29,0:13:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 那真是伤脑筋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.67,0:13:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿空姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.12,0:13:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前 美美也说过相同的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.08,0:13:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我不要战斗 」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.11,0:13:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不想看见谁受伤」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.12,0:13:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.69,0:13:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.05,0:13:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「数码兽相遇真是太好了」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「能够一起冒险太好了」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.20,0:13:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样想的日子一定会到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.88,0:13:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.69,0:14:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿空姐姐的手好温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.02,0:14:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织君对数码世界是怎么看的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.49,0:14:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样的 我还不知道 才刚来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有在考虑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.26,0:14:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我也用自己的想法提出了很多假说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.05,0:14:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是新的疑问总是接二连三地浮现出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.57,0:14:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道的事情明明有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.94,0:14:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织君拥有很多求知的心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.58,0:14:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我想的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.78,0:14:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求知的心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.32,0:14:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有不明白的事请随便问
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.08,0:14:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是伙伴 随时都会帮助你们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.30,0:14:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一起思考吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.72,0:14:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.73,0:14:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 小京 伊织君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.84,0:14:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请喊出「数码之心升级」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.25,0:14:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.33,0:15:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.63,0:15:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.93,0:15:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.01,0:15:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像宇宙飞船一样飞翔的兽型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.43,0:15:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是从翅膀发出的攻击 「马赫冲击波」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.47,0:15:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.54,0:15:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.90,0:15:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.99,0:15:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.93,0:15:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地中所向无敌的昆虫型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.75,0:16:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必杀技是钻头发出「金钻冲击」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.62,0:16:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 去救我们的伙伴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.76,0:16:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 把我的神圣计划还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.42,0:16:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.02,0:16:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.53,0:16:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是随便进入别人家后院的惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.90,0:16:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的数码兽成为我的手下这瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.86,0:16:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你欣赏下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.18,0:16:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.66,0:16:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的到的话就试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.52,0:16:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我是不会成为你的手下的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.61,0:16:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.27,0:16:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等待 一直在等待和大辅见面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.16,0:16:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚遇见大辅 怎么可以就成为你的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.98,0:16:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.52,0:16:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么现在就让你试试
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.82,0:16:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.76,0:16:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.21,0:16:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.37,0:16:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.99,0:16:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.30,0:16:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来救你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.98,0:16:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.45,0:17:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你通过这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.88,0:17:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准你碰小贤一根手指
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.56,0:17:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫拳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.40,0:17:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.61,0:17:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.93,0:17:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.45,0:17:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来吧 螳螂兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.31,0:17:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛人兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.67,0:17:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻地兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.82,0:17:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.29,0:17:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.22,0:17:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.10,0:17:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始反击了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.81,0:17:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 Ｖ仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.92,0:17:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.28,0:17:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.63,0:17:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ｖ仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.46,0:18:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.11,0:18:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.70,0:18:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小京 紧紧抓住我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.39,0:18:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.46,0:18:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要破坏黑色魔轮 这样的话大家就恢复正常了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.28,0:18:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.51,0:18:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.61,0:18:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超冰箭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.47,0:18:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰之火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.69,0:18:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.47,0:18:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.43,0:18:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马赫冲击波
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.19,0:18:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.18,0:19:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.52,0:19:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼 很厉害嘛 一定要这样才有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.96,0:19:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有事吧 对不起了 只有那个方法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.81,0:19:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这点疼痛和成为暴龙改造者的手下比起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.28,0:19:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是不值一提
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.72,0:19:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.49,0:19:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像开始非常火大起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.67,0:19:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.13,0:19:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也愿意助我一臂之力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.23,0:19:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以 我奉陪到底
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.38,0:19:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 今后也多指教了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.87,0:19:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是请你多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后也要连我们的份也一起努力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.75,0:19:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我们也一定要努力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.33,0:19:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 阿空 我们也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.85,0:19:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不能输给年轻人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.11,0:19:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.49,0:19:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.84,0:20:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来用哪只数码兽来玩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.22,0:20:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 受不了 受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.31,0:20:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤山老师的话真长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.54,0:20:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 没有事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.11,0:20:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.88,0:20:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连数码兽们都带过来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.86,0:20:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.27,0:20:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实也不是带过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.58,0:20:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是自己跟过来的 但是为什么是这个形状
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.37,0:20:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是回到幼年期了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.81,0:20:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.21,0:20:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为神圣计划不同吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.04,0:20:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 比丘兽和甲虫兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.62,0:20:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿空
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.25,0:20:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿空 我们去调查一些暴龙改造者的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.47,0:21:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是明白了什么会通知你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.12,0:21:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 小心一点 不要勉强哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.11,0:21:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 真对不起 请快点让开
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集預告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.42,0:22:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巨龙兽军团袭来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.45,0:22:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法进化和超进化
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.01,0:22:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和迪路兽只能逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.43,0:22:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳和小光充满不甘
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.64,0:22:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「难道我们没有战斗的力量吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.99,0:22:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在两人心中重新闪耀出希望之光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.49,0:22:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和迪路兽终于装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.37,0:22:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.17,0:23:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.60,0:22:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「数码之心升级」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.17,0:23:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
