[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.99,0:01:35.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们回忆起三年前改变命运的那次露营
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.57,0:01:38.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也回到了当年去过的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.32,0:01:41.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同一个时间里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.32,0:01:43.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才刚刚重建完成的富士电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.99,0:01:45.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却放生了灵异事件
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.49,0:01:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个幽灵竟然是巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.40,0:01:57.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽是来告知危机即将来临 需尽早防备
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.73,0:02:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}寻找暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.23,0:02:12.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们听了巫师兽的话后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.07,0:02:16.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,积极前往数码世界侦查
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.15,0:02:21.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.73,0:02:24.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.57,0:02:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再一下就到山顶了 加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.90,0:02:29.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎 快点上来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.73,0:02:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？甲虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.98,0:02:36.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎你看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.65,0:02:42.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.73,0:02:44.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么有这么多黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.31,0:02:56.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们好残忍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.06,0:03:00.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像是从那个凹下去的地方跑出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.48,0:03:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这只是我的假设
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.73,0:03:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里说不定就是暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.73,0:03:10.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遭了 我们可能被发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.15,0:03:16.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 在这里根本无法进化
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.73,0:03:19.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里交给我就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.23,0:03:20.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.56,0:03:21.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.23,0:03:23.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.40,0:03:27.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.81,0:03:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.14,0:03:39.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃到这里就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.06,0:03:44.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.48,0:03:45.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.81,0:03:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这里做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.81,0:03:50.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个 我们不打算告诉你答案
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.73,0:03:51.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.38,0:03:52.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.06,0:03:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽进化 比多...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.64,0:03:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.98,0:04:03.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在黑暗装甲暴龙机的势力范围内
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.98,0:04:04.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不可能进化的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.98,0:04:06.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们忘记了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.39,0:04:14.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.56,0:04:16.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幸好赶上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.47,0:04:22.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你救了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.06,0:04:23.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.89,0:04:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.81,0:04:29.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甲虫兽进化 比多兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.64,0:04:35.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个就是比多兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.81,0:04:37.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以有更多关于他的资料了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.06,0:04:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.22,0:04:44.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.39,0:04:47.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 还没有回来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.14,0:04:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还好赶回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.05,0:04:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 那里怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.05,0:04:53.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里建了好多好多的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.14,0:04:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.22,0:04:57.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们负责的区域一定也有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.47,0:04:59.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不就像电线杆一样了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.89,0:05:01.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不只是这样而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.39,0:05:03.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们找到暴龙改造者的基地了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.05,0:05:04.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基地？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.72,0:05:09.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我接着去看看有什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.05,0:05:09.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.05,0:05:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 请过来看一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.05,0:05:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先 这是大辅他们去的地区
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.05,0:05:22.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边是阿岳他们去的地区
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.55,0:05:24.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着 这里是我和甲虫兽去的地区
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.64,0:05:25.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连在一起的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.63,0:05:33.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是有规则的在侵略数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.55,0:05:35.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.63,0:05:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.22,0:05:40.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是真的在一点一点征服数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.55,0:05:42.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,时间越来越紧迫了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.63,0:05:44.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们一定要快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:46.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽特意来说的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.55,0:05:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这件事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.55,0:05:49.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:50.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.63,0:05:52.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们不应该还在这里浪费时间
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.88,0:05:54.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然找到了暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.55,0:05:56.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在就去摧毁他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.63,0:05:57.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不对 豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.55,0:05:59.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.80,0:06:01.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要摧毁暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.80,0:06:04.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能草率 一定要制定好计划才行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.38,0:06:05.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.22,0:06:08.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才只是一时冲动说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.88,0:06:11.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为这次不能跟以前一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.38,0:06:12.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.55,0:06:15.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次我们不能再像以前那样当天来回了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.21,0:06:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是  如果我们一直在意回来的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.21,0:06:21.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就没有办法专心攻打基地
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.71,0:06:24.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不打倒暴龙改造者绝不回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.96,0:06:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一定要有这样的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.21,0:06:28.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.38,0:06:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是有这样的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.13,0:06:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是如果到吃晚饭的时间还不回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.88,0:06:34.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会很担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.71,0:06:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,撒个谎不就得了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.05,0:06:39.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比如说去朋友家过夜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.63,0:06:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你常常做这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.88,0:06:43.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是打个比方嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.63,0:06:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想不到数码世界建了这么多黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.21,0:06:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的数码兽根本无法进化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.38,0:06:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算我们一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.29,0:06:54.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也帮不上他们的忙吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.63,0:06:56.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我认为就算我们不去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.63,0:06:58.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是一样可以帮助他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.71,0:07:02.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,露营 就是说我们大家一起去露营
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.88,0:07:03.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,露营？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.71,0:07:07.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说去露营 事实上是去数码世界吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.38,0:07:08.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.71,0:07:12.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 爸妈打电话到露营地的话就穿帮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.46,0:07:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我和阿和他们必须真的去露营
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.21,0:07:18.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就由我们来制造不在场证明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.63,0:07:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？这个主意不错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.96,0:07:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请...请进
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.54,0:07:26.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 欢迎你们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.96,0:07:27.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.71,0:07:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.46,0:07:32.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们聚在一起商量什么事呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.71,0:07:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪个...其实我们正在讨论要去露营的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.87,0:07:40.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.79,0:07:43.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是有没有谁家的大人跟你们一块去啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.62,0:07:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸可以跟我们一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.62,0:07:50.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有问题吗？阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.04,0:07:51.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.29,0:07:54.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我跟你们一起去露营？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.37,0:07:58.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托啦 我都已经跟大家说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.21,0:08:02.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸不是常说还有很多假没有休吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.04,0:08:04.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.79,0:08:08.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸不是刚刚才拿了年终奖吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.12,0:08:10.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你想要买电脑吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.95,0:08:13.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.29,0:08:15.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啦 很恶心哎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.20,0:08:17.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们要去露营是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.62,0:08:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.37,0:08:19.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他们也会去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.04,0:08:20.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.95,0:08:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话 阿和也会去啰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.37,0:08:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.54,0:08:27.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道 我们打个商量嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.37,0:08:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你很烦哎 请你出去好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.12,0:08:31.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我都还没说是什么事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.87,0:08:33.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我们来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.45,0:08:35.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至今仍下落不明的天才少年一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.62,0:08:37.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本台访问到他的父母
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.20,0:08:39.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子一定会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.20,0:08:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信他一定在某个地方活着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.45,0:08:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.12,0:08:47.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤真的是一个很乖巧的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.87,0:08:58.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我们这一次
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.03,0:09:00.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许不能像以前一样当天来回了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.95,0:09:02.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不打倒暴龙改造者绝不会来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.62,0:09:04.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一定要有这样的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.45,0:09:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.53,0:09:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次的冒险跟以前都不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.12,0:09:11.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗？小京
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.70,0:09:15.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还没睡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.87,0:09:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不早点谁的话 明天会起不来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.53,0:09:21.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.20,0:09:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要加油 一定要加油
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.36,0:09:33.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界 GO GO
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.86,0:09:37.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要消灭暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.36,0:09:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.53,0:09:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一大早起床就这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.28,0:09:44.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电脑我已经设定好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.36,0:09:47.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Bingo GO GO Let' s go
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.61,0:09:49.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.78,0:09:51.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边就交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.78,0:09:52.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.03,0:09:55.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么大家出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.70,0:09:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.70,0:10:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.78,0:10:13.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.19,0:10:16.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你了 伯父
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.03,0:10:16.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.19,0:10:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们是不是要出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.19,0:10:24.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和 早上好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.36,0:10:28.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 我怎么不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.86,0:10:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.28,0:10:32.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 先想办法骗过她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.94,0:10:35.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.11,0:10:37.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我听说你们要露营
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.69,0:10:39.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就一起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.69,0:10:40.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.86,0:10:44.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅这一次又要被阿和臭骂一顿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.36,0:10:46.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帅哥的麻烦总是比较多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.61,0:10:48.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 大辅他们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.52,0:10:51.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们坐别的车先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.61,0:10:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们坐的是我爸爸同事的车
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.11,0:10:57.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.02,0:11:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪个 有件事可以拜托你吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.69,0:11:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不可以请你向后转 然后数到十
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.94,0:11:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你的眼睛可以闭上 那就更好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.19,0:11:15.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 1 2...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.69,0:11:17.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸 我们快走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.52,0:11:19.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩不管她吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.86,0:11:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.61,0:11:28.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,6 7 8 9 10
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.02,0:11:34.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.44,0:11:53.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在那上面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.69,0:11:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.60,0:11:57.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 小京...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.69,0:12:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 大事不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.52,0:12:02.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者的基地不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.35,0:12:04.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.10,0:12:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个大洞 那里本来有个突出来的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.27,0:12:19.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.60,0:12:21.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.93,0:12:23.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 等一下 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.93,0:12:28.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的在这里没错吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.93,0:12:30.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对错不了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.52,0:12:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这里怎么会有那么大的洞？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.27,0:12:37.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 居然连基地都一起消失不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.18,0:12:39.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失不见了 怎么可能呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.77,0:12:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.85,0:12:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 事到如今
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.77,0:12:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不可能现在就回去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.27,0:12:45.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去找找看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.43,0:12:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要找到暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.60,0:12:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后摧毁他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.68,0:12:50.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在天空
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.68,0:12:55.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.26,0:12:58.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定 一定...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.76,0:13:02.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 暴龙改造者的基地一定飞到天上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.01,0:13:05.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 太危险了 赶快下来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.68,0:13:06.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.76,0:13:10.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经有证据了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.68,0:13:11.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点自己招供吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.18,0:13:13.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者的基地在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.76,0:13:16.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在想什么啊？ 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.76,0:13:19.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就是元凶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.10,0:13:21.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 请别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.60,0:13:22.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不太对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.76,0:13:25.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是那是小京努力的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.10,0:13:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是无所谓啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.01,0:13:29.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是她又开始做什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.34,0:13:36.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,二等兵井上京　立刻去寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.09,0:13:40.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者位于底下的帝国了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.34,0:13:41.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.18,0:13:46.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你 饶了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.18,0:13:49.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶快回去跟大家一起行动吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.09,0:13:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你很烦哎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.93,0:13:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次的冒险跟以前都不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.93,0:13:53.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 求求你快回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.84,0:13:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你看看我的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.59,0:13:55.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京你听我的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.68,0:14:04.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛兽 全身被电脑病毒寄生的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.68,0:14:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昆虫型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.43,0:14:09.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是可怕的「毒液攻击」和「追击刺杀」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.09,0:14:19.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.67,0:14:25.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.59,0:14:26.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.67,0:14:27.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京...小京...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.17,0:14:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.42,0:14:37.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.76,0:14:47.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.84,0:15:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.67,0:15:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.34,0:15:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽...麻鹰兽... 振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.58,0:15:31.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.08,0:15:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.58,0:15:42.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 只差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.67,0:15:46.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.58,0:15:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.17,0:16:02.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.92,0:16:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽怎么样了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.91,0:16:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.41,0:16:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经做过紧急处理了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.00,0:16:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在要让他安静 等他恢复意识再说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.66,0:16:19.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.08,0:16:23.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.50,0:16:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.33,0:16:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 我自己一个人留下来照顾麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.50,0:16:37.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们继续去找暴龙改造者的基地吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.66,0:16:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.83,0:16:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 我不想再给大家惹更多的麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.33,0:16:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.16,0:16:54.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 那我们走吧  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.32,0:16:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.24,0:16:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...我留下来好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.91,0:17:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.16,0:17:04.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定又会有数码兽来攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.24,0:17:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以需要保护
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.49,0:17:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.91,0:17:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.66,0:17:11.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一有什么事情的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.74,0:17:14.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就用DT暴龙机写信给我们联系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.41,0:17:17.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天黑之前还没找到基地的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.24,0:17:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.16,0:17:22.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们走了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.16,0:17:23.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.49,0:17:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.24,0:17:27.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好努力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.41,0:17:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.49,0:17:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.66,0:17:36.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我昨天说了什么让你很在意的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.57,0:17:38.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.49,0:17:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那句：“大家一定要有决心”
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.07,0:17:47.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是小光的错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.99,0:17:48.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千万不要放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.99,0:17:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.99,0:17:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信这片森林里一定可以找到解毒草
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.49,0:18:00.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我去找找看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.74,0:18:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里也有黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.49,0:18:06.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是最近刚建好不久
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.91,0:18:08.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之先到前面看看再说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.24,0:18:11.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定暴龙改造者的基地就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.90,0:18:17.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.15,0:18:19.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事 穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.15,0:18:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才看到那边...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.99,0:18:23.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.82,0:18:26.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.32,0:18:27.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然你会跟丢的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.74,0:18:30.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我马上过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.82,0:18:40.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在已经知道黑暗漩涡的位置了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.40,0:18:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.74,0:18:46.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只差最后一步了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.57,0:18:50.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.15,0:18:57.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.65,0:19:00.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 你终于醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.82,0:19:01.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.57,0:19:04.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.65,0:19:07.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不要放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.40,0:19:19.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我找到解毒草了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.32,0:19:23.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 先等一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.23,0:19:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一想到要和暴龙改造者决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.23,0:19:31.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就忍不住紧张起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.98,0:19:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且无法控制自己
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.31,0:19:36.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才会有那些奇怪的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.15,0:19:39.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为我的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.40,0:19:42.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才会让麻鹰兽差点就丧命
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.73,0:19:47.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是上紧了发条就停不下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.31,0:19:48.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.23,0:19:51.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样我实在不够资格当一个好伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.06,0:19:53.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不要再自责了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:56.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为这就是最真实的小京啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.23,0:20:04.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而我就喜欢小京你这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.48,0:20:07.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.14,0:20:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我属于那种遇事容易慌张的紧张大师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.81,0:20:12.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后还要请你多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.39,0:20:14.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.14,0:20:26.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个解毒草的效果真是非常好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.64,0:20:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的伤已经完全好了 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.73,0:20:31.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.48,0:20:36.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么声音啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.48,0:20:43.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.98,0:20:47.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪个...一定是暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.56,0:20:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是可以在空中飞的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.31,0:20:54.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 你说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.81,0:21:07.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的原创数码兽就快诞生了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.22,0:22:38.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了征服数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.72,0:22:39.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一只融合了加鲁鲁兽的腿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.22,0:22:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比多兽的头
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.30,0:22:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽跟飞龙兽的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.30,0:22:46.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及恶魔兽黑暗能量的怪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.38,0:22:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于在暴龙改造者的手中诞生了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.55,0:22:52.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面对强大的黑暗完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.05,0:22:53.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们有力量对抗吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.21,0:22:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.46,0:22:57.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「合成魔兽 基米拉兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.21,0:23:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}合成魔兽 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.21,0:23:00.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
