[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.75,0:01:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由于误中陷阱 大辅一行人被关在数码世界海底油田里了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.75,0:01:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织乘着紧急逃生艇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.66,0:01:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回到现实世界向阿丈求助
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.00,0:01:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后来伊织的诚实徽章发光了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.00,0:01:50.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,启动了装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.50,0:01:54.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽装甲进化为潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.53,0:02:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}御台场纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.00,0:02:18.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.25,0:02:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把它放在刚才的远景镜头后面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.58,0:02:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地冈 这部片子举行过驱邪仪式了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.25,0:02:28.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有 有必要吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.00,0:02:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为像这种灵异节目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.08,0:02:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是经常发生些奇怪的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.25,0:02:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.83,0:02:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,例如有鬼影子出现在影片里面等等
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.50,0:02:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种节目怎么可能会有鬼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.66,0:02:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.75,0:02:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.58,0:03:00.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才刚回来你肚子就饿啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.00,0:03:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那有什么办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.91,0:03:04.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我真的肚子饿了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.33,0:03:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 今天我们又收复一块区域
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.08,0:03:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家好好吃一顿零食吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.91,0:03:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Bingo 我又买了新的电玩游戏哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.00,0:03:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个要不要玩啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.08,0:03:14.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么 你买了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.16,0:03:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.08,0:03:18.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.75,0:03:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者已经好久 没有对我们采取行动了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.50,0:03:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织说的一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.08,0:03:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只看到他的地盘在扩大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.91,0:03:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却没有看到任何实际行动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.41,0:03:29.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想那么多干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.66,0:03:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正我们赢了就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.50,0:03:36.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是明天开始我们就不能使用这个教室了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.50,0:03:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.16,0:03:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 因为从明天开始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.08,0:03:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这间教室要给一二年级当电脑夏令营的教室
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.25,0:03:45.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么没有听说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.50,0:03:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那明天开始我们就不能去数码世界了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.33,0:03:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.66,0:03:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们明天刚好有事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.83,0:03:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以无论如何 我们都不能去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.91,0:03:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们？我们是指谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.75,0:03:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是我跟阿岳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.00,0:04:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.58,0:04:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道...是去约会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.08,0:04:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.83,0:04:09.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八分之一（1/8）的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:11.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是八月一日（8/1）的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.83,0:04:16.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是分数的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.66,0:04:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该读成一分之八才对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.16,0:04:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.58,0:04:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 故意欺负我分数不好是不是？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们要不要一起去？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.66,0:04:29.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去约会啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.66,0:04:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是去约会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.33,0:04:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.41,0:04:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说道八月一日 就要提到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.16,0:04:39.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前 也就是1999年的夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.75,0:04:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 那是太一学长他们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.00,0:04:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次到数码世界的日子 是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.58,0:04:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我没有和他们一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.66,0:04:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光那时因为生病所以没去露营
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.83,0:04:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟阿岳第一次见面就是今天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.83,0:04:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.58,0:04:59.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是太一学长他们来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.41,0:05:02.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你们也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.91,0:05:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.50,0:05:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.41,0:05:05.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.50,0:05:06.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.08,0:05:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久没有这样所有人都聚在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.08,0:05:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.08,0:05:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.16,0:05:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天是我们的纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.00,0:05:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天对孩子们来说是个永远难忘的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.75,0:05:21.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们经历了一个好像很长又好像很短的旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.58,0:05:27.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们三个人从太一等人口中听到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.75,0:05:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很多他们在数码世界里的冒险经历
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.33,0:05:33.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然有这种事情 真不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.08,0:05:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐真的很不一样耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:37.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.83,0:05:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以小光和阿岳才会变成现在这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.58,0:05:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一场又一场的战斗与冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.16,0:05:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们遇到的事情一整天都说不完
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.25,0:05:53.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一次又不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.75,0:05:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说都觉得很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.16,0:05:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是录像机当时拍摄到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.41,0:06:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么倒带重播的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.25,0:06:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该会一模一样才对
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.91,0:06:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我的第一份工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.66,0:06:10.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里也有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.91,0:06:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知是我们的节目而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.83,0:06:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家电视台全部都是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.58,0:06:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部 怎么会呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.66,0:06:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定被诅咒了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.75,0:06:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你不要胡说八道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.58,0:06:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这幢大楼才刚重建好不久
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.16,0:06:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且机器也全部都是新的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.08,0:06:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.75,0:06:33.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们三个怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.41,0:06:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下子听到太多不可思议的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.00,0:06:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以脑筋还没有转过来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉得好像连肚子都饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.08,0:06:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得脑子好像再也装不下东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.33,0:06:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你的脑容量太小了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.66,0:06:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在要把棒子交到你们手上了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.58,0:06:50.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.41,0:06:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.58,0:06:54.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.16,0:07:01.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久没来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.41,0:07:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 你这里好像永远都是那么脏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.41,0:07:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么办法
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.58,0:07:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两个男人住在一起就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.25,0:07:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要我来帮你洗衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.66,0:07:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的家事不用你操心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.08,0:07:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前来我来这里住的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.91,0:07:17.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也说一样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.83,0:07:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.58,0:07:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有吗？三年前就是去露营那天
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.41,0:07:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,记得那时你什么事都不会 都要妈妈帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.41,0:07:31.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的房间妈妈永远帮你打理的很整齐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.33,0:07:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿的都是洗干净的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.58,0:07:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么时候回来一定都有饭吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.25,0:07:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我没有想那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.00,0:07:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓 其实你也不用想太多
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.16,0:07:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易才熬过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.50,0:07:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道以后能不能来这帮我们打扫洗衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.66,0:07:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫妈妈来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.25,0:07:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我大概会挨骂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.83,0:07:55.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚上你要吃什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.75,0:07:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正这个家本来就是我在做饭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.75,0:07:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过也不要期待能吃到好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.50,0:08:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃什么都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.75,0:08:03.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要是你做的 我一定把它吃光光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.08,0:08:06.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你说的 不要后悔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.08,0:08:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了 你每天都给爸爸吃这种东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.08,0:08:18.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 今天比较特别
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.16,0:08:21.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了招待你才做的特别餐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.58,0:08:22.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特别餐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.75,0:08:24.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吃普通的就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.91,0:08:26.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能怠慢稀客呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.33,0:08:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一年也只能来这么一次
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.75,0:08:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就好像七夕的牛郎和织女一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.00,0:08:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一年见一次面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.08,0:08:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,牛郎和织女听到一定会被你气死的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.91,0:08:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.50,0:08:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你来来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.58,0:08:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳来了 原来是今天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.66,0:08:45.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 爸爸原来忘记了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.41,0:08:46.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.41,0:08:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 是每年的今天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.25,0:08:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.08,0:08:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说有事也算没事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.66,0:09:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 你的口气好诡异
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.25,0:09:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很诡异是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.91,0:09:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 的确很诡异
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.58,0:09:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我实在是不愿意想
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.50,0:09:11.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不管我怎么避免
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.25,0:09:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就会一直想到很诡异的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.16,0:09:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.83,0:09:16.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.75,0:09:19.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你看到走廊上有一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.08,0:09:20.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你会怎么想？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.08,0:09:23.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想？我想他一定是要去什么地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.83,0:09:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正常情况下应该如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.00,0:09:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就偷看了下 看他要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.50,0:09:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果你猜...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.41,0:09:32.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.75,0:09:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我以为看到有人的走廊上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.50,0:09:37.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然一个人都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.50,0:09:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能本来就没人 是你看错了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.33,0:09:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的有道理
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.41,0:09:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是我的错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.00,0:09:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是这样 你会怎么想？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.41,0:09:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正在剪辑的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.41,0:09:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果画面上出现了当时没有拍摄的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.25,0:09:54.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该是拍的时候有拍到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.41,0:09:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是当时没发现而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.25,0:09:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？你是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.08,0:09:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正常情况下应该是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.91,0:10:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是说嘛 这样就对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.91,0:10:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 闹鬼了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.83,0:10:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.41,0:10:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果只是一两个人看见的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.50,0:10:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那还有可能是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.66,0:10:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是有十个二十个人看到 那就...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.33,0:10:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 这个MD是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.66,0:10:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是樱出那家伙帮我录的佛经
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.58,0:10:19.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佛经？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.75,0:10:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 听说对付牛鬼蛇神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.66,0:10:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,播这个很有用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.16,0:10:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是根本就没用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.25,0:10:28.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真是太可笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.41,0:10:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先去洗澡好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.58,0:10:39.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那我先吃饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.25,0:10:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辣死了...辣死了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.83,0:11:02.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.66,0:11:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.41,0:11:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事情就不好收拾了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.16,0:11:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个节目后天就要播出了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.83,0:11:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说这个有什么用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.00,0:11:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们总不能播这种东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.08,0:11:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.83,0:11:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次剪片就碰到这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是很用心拍的片子耶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.41,0:11:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.41,0:11:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是放来试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.16,0:11:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说佛经
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.58,0:11:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么换成MD 还在听这种东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.41,0:11:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候管不了那么多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.75,0:11:30.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.50,0:11:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有声音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.83,0:11:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是坏了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.83,0:11:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该不会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.25,0:11:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这台MD才刚买不久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.24,0:12:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}迪...路...兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.50,0:11:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪的佛经哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.41,0:11:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊 这个声音不是从MD跑出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.16,0:11:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.75,0:12:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？有怪声音
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.58,0:12:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是东京铁塔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.41,0:12:31.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.25,0:12:34.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,铁塔现在也已经修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.83,0:12:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一次东京铁塔好像坏掉了 是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.66,0:12:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候整个东京都好乱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.91,0:12:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为数码世界的邪恶数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.91,0:12:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都跑到现实世界来作乱了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.75,0:12:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,涉谷还是没变 人好多哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.16,0:13:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.50,0:13:11.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们其实都是好的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.58,0:13:16.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个...好不容易大家都聚在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.75,0:13:19.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在做个实验 你们觉得怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.08,0:13:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什么实验啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.66,0:13:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是有关数码世界大门的实验
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.58,0:13:27.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门？就是我们每次使用的那个大门吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.91,0:13:33.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 每次我们都是从电脑教室的电脑进出数码世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.83,0:13:38.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以想测试下从别的地方能不能进入数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.00,0:13:39.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么实验呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.08,0:13:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从别的地方也可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.91,0:13:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我现在只能说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.16,0:13:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定真的可以从别的地方出入
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思啊？ 光子郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.50,0:13:50.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,换句话说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.50,0:13:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为并不是只有我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.25,0:13:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每次使用的那台电脑才能打开大门
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.66,0:13:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门之所以能够打开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.33,0:14:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我们手上的D3装甲暴龙机的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.66,0:14:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.75,0:14:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 以前我就注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.41,0:14:05.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我没有十足的把握
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.75,0:14:08.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以一直都没有说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.16,0:14:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是有时也会遇到今天这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.00,0:14:13.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能够使用电脑教室的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.91,0:14:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一这时候暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.25,0:14:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚好在那里有什么行动的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.91,0:14:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们什么事也不能做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.66,0:14:19.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.91,0:14:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们应该从什么地方进去比较好？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:23.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就从这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.83,0:14:24.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.25,0:14:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有电脑就可以进去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.83,0:14:30.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 说不定就算没有电脑也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.75,0:14:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有D3装甲暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.91,0:14:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以进入数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.83,0:14:39.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你来试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.33,0:14:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.41,0:14:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.08,0:14:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就试试看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.33,0:14:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.50,0:14:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.83,0:14:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门真的打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.58,0:14:57.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.41,0:15:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然都已经打开了 就走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.16,0:15:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.16,0:15:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家里来了这么多人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.00,0:15:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.66,0:15:10.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.16,0:15:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.41,0:15:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门口有那么多双鞋子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.50,0:15:15.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,房里却没人 这不是很奇怪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.91,0:15:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.58,0:15:20.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关起来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.08,0:15:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然从这里也可以打开
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.58,0:15:25.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是早一点知道这个秘密就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.16,0:15:27.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那昨天八月一日
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.58,0:15:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家就可以一起去数码世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.58,0:15:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 我发现的太慢了 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.91,0:15:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 这不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.25,0:15:37.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明年还有机会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.41,0:15:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然从自己家里去数码世界很方便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.83,0:15:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是说不定也会有以外的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.41,0:15:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.33,0:15:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有朋友来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.58,0:15:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伯母 打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.91,0:15:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们好 慢慢玩哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.41,0:15:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织说的一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.33,0:15:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要从自己家的电脑出入的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.33,0:16:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要比以前更小心不要被家人发现才好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.00,0:16:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果发现我们无缘无故从房间里面消失
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.83,0:16:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们一定会吓一跳跑去警察局报案的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.33,0:16:12.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要想好对策以防万一
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.08,0:16:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天气怎么突然就变了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.33,0:16:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闪电打中电视台了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.91,0:16:31.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快跑...快跑...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.58,0:16:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊...快逃...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.58,0:16:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.08,0:17:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.91,0:17:07.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.50,0:17:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}迪...路...兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.50,0:17:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出来吧 我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.91,0:17:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再叫了 我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.16,0:17:27.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是数码兽在作怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.83,0:17:28.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.08,0:17:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 一定是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.08,0:17:33.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么知道一定是数码兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.16,0:17:35.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为同样是数码兽 所以知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.25,0:17:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁兽进化 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.41,0:17:48.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽进化 穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.57,0:17:53.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽进化 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.16,0:17:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.33,0:17:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现实世界里一旦出现数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.66,0:17:59.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是我们的敌人 不会错的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.33,0:18:01.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是数码兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.83,0:18:02.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.83,0:18:04.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.58,0:18:06.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}迪路兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.15,0:18:05.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.58,0:18:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.91,0:18:14.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.91,0:18:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.91,0:18:21.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.83,0:18:23.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在叫迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.75,0:18:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽...迪路兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.08,0:18:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.91,0:18:37.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.91,0:18:40.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.08,0:18:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.91,0:18:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问他是...？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.25,0:18:44.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.66,0:18:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽 是你在叫我是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.08,0:18:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为有件事我一定要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.58,0:18:52.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有事要告诉我 什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.91,0:18:53.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打败敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.33,0:18:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,凭你们现在的力量是没有办法打的过的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.58,0:19:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敌人 你是说暴龙改造者吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.91,0:19:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敌人 不只是现在看到的对手而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的背后还有比这个更强大的黑暗力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.75,0:19:11.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗...只靠武力是没有办法赶走的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.91,0:19:14.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要让黑暗所吞没的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.41,0:19:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恢复本来的模样一定要...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.50,0:19:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要怎么样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.16,0:19:20.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温柔能够绽放出金黄色的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.33,0:19:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温柔能够绽放出金黄色的光芒？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.16,0:19:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且只有温柔也是不够的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.00,0:19:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不只要温柔 还要有金黄色的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.58,0:19:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.25,0:19:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,时间越来越紧迫了 你们要快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.33,0:19:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.75,0:19:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.66,0:19:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.08,0:20:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽...巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.41,0:20:03.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.41,0:20:05.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.41,0:20:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.08,0:20:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是特地跑来告诉我们这个讯息的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.83,0:20:19.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天也是巫师兽的忌日
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.75,0:20:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后再也见不到了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.08,0:20:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定可以再见的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.33,0:20:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.58,0:20:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.33,0:20:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为我们而死
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.83,0:20:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会是白白牺牲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.16,0:21:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然见面只是短短的几分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.50,0:21:02.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽留给孩子们的讯息
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.16,0:21:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温柔能够绽放出金黄色的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.00,0:21:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么意思呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.61,0:22:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}寻找暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.66,0:22:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界里到处竖立着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.16,0:22:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,代表邪恶的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.91,0:22:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的力量越来越大了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:45.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要找到暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.66,0:22:47.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把事情做个了结
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.08,0:22:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备好就出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:53.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅一行人展开了长期的数码世界之旅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.83,0:22:55.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.08,0:22:57.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「寻找暴龙改造者的基地」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.75,0:22:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
