[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,SimHei,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,1,1,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.58,0:01:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅等人在数码世界遇见了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.91,0:01:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,2001年被选召的孩子 麦克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.75,0:01:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅没想到原来美国也有被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.75,0:01:46.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.75,0:01:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美纯真的徽章和小京新的装甲数码蛋产生了共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.41,0:01:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽装甲进化为忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}忍者兽的武功秘籍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.16,0:02:15.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 这个地区也是我们的了 对不对？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.66,0:02:23.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不要乱动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.08,0:02:32.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 真的很痒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.16,0:02:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不要那么大声好不好 会被听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.41,0:02:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为真的很痒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.33,0:02:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要笑了 真那么痒吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.41,0:02:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅一个人在浴室笑得那么大声
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.08,0:02:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来播报下一则新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.58,0:03:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然行踪不明的天才少年 一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.91,0:03:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失踪至今已经两个多月仍下落不明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.83,0:03:10.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,警方担心他是否遭遇不测
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.00,0:03:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以仍在搜寻之中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.91,0:03:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在看耶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.58,0:03:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在时间不早了 快点睡觉去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.25,0:03:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这很碍手碍脚 不要放在这里好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.58,0:03:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.66,0:03:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天我们再到数码世界去吧 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.00,0:03:49.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关灯啰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.08,0:03:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 不好了 不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.58,0:04:02.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下... 陛下...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.66,0:04:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大事不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.50,0:04:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 请快点起床
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.41,0:04:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔快要盖好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.16,0:04:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.41,0:04:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下请看 黑暗之塔在森林的那一边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.75,0:04:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 暴龙改造者居然跑到我的地盘上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:05:00.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者最近不知道在做什么 都没有消息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自上次他抓走了亚古兽说要做实验之后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.00,0:05:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就没有再出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.66,0:05:06.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.41,0:05:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过他还是继续在数码世界扩张他的领土
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.50,0:05:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道他忙得没有时间跟我们玩了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.41,0:05:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能他又在计划什么新的诡计
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.75,0:05:19.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们就先下手为强
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.58,0:05:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要从暴龙改造者手里抢回土地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.91,0:05:23.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算只有一个地区也好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.00,0:05:32.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.00,0:05:34.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.08,0:05:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么地方啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.75,0:05:50.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.41,0:05:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里和昨天电视上看到的一模一样耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.41,0:05:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是京都的大秦制版厂吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.66,0:05:58.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该是哪里的电影城
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.83,0:06:00.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 这里的确是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.08,0:06:02.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.83,0:06:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的确是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.00,0:06:13.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.41,0:06:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得有人要出现一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.83,0:06:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花拉兽 整张脸是朵花的成长期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.58,0:06:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是释放让人失去战斗意志的花粉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.00,0:06:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「过敏喷雾」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.91,0:06:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蘑菇兽 外形像颗蘑菇的成长期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.33,0:06:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是丢掷小型蘑菇炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:46.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「剧毒超蘑菇」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.50,0:06:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过敏喷雾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.33,0:06:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剧毒超蘑菇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.41,0:06:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勾勾拳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.08,0:06:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甩耳光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.50,0:06:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过敏喷雾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.83,0:07:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,猫儿眼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.33,0:07:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打不过你了 好累哦 我要睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.08,0:07:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剧毒超蘑菇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.50,0:07:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,羽毛回力刀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.25,0:07:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你给我记住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.25,0:07:26.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.50,0:07:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊贺兽 行走在数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.08,0:07:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到处修炼忍术的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.75,0:07:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是投掷巨大的飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.75,0:07:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「伊贺飞镖」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.83,0:07:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然躲得过我的伊贺飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.00,0:07:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想必你也有两下子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.00,0:07:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过这次你一定躲不过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.58,0:07:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,见识过了 虽然你的飞镖技术还算不错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.25,0:07:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过在数码世界 你还只算第二名
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.25,0:07:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 那么第一名是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.58,0:08:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是在下我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备啰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.25,0:08:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.00,0:08:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.58,0:08:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉涌般的纯真 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.50,0:08:22.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说你也会使用飞镖 对吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.33,0:08:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.25,0:08:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不服气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.00,0:08:36.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽真够帅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.25,0:08:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.00,0:08:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.75,0:08:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要跑...不要跑...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.75,0:08:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔头槌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.25,0:08:48.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山抓
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.33,0:08:49.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空气炮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.58,0:08:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫拳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.25,0:08:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去没完没了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.33,0:08:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整个小镇的数码兽都被控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.25,0:08:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 快点逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.83,0:09:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等我...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.25,0:09:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家 这边
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.50,0:09:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪蛙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.58,0:09:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.83,0:09:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 这边
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.24,0:09:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下水道？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.75,0:09:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么江户时代的街上会有下水道？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.50,0:09:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为这里不是江户时代
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.50,0:09:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.58,0:09:27.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要管这个了 快点进去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.58,0:09:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽回来 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.50,0:09:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽快回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.25,0:09:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天到此为止 下次再比个高低
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.08,0:09:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.00,0:09:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是被选召的孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.75,0:09:50.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上次怪蛙兽和蝌蚪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.50,0:09:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多亏有你们搭救才能逃过一劫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.25,0:09:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的很感谢你们拔刀相助
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.00,0:09:57.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蝌蚪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.25,0:10:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是我和美美遇见的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.00,0:10:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.00,0:10:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实你们是这个地方的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.58,0:10:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直都住在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.33,0:10:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伺候国王陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.25,0:10:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.33,0:10:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道暴龙改造者在什么地方吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.50,0:10:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想他不在我们的城里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.00,0:10:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是有一些黑色魔轮飞过来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.08,0:10:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,城里的百姓一下子都被洗脑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.83,0:10:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果只有住在宫殿里的人没被洗脑 是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:38.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们再也不要变成暴龙改造者的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.08,0:10:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被他控制
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.25,0:10:44.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下 我们现在该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.33,0:10:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.75,0:10:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像这种时候嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.83,0:10:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.83,0:11:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就睡觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.75,0:11:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你也变成暴龙改造者的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.08,0:11:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一个就是那个家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.75,0:11:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.58,0:11:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们先破坏黑暗之塔再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.25,0:11:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么困难的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.00,0:11:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要装甲进化就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.08,0:11:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不对 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.33,0:11:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 反正对手看起来不堪一击的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.83,0:12:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,简单 简单 没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.25,0:12:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是地震吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.58,0:12:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要地震 好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 镇定一点 地震已经停了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.75,0:12:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.58,0:12:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下发疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.50,0:12:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.25,0:12:40.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪蛙皇 顾名思义
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.58,0:12:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是所有怪蛙兽的国王
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.33,0:12:42.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.50,0:12:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是身上大喇叭所发出的低音波
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.75,0:12:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「破坏音波」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.08,0:12:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊 不要丢下我一个人...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.25,0:12:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.00,0:12:58.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蝌蚪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.25,0:13:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在连陛下都被暴龙改造者控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.00,0:13:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们 救救陛下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.00,0:13:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我们身上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.58,0:13:10.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 小心一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.83,0:13:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们一起来攻击了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.58,0:13:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 上了 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.50,0:13:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.33,0:13:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.25,0:13:35.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.50,0:13:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坚固的友情 雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.25,0:13:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.83,0:14:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.25,0:14:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.33,0:14:22.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.58,0:14:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.00,0:14:38.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.33,0:14:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.58,0:15:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.00,0:15:23.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.75,0:15:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备了 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.33,0:15:28.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.83,0:15:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.58,0:15:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个飞镖是...伊贺兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.00,0:15:37.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.33,0:15:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是一封挑战书
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.08,0:15:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挑战书？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.50,0:15:46.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.50,0:15:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.25,0:15:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 还是拿不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.25,0:15:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.58,0:16:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 坐上来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.08,0:16:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剧毒超蘑菇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.75,0:16:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷电伏特
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.83,0:16:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.83,0:16:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就全部一下解决掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.50,0:16:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.75,0:16:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等你很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.75,0:16:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.00,0:16:34.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放马过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.50,0:16:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京快点回到天守阁里去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.25,0:16:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽 你一定要赢哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.00,0:16:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.75,0:16:47.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你完了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.33,0:16:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.50,0:16:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.75,0:16:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏音波
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.50,0:17:01.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.50,0:17:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有我们没有办法打倒完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.24,0:17:08.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.00,0:17:11.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如引诱那家伙去破坏黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.83,0:17:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.08,0:17:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:19.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.58,0:17:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏音波
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.25,0:17:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.25,0:17:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.25,0:17:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪...怎么会这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.58,0:17:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我到底在干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.58,0:17:45.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒竖冲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.50,0:17:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.25,0:17:55.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 伊织 拜托你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.08,0:17:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.75,0:17:59.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闪电角斩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.00,0:18:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.58,0:18:04.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.25,0:18:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.25,0:18:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.08,0:18:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 小京呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.50,0:18:15.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽也不在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.00,0:18:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她到底到哪里去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.25,0:18:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊贺流派忍者飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.08,0:18:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔都已经倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.83,0:18:30.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个为什么还要打啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.25,0:18:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为不可能有两个人同时使用飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.50,0:18:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊贺流派独门分身术
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.75,0:18:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊贺流派飞镖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.33,0:18:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,树叶隐身术
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.00,0:18:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.33,0:18:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊贺兽 你觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.25,0:18:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.58,0:19:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,分出胜负了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.25,0:19:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次...下次我一定要打败你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.83,0:19:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你给我记住
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.83,0:19:13.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽 你太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.50,0:19:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太帅了 我好喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.24,0:19:18.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.75,0:19:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.08,0:19:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.75,0:19:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.58,0:19:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才到底跑到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.83,0:19:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有点事嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.25,0:19:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们能不能趁现在取下黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.58,0:19:41.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太麻烦了 反正他都睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.25,0:19:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看不必了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.50,0:19:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以这么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.75,0:19:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.08,0:19:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以...不可以...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.50,0:19:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你太残忍了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.50,0:19:57.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是开玩笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.25,0:20:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 只是开玩笑而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.33,0:20:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那就大家一起瞄准黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.25,0:20:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.33,0:20:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.50,0:20:11.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.75,0:20:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.58,0:20:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.75,0:20:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.33,0:20:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陛下...陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.58,0:20:31.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 你们在哭什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.00,0:20:37.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的非常非常谢谢你们的帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.50,0:20:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感激不尽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.08,0:20:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事用不着道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.25,0:20:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看他得意忘形的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.00,0:20:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不是嘛 还真得嘞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.75,0:20:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是举手之劳而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.08,0:20:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.00,0:20:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.08,0:20:54.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些小鬼又攻下我们一城了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.83,0:20:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随他们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.83,0:21:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔给他们一点甜头尝尝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.08,0:21:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才可以松懈他们的戒心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.08,0:21:05.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正他们是永远不可能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.49,0:21:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这个天才的计划的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.33,0:22:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作战计划失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.58,0:22:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能有一个人能够对外面救援
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.33,0:22:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织不打算以说谎来完成任务
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.24,0:22:44.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为爷爷叮嘱过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.74,0:22:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是有阿丈温和体贴的劝说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.33,0:22:48.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及始终相信伊织的穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.33,0:22:50.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有已经找到的诚实装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.33,0:22:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,载着伊织的新数码兽出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.83,0:22:55.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.99,0:22:57.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「潜鲨兽 冲出海底」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.90,0:22:59.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}潜鲨兽 冲出海底
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.33,0:23:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
