[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.24,0:01:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面对因为暴龙改造者而黑暗进化的亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.60,0:01:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅虽然一时下不了手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.20,0:01:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是当他明白大家因为相信亚古兽 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.04,0:01:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而全力战斗的心情之后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.20,0:01:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅的疑虑也消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.64,0:01:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的装甲数码蛋有了反应
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽装甲进化为雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.92,0:02:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在与大家的通力合作下成功救回了亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.99,0:02:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}数码兽牧场的决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.00,0:02:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.92,0:02:31.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 武之内同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.76,0:02:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我的脚好像有点扭伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.64,0:02:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.04,0:02:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一位 有迫同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.52,0:02:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是数码世界的比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.96,0:02:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.08,0:03:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要快点通知小光他们才行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.64,0:03:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.96,0:03:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再一下下就好了 这里的毛有点翘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.92,0:03:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 又不是要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.60,0:03:17.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.76,0:03:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的好爱漂亮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.40,0:03:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系 别管我嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.16,0:03:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只不过是去散步而已耶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.68,0:03:29.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.76,0:03:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.20,0:03:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃得好饱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.72,0:03:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一大早就吃这么撑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.08,0:03:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁兽 你还不是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.84,0:03:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这个月的零用钱一定会透支啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.48,0:03:47.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.28,0:03:51.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是比丘兽来的求救信号
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.84,0:03:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽...不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:03:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.36,0:04:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.64,0:04:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.16,0:04:21.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是你啊 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.48,0:04:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慌慌张张的 一点也不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.12,0:04:26.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才收到空学姐发来的电子信
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.12,0:04:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.20,0:04:29.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空传来的电子信
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.56,0:04:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.20,0:04:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳跟小光呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.60,0:04:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们还没有来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.12,0:04:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会不会他们没有留意到有信
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.56,0:04:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好宁静的感觉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.16,0:05:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一站要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.48,0:05:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...我的公主
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.60,0:05:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.36,0:05:13.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你给我记住 巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.52,0:05:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你才是呢 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.00,0:05:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能是去约会了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.68,0:05:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事 开玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.80,0:05:25.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就我们几个去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.16,0:05:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.24,0:05:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽的求救信号是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.72,0:05:37.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是暴龙改造者控制的区域
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.28,0:05:38.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.68,0:05:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.16,0:05:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.36,0:06:15.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是美国的西部小镇吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.36,0:06:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像没有看到黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.04,0:06:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定在某个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.16,0:06:38.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们去那边看一看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.04,0:06:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.44,0:06:48.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了 有没有人在家？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.76,0:06:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.00,0:06:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你们来到西部小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.00,0:07:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是这个小镇上维护正义的警长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.36,0:07:01.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,五角星兽 大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.60,0:07:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,五角星兽 穿着五角星型的装甲西服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.88,0:07:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连围巾和靴子上都有商标记号的突然变异型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.24,0:07:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「流星雨召唤」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.36,0:07:19.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我代表这个小镇 欢迎你们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.00,0:07:21.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是沙漠迎宾牛奶 请用
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.00,0:07:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迎宾牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.96,0:07:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里的气候很干燥 你们一定渴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.52,0:07:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请喝点沙漠迎宾牛奶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.88,0:07:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.96,0:07:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这么一说我还真的口渴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.20,0:07:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.08,0:07:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.12,0:07:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义警长的服务真的好周到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.32,0:07:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.88,0:07:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢警长...谢谢警长...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.88,0:07:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好享用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.56,0:07:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 警长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.40,0:07:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有何指教呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.68,0:07:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.36,0:07:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.84,0:07:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你听过她的名字吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.72,0:08:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛 我知道这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.44,0:08:03.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我也正在找她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.84,0:08:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽 她做错了什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.80,0:08:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通说她被暴龙改造者追杀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.28,0:08:14.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以逃到这一座小镇上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.72,0:08:16.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身为维护正义的警长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.72,0:08:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有责任保护她的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.04,0:08:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.16,0:08:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为比丘兽做错了什么坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.36,0:08:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要逮捕她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.96,0:08:27.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空 比丘兽不会做坏事 你放心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.92,0:08:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.36,0:08:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除非她被套上黑色魔轮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.04,0:08:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就另当别论了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.88,0:08:39.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事...真不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.12,0:08:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色魔轮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.00,0:08:44.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才还觉得很纳闷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.92,0:08:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么暴龙改造者控制的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.28,0:08:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也有维护正义的警长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.52,0:08:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 你刚才可不是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.44,0:08:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自称维护正义的人 通常都是有问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.64,0:08:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小镇才说好像慢了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.56,0:09:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被你们发现也没有办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.52,0:09:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是暴龙改造者大王的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.56,0:09:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦发现被选召的孩子们 一律格杀勿论
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.80,0:09:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者现在在什么地方？ 快说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.48,0:09:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙正在改良...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.32,0:09:23.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 是大王正在改良黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.84,0:09:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 你们逃也没有用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.76,0:09:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.32,0:09:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 现在我去帮你们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.72,0:09:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在行刑台后面做一片墓地吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.56,0:09:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.24,0:10:01.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.92,0:10:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.20,0:10:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.88,0:10:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比丘兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.56,0:10:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么这么慢呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.80,0:10:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.92,0:10:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你既然来了 我就原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.00,0:10:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你出了什么什么事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.32,0:10:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为暴龙改造者的飞龙兽突然来攻击我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.72,0:10:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打不过 所以只好逃到这个镇上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.48,0:10:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到这里也被他控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.64,0:10:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,疲惫的旅行者啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.88,0:11:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来一杯冰牛奶怎么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.48,0:11:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的口好渴哦 我要喝冰牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.16,0:11:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.12,0:11:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔头槌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.88,0:11:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一片墙壁好硬哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.12,0:11:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.84,0:11:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.08,0:11:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.12,0:11:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你进化成钢钻兽去破坏那片墙壁好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.80,0:11:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是那件事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.64,0:11:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.76,0:11:49.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的肚子好饿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.48,0:11:55.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 我们今天早上都还没有吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.64,0:11:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.76,0:12:04.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好像听到声音
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.96,0:12:14.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越来越近了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.44,0:12:23.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是正义的一方...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.76,0:12:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.28,0:12:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.20,0:12:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体就是一把手枪的突然变异型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.40,0:12:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有强烈的正义感
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.44,0:12:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 另一方面又很喜欢赌博
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.96,0:12:33.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「正义之魂」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.80,0:12:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干什么？你们这是什么眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己说自己是正义的一方一定有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.16,0:12:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.00,0:12:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定待会就会发现他的帽子底下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.48,0:12:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也有一个黑色魔轮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.08,0:12:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.96,0:12:57.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能会被暴龙改造者所控制呢 你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.88,0:12:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那围巾呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.00,0:12:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.84,0:13:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靴子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.80,0:13:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.96,0:13:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手套
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.00,0:13:03.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.68,0:13:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上衣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.56,0:13:04.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.32,0:13:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裤子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.92,0:13:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.72,0:13:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.48,0:13:08.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.64,0:13:11.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿帮了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.44,0:13:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们太过分了...太过分了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.52,0:13:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照这么看来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.48,0:13:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是真的来救我们几个出去的啰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.00,0:13:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.48,0:13:23.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.36,0:13:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...我只想和女孩子玩扑克牌
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.40,0:13:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以只救女生就好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.00,0:13:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.20,0:13:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你也就我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.16,0:13:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我不想和男生玩牌
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.52,0:13:37.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然没错 这个家伙很不正常
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.40,0:13:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,岂止是不太正常而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.44,0:13:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看简直就是变态
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.68,0:13:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐们 出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.72,0:13:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.64,0:13:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出发
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.28,0:13:59.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.64,0:14:01.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等吃过午饭再来处死他们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.76,0:14:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃午饭啰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.96,0:14:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.44,0:14:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才左轮兽来过把女生都救走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.72,0:14:25.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他说他只想跟女生玩扑克牌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.72,0:14:27.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙很奇怪耶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.72,0:14:29.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽这个臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.32,0:14:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天我非要跟他拼个你死我活不可
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.44,0:14:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.20,0:14:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.20,0:14:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.68,0:14:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,午饭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.16,0:14:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要填饱肚子就可以装甲进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.44,0:14:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.80,0:14:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.84,0:14:49.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把我身上的绳子当食物吃掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.32,0:14:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当食物？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.08,0:14:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起合作的话也许会成功
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.48,0:14:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看太难了 你没看到她的枪法吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.32,0:15:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.48,0:15:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在左轮兽要在这里和两位小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.24,0:15:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比赛玩扑克牌接龙啰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.04,0:15:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍手...欢呼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.04,0:15:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看我们还是暂时乖乖的陪他玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.76,0:15:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.84,0:15:21.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 只差一点点了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.44,0:15:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,写了 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.28,0:15:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小事 没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.96,0:15:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.72,0:15:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把它套过来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.00,0:15:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 现在把方块七拿出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.44,0:15:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.44,0:15:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.12,0:15:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是谁呢 原来是你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.28,0:15:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽 我们来决斗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.64,0:15:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决斗？ 有什么问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.96,0:15:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,套上了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.76,0:16:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有关系 穿山兽你尽量吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.88,0:16:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不好意思 那我就先吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.52,0:16:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 你今天早上已经吃了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.80,0:16:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是忍耐一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.76,0:16:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.76,0:16:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.76,0:16:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我已经可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.76,0:16:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.92,0:16:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.68,0:16:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.80,0:16:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.00,0:17:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 轮到我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:05.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.11,0:17:12.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.24,0:17:27.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坚固的友情 雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.80,0:17:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们三步决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.08,0:17:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第三步就决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.44,0:17:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事情怎么会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.44,0:17:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.72,0:17:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.16,0:17:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.44,0:17:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决斗算我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.88,0:17:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你...你根本没有走第三步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.24,0:17:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才不是说了吗？第三步决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.56,0:17:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个小人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.40,0:18:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赢的人就是正义
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.44,0:18:02.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义之魂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.08,0:18:08.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义之魂...正义之魂...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.52,0:18:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我实在看不出哪个才是被黑色魔轮所控制的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.44,0:18:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.16,0:18:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义之魂...正义之魂...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.16,0:18:17.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义之魂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.04,0:18:21.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？我的子弹用完了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.68,0:18:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我...怎么收拾你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.64,0:18:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.28,0:18:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.24,0:18:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就是你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.76,0:18:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们被处死的时间到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.44,0:18:42.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.96,0:18:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.96,0:18:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,五角星兽 冲着我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.40,0:18:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少罗嗦 流星雨召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.88,0:18:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.36,0:18:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.28,0:19:01.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.04,0:19:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.28,0:19:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 这一次我进化成烈焰兽来对付他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.24,0:19:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.12,0:19:15.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.80,0:19:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.16,0:19:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.04,0:19:44.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.60,0:19:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.48,0:19:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.44,0:19:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.20,0:20:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.96,0:20:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来黑暗之塔在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.20,0:20:21.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,风沙太大 因此大部分埋在沙子里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.56,0:20:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下子 终于把西部小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.76,0:20:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从暴龙改造者手里救出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.00,0:20:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 空
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.12,0:20:33.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们 被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.00,0:20:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 现在事情解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.40,0:20:48.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没大家一起来玩扑克牌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.96,0:20:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,左轮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.88,0:21:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空 我们是不是该回家了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.28,0:21:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.00,0:21:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以回去呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.76,0:21:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没现在来玩扑克牌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.52,0:21:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天哪...天哪...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.16,0:22:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然出现在学校的神秘黑色影子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.44,0:22:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在脑海中一闪而过的儿时回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.20,0:22:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吞没一切的浓雾之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.92,0:22:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个声音不断地呼唤着小光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.24,0:22:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一股不可抗拒的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.84,0:22:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开启神秘的钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.00,0:22:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,带着小光前往未知的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.96,0:22:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.43,0:22:57.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「达高兽的呼唤」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.55,0:23:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}达高兽的呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.16,0:23:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
