[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,SimHei,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,1,1,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.91,0:01:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.41,0:01:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为得到了第二个装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.08,0:01:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽和麻鹰兽分别有了新的装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.25,0:01:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 只剩下阿丈的诚实徽章还没有找到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.33,0:02:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诚实徽章到底在什么地方呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}潜鲨兽 冲出海底
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.91,0:02:34.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.41,0:02:37.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是他为什么没有来攻击我们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.33,0:02:39.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是时间的问题而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.16,0:02:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要这里的空气没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.16,0:02:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们自然...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.08,0:02:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我不好 都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.33,0:02:55.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切要从几个小时前说起...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.58,0:03:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像在这片海底油田的某个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.91,0:03:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.33,0:03:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.08,0:03:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那可不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.41,0:03:19.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许是阿岳或者是小光的也说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.41,0:03:22.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们来赛跑看谁先到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.66,0:03:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会输给你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.41,0:03:25.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛那么急
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.83,0:03:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等我...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.25,0:03:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.00,0:03:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在忙得很
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.58,0:03:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可没有那么多美国时间去管他们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.58,0:03:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.08,0:03:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢怎么做 随你便
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.00,0:03:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.08,0:04:28.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进水了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.25,0:04:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.41,0:04:31.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.83,0:04:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.33,0:04:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着「紧急止水闸」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.41,0:04:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紧急？就是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.25,0:04:37.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快按那个钮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.16,0:04:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:47.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.16,0:04:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.91,0:04:51.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们回不到上面去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.50,0:04:54.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 我们被关在这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.00,0:05:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的错 都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.83,0:05:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.16,0:05:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么这么说？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.58,0:05:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁都没想到会发生这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.91,0:05:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都因为我没有弄清楚这是不是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.33,0:05:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就急着进来 才会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.58,0:05:20.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.08,0:05:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是刚刚好 你跑了第一个而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.08,0:05:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.33,0:05:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看 这是什么东西啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.00,0:05:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着「紧急救生艇」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.50,0:05:37.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 有救了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.58,0:05:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是好像只能做一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.58,0:05:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得伊织最合适了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.83,0:05:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赞成 我也这么觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.50,0:05:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.08,0:05:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.83,0:05:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也赞成吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.16,0:05:53.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成小光的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.16,0:05:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织赶快坐上紧急逃生艇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.25,0:05:58.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为...为什么是我呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.83,0:06:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是因为我年纪小
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.33,0:06:01.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.00,0:06:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？你不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.00,0:06:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的诚心诚意
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.50,0:06:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然就这样被你拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.75,0:06:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不能接受
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.08,0:06:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你最好乖乖的接受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.41,0:06:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要就是不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.08,0:06:14.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按照伊织的个性
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.41,0:06:15.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他会这么说一点也不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.91,0:06:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我来好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.16,0:06:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家有意见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.25,0:06:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了公平 我们抽签决定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.41,0:06:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抽签很公平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.75,0:06:24.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这种事情用抽签...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.58,0:06:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这种办法很好啊 我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.16,0:06:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织也没意见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.75,0:06:34.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们数码兽的签就不用做了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.08,0:06:37.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 既然要做就全部做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.91,0:06:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.91,0:06:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管是人还是数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.33,0:06:42.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抽签之前 一律平等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.41,0:06:44.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,猜拳来决定怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.58,0:06:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得抽签比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.08,0:06:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.83,0:06:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 第一个人是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.33,0:06:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先抽好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.41,0:06:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要做先抽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.25,0:06:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我先？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.58,0:06:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织先抽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.16,0:06:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.83,0:07:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织你好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.33,0:07:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一个就抽中 真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.58,0:07:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然这就是命运的安排
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.50,0:07:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.25,0:07:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 你干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们根本就是在骗我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:16.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们的确是在骗你 可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.83,0:07:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.00,0:07:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这也是没办法的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.50,0:07:22.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 因为你不管说什么都不肯去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.00,0:07:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.25,0:07:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还在想如果我抽中了要怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.50,0:07:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你们一点都没有发现吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.00,0:07:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你们全都知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.58,0:07:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是常识
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说不去就不去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.50,0:07:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 大辅     
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.32,0:07:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.25,0:07:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放开我... 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.83,0:07:44.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 回到现实世界后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.33,0:07:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要把这件事告诉阿丈哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.25,0:07:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在只有阿丈的海狮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.25,0:07:50.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才能救我们离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.83,0:07:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.75,0:07:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.50,0:07:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去 放我出去...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在 超海龙兽已经暂时离开了  
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.07,0:08:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.08,0:08:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你拨打的电话暂时不在服务区
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.25,0:08:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请稍后再拨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.00,0:08:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,城户...城户 品川的补习班
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.25,0:08:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,品川的补习班...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.00,0:08:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你会来的正好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.08,0:08:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正想请你送东西到信实先生家去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.75,0:08:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...现在可能不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.58,0:08:51.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有其他事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.83,0:08:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.83,0:08:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是什么事 可以说说看吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.08,0:08:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我不能说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.25,0:08:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不能说 到底是什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.33,0:09:01.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就别问他了 富美子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.33,0:09:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.58,0:09:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你强迫他的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.50,0:09:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后只会逼得他说谎敷衍你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.25,0:09:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他真的不想说就别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.00,0:09:11.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之比他说谎来得好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.25,0:09:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千万不可以说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.50,0:09:15.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以说谎哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.50,0:09:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.25,0:09:28.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可不可以不要再撞头了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.00,0:09:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道这样很吵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.00,0:09:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你可不可以不要再摇你的脸了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.58,0:09:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看让人很烦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.33,0:09:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是故意要摇的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.75,0:09:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道其实你们都很紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.83,0:09:42.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.00,0:09:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.00,0:09:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.25,0:09:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.75,0:09:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家干脆来玩歌唱接龙解闷吧 怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.58,0:09:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我实在没有那个心情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:57.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么在这种生死存亡的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.25,0:09:58.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还有心情唱歌呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.75,0:10:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我相信伊织可以完成任务
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也相信伊织啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.25,0:10:06.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是谁知道他能不能及时赶到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 再不快点的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.58,0:10:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦氧气没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.58,0:10:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等到空气没有了 我们就会...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.25,0:10:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟 他们现在在考试
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.75,0:10:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我有急事 一定要找城户丈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.25,0:10:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按照规定 考试中是不可以出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.08,0:10:32.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是他家里出事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.58,0:10:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或者是父母有人住院
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.75,0:10:37.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就另当别论了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.50,0:10:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他爸爸住院了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.00,0:10:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千万不可以说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.75,0:10:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以说谎哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.25,0:10:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我该怎么办才好？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.58,0:11:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.08,0:11:37.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.83,0:11:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得一定就藏在这个下面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.00,0:11:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种地方会有装甲数码蛋吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.08,0:11:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话是没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.25,0:11:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是比起这样耗着浪费时间 还不如做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.00,0:11:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 我们一起来帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.00,0:11:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.58,0:12:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.75,0:12:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿丈 真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.25,0:12:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该怎么跟你道歉才好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.58,0:12:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 你别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.08,0:12:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚开始 我也吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然是这件事情的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.50,0:12:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那也是情有可原
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.75,0:12:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的...我真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.50,0:12:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说过没关系的啦 对了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.00,0:12:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.25,0:12:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再不快点的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.00,0:12:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 可是不管怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.25,0:12:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要先通知光子郎才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.25,0:12:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂...光子郎吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.50,0:12:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事实上大辅他们陷入困境了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.00,0:12:34.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此有件事想要拜托你一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.08,0:12:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.75,0:12:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是伊织的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.33,0:12:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.75,0:12:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又有新的装甲进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.83,0:12:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不知道会变成什么样子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.08,0:12:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那还用说啊 一定是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.25,0:13:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.75,0:13:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.58,0:13:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.50,0:13:12.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在笑耶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.50,0:13:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们终于了解你相信伊织的心情了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.58,0:13:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.33,0:13:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 大家都很累了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.50,0:13:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还能勉强的笑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.83,0:13:24.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,表示还有一点理性在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.25,0:13:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,, 可是在肉体和精神上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.00,0:13:28.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都已经倒了极限
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.75,0:13:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.33,0:13:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.00,0:13:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道...是错觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.00,0:13:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.25,0:13:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽来救我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.00,0:13:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.33,0:13:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.75,0:13:54.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是 超海龙兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.25,0:13:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.08,0:13:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟踪型鱼雷一般猛追敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.33,0:14:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不达目的决不罢休的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.00,0:14:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.00,0:14:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「轰雷枪」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.25,0:14:05.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前虽然在东京打败过他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.33,0:14:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是不变成祖顿兽打得过他吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.58,0:14:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.58,0:14:16.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鱼叉机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.75,0:14:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.25,0:14:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.25,0:14:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鱼叉机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.00,0:14:32.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.58,0:14:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.58,0:14:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来救你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.25,0:14:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家赶快到巨鲸兽的嘴巴里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.25,0:14:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.25,0:14:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看吧 我说的一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.50,0:14:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好神奇哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.58,0:14:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...果然厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.75,0:15:00.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 巨鲸兽怎么会来呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.25,0:15:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我拜托光子郎的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.25,0:15:04.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请甲虫兽去向巨鲸兽求救的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.00,0:15:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们还在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.08,0:15:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点进来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.83,0:15:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.25,0:15:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.08,0:15:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有你的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.83,0:15:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有我的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.00,0:15:16.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...那不是诚实徽章吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.58,0:15:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诚实？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.58,0:15:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和伊织的个性很像
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.00,0:15:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不觉得这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.75,0:15:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得跟伊织的个性非常相称
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.33,0:15:25.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.75,0:15:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.83,0:15:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家会陷入危险都是因为这个装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.33,0:15:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种装甲数码蛋我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.25,0:15:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管这个了 还是先逃命要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃命前先拿走这个装甲数码蛋再说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.08,0:15:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说我不要了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.33,0:15:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.58,0:15:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道要让这个诚实的数码装甲蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.00,0:15:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永远石沉大海 不见天日吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.00,0:15:53.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点 我们一起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.33,0:16:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 你去拿拿看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.33,0:16:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点拿拿看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.58,0:16:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能的啦 我一定拿不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.75,0:16:16.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情不试试看怎么知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.75,0:16:18.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 都是我的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.83,0:16:19.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才会害得大家差点死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.83,0:16:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.00,0:16:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.00,0:16:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照你这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.00,0:16:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们关上止水闸也有错了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.33,0:16:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实谁都没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.50,0:16:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我还说了谎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.75,0:16:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出门前爷爷还交代我千万不能说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.75,0:16:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我根本没有资格
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.75,0:16:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有这个代表诚实的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.50,0:16:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说谎有两种
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.33,0:16:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一种是存心欺骗别人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.50,0:16:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另一种是没有恶意的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.50,0:16:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前一种是会伤害到别人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.00,0:16:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是后面一种是可以帮助别人的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.25,0:16:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对...对 这就是所谓的善意的谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.00,0:16:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.25,0:16:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.00,0:16:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然这样好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.25,0:16:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去之后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.08,0:16:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来向你爷爷解释这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.50,0:17:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少我并没有因为你说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.75,0:17:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而受到任何伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.08,0:17:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相反 如果你没有说谎的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.58,0:17:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事情不知道会变成什么样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.00,0:17:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿丈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.75,0:17:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样你能明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.75,0:17:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点过去拿拿看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 果然是伊织的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.50,0:17:19.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 装甲进化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.00,0:17:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.75,0:17:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永不止息的诚实 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.50,0:17:53.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是诚实的装甲数码蛋 好帅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.58,0:17:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是水里的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.25,0:18:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜鲨兽 借着诚实的装甲数码蛋力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.00,0:18:01.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化而成的水栖型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.50,0:18:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「潜行攻击」和「高压氧气」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.83,0:18:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快点 我们立刻离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.25,0:18:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点进来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.58,0:18:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 潜鲨兽 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.08,0:18:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出动
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.08,0:18:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,追魔机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.50,0:18:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们来帮助你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.58,0:18:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 这下可以双重攻击了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.33,0:18:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我当诱饵引开他 你负责攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.00,0:18:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.58,0:19:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高压氧气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.50,0:19:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.33,0:19:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙变的比刚才老实多了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.75,0:19:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他好像变的老实多了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.58,0:19:39.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.75,0:19:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色魔戒被我们破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.08,0:19:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是伊织 还有潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.50,0:19:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.25,0:19:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,共同的功劳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.00,0:19:49.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙似乎脱离险境了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.08,0:19:51.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样没关系吗？ 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.58,0:19:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.50,0:20:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你前阵子说的计划就是这个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.25,0:20:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整件事情跟你没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.25,0:20:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快回大家那里去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.75,0:20:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不急 不急
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.08,0:20:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.00,0:20:46.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真的好大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.50,0:20:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 好静好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.33,0:20:59.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是一句 但是潜鲨兽的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.58,0:21:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在伊织的心理不知引起了多大的回响
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.08,0:22:39.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光的记事本上写了红色的日期
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.08,0:22:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道 小光和阿岳要约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.83,0:22:44.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅的心里好像受到了强烈的打击
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.74,0:22:46.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不敢相信也不愿相信
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.08,0:22:50.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,御台场的电视台发生了灵异事件
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.74,0:22:53.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道又是数码兽发生战斗了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.83,0:22:55.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.24,0:22:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「御台场纪念日」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.82,0:23:00.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}御台场纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.83,0:23:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
