[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.24,0:02:00.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,330)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}达高兽的呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.00,0:02:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.16,0:02:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,独自一个人在数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道又要使用什么计谋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.66,0:02:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.50,0:02:11.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然回到正常的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.08,0:02:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却经常想到数码世界的种种 以及自己的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.25,0:02:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.58,0:02:25.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 你们早
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.66,0:02:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再不赶快走 上学要迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.58,0:02:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光看起来好像很有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.50,0:02:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们好像一点都没有变
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.66,0:02:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是孩子们都一天天的长大了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.75,0:02:48.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.40,0:02:49.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.41,0:02:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得最近
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.91,0:02:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光好像有心事的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.25,0:02:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.33,0:02:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.25,0:03:01.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许是我的错觉吧 走了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.91,0:03:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.91,0:03:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.00,0:04:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.00,0:04:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.41,0:04:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.58,0:04:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要到保健室去休息下？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.41,0:04:35.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久没有这样了 怎么会呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.66,0:04:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.66,0:05:29.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.58,0:05:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问 八神同学...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.25,0:05:34.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有人来这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.91,0:05:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到...到底跑到哪里去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.66,0:05:49.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.91,0:05:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她不可能忽然不见哪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.50,0:06:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才...到海边去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.66,0:06:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海边？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.33,0:06:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...说不定就快要离开这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.91,0:06:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直觉得有人在呼唤我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.41,0:06:48.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有人在呼唤你 谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.83,0:06:51.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.08,0:06:53.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.25,0:06:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果他再次呼唤我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.83,0:06:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会到他那里去的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.25,0:07:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.00,0:07:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是谁要叫你走啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.25,0:07:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥每次都说他一定会保护我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.50,0:07:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是现在...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是太一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.75,0:07:13.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一 太一 你什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.00,0:07:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才能用不着你哥哥的保护啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.50,0:07:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 你这样是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.50,0:07:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海边...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.82,0:08:01.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.75,0:08:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光她...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.00,0:08:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要扩充DT暴龙机的程序和机能
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.33,0:08:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你要怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.58,0:08:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我希望和数码世界之间除了通信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.25,0:08:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还可以进行即时通话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.25,0:08:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者的DT暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.25,0:08:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定有这种功能
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.50,0:08:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到时候只要知道他在哪就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.08,0:08:47.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.33,0:08:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来我跟我们的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.00,0:08:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就不会被迫黑暗进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.25,0:08:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.75,0:08:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无精打采的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.25,0:08:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事 我很好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.50,0:09:02.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光她...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.83,0:09:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说她消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.00,0:09:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会有这种事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.83,0:09:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平常我们去数码世界 只能从这里出发啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.58,0:09:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许小光...她不用经过这里也说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.83,0:09:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.25,0:09:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.00,0:09:57.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在的这个系统
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.50,0:09:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法知道小光在什么地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们现在立刻要到数码世界去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.25,0:10:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点打开大门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.50,0:10:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.50,0:10:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去把小光找回来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快一点呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.50,0:10:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你们听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.75,0:10:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们根本就不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.25,0:10:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们根本就不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.75,0:10:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光现在去了什么地方 不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.50,0:10:19.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果就这样到数码世界去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.75,0:10:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么大的地方 可能会迷路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.83,0:10:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她不是去数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.08,0:10:28.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海边 对 是海边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.75,0:10:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.25,0:10:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...什么地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.33,0:10:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是数码世界吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.33,0:10:54.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 原来你在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.50,0:10:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我们看来 小光已经变成数据资料了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.25,0:11:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光果然是到数码世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.50,0:11:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.50,0:11:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她去的地方 绝对不是我没去过的数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.33,0:11:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为那一次只有我看见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.33,0:11:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光她...小光在课堂上差一点消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.75,0:11:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 她到底跑到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.25,0:11:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.83,0:11:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.00,0:11:23.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我一定要把小光找回来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.25,0:11:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算现在有这个东西又有什么用呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.08,0:11:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不应该对小光说那么重的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.83,0:11:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.25,0:11:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我应该负起保护小光的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.50,0:12:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光不是那么脆弱的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.58,0:12:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光很坚强的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.00,0:12:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为有互相合作的伙伴的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...可是现在我们什么也不能做 不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.08,0:12:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.83,0:12:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么可怕的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.08,0:12:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我可以不要做的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.58,0:12:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我偏偏...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.58,0:12:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁？是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.00,0:12:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁在那里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.25,0:12:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.00,0:12:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管阿岳那家伙到底说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.00,0:12:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信小光一定在数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.00,0:12:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样 我要把小光找回来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.08,0:12:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.75,0:12:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.75,0:13:01.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么打不开呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.08,0:13:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.08,0:13:05.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.58,0:13:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是...数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.58,0:13:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.50,0:13:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇蛙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.50,0:13:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水栖兽人型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.25,0:13:22.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.50,0:13:24.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.08,0:13:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我们是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.00,0:13:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道为什么我们会在这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.58,0:13:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.00,0:13:35.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.00,0:13:39.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奉深海底下的神明指示来到这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.75,0:13:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神明...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.25,0:13:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...可是你们怎么会这样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.33,0:13:53.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一天 这个东西突然夺走了我们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.00,0:13:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一个声音强迫我们去拜不是我们的神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.00,0:14:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.00,0:14:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你果然知道是什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.08,0:14:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以很清楚的看得到你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.83,0:14:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管你在什么地方都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.33,0:14:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有你 只有你这个被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.33,0:14:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以帮我们把身上这个东西拿掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.75,0:14:24.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们才会不停地叫我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.33,0:14:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 我有这个能力吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.25,0:14:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还没有试 我就说不行呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.50,0:14:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.58,0:14:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.25,0:14:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们快点离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.75,0:14:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.75,0:15:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.08,0:15:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那时空我们的新的神
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.75,0:15:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是新大王派来的使者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.08,0:15:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.00,0:15:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.25,0:15:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以这么残忍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.83,0:15:31.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.25,0:15:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这里叫也没有用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.75,0:15:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.25,0:15:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.83,0:15:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.08,0:15:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥救我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.75,0:15:51.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.75,0:15:54.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.75,0:15:58.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光...小光...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.25,0:16:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.50,0:16:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.25,0:16:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要希望就可以连接世界
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.00,0:16:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里不是平常的数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.58,0:16:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.25,0:16:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们终于来这里救我了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.50,0:16:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.25,0:16:34.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 准备
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.33,0:16:37.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.25,0:16:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.58,0:16:55.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.25,0:17:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的家伙 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.33,0:17:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣针雨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.75,0:17:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 我也要装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.00,0:17:22.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是装甲暴龙机 在书包里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:24.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.58,0:17:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我绝对不会输给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.58,0:17:40.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.58,0:17:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽 快点去破坏那座塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.08,0:17:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那座灯塔夺走了我们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.58,0:17:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.50,0:17:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽 准备
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.25,0:17:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.50,0:17:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.50,0:18:17.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.50,0:18:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天女兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.08,0:18:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天女兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.75,0:18:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.25,0:18:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂紫光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.83,0:18:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.83,0:18:58.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞龙兽被我们打败了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.75,0:19:25.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个才是你们的真面目吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.50,0:19:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.00,0:19:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放开小光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.83,0:19:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们之所以会叫你来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.58,0:19:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为希望你可以当我们的新娘子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.25,0:19:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了抵抗那个新的神
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.83,0:19:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脱离他的控制
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.08,0:19:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此我们必须要繁衍更多的后代
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.00,0:19:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我救了你们 你们却...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.00,0:19:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选中的少女
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.50,0:19:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来以为
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.00,0:20:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你会很乐意成为我们的新娘子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.25,0:20:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你不愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.00,0:20:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只好回到深海里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.25,0:20:08.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去找我们原来的神
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.50,0:20:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那里等候时机成熟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.33,0:20:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.50,0:20:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.75,0:20:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是来接你回家的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.58,0:20:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许孩子们说看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.50,0:20:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并不是他们向来熟悉的数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.50,0:20:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是另外一个未知的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.08,0:22:39.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅一行人在蛋蛋兽的餐厅遇到了困难
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.33,0:22:43.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幸好遇到美美和美国被选召的孩子麦克
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.83,0:22:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在一场激战之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.24,0:22:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京继承了美美的纯真之心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.49,0:22:50.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿到了纯真的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.33,0:22:53.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽有了另一种装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.58,0:22:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.07,0:22:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「疾风 忍者兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.07,0:22:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,310)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}疾风 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.58,0:22:59.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
