[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.24,0:01:34.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悬浮在空中的巨大基地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.64,0:01:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来就是暴龙改造者的司令总部
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.24,0:01:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,司令总部里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.20,0:01:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在秘密进行着暴龙改造者的终极计划
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.24,0:01:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们能不能阻止这项计划呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.58,0:02:09.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}合成魔兽 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.84,0:02:13.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在暴龙改造者的基地离开之后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.96,0:02:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅等人又和小光她们会合了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.88,0:02:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等到第二天早上...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.00,0:02:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅一定会生气的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.96,0:02:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.56,0:02:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么刚刚不找大辅他们一起侦查呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.80,0:02:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总不能留下小光她们两个女孩子在那里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.80,0:02:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经知道暴龙改造者的基地去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.08,0:02:45.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,往哪里去啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.00,0:02:51.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然丢下我不让我去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.56,0:02:54.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要沮丧 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.16,0:02:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的部分打算怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.52,0:03:02.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别着急 马上就可以拿到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.72,0:03:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.72,0:03:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是昨天知道他们是去山中湖的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.36,0:03:18.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我早就追过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.56,0:03:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等我一下...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.28,0:03:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧 连小光她们都...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么影子也没有看到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.56,0:03:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道伊织他们有什么发现
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.76,0:03:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.08,0:03:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们说从天空看 什么也没有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.68,0:03:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海底也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.88,0:03:43.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么回报
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.12,0:04:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.04,0:04:02.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要赶快通知阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.68,0:04:07.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发现基地了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.44,0:04:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在必须要从山洞潜入才行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.08,0:04:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要告诉他们千万不要勉强
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.36,0:04:18.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.00,0:04:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是漩涡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.64,0:04:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看样子好像快要出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.88,0:04:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么东西 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.96,0:04:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个大漩涡是通往黑暗能量的入口
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.04,0:04:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以这么说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.92,0:04:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信那里肯定有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.56,0:04:44.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗系数码兽的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.60,0:04:45.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要回收那些资料
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.96,0:04:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来完成我所发明的合成数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.36,0:04:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.24,0:04:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.84,0:04:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.80,0:05:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是却无法用言语来描述
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.40,0:05:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个漩涡地下到底是什么东西 好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好怕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.80,0:05:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个没用的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.76,0:05:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不可以去 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.64,0:05:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我警告你休想指使我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.68,0:05:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨大的漩涡？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.48,0:05:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.84,0:05:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要赶快通知潜入基地的穿山兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.16,0:05:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.72,0:05:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.68,0:05:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是从刚才就一直无法联系上他们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.96,0:05:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是再不快点的话就遭了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.20,0:05:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 后果不堪设想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.56,0:05:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个为什么从刚才开始
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.32,0:05:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就一直很激动的样子呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.20,0:05:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然会激动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.00,0:05:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为看到了那个漩涡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.92,0:05:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 难道完全没有感觉到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.52,0:06:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到了 那是什么东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.40,0:06:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里大概就是动力室了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.80,0:06:23.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要轰掉他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.52,0:06:25.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我们再调查清楚一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.68,0:06:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 对了 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.60,0:06:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得里面很冷吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.60,0:06:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.92,0:06:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.52,0:06:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一进来就觉得好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.84,0:06:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你了 千万不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.40,0:06:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有这一次 请你一定要听我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.92,0:06:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,否则你一定会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.84,0:06:51.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.04,0:06:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始移动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.44,0:07:00.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.96,0:07:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他往漩涡的方向去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.36,0:07:03.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.96,0:07:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.04,0:07:07.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.12,0:07:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是被暴龙改造者抓起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.92,0:07:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.52,0:07:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先别管动力室了 救人要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.72,0:07:22.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你装甲进化破坏栅栏放他们出来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.52,0:07:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.00,0:07:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 数码之心...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.04,0:07:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.08,0:07:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备进入漩涡中心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.80,0:07:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么都没有人要停下来载我呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.68,0:07:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去露营啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.32,0:07:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼 年轻真好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.48,0:07:56.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玛丽 我们以前也曾经年轻过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.64,0:08:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你在想什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.44,0:08:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在想砍下这棵树
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.64,0:08:10.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做一艘独木舟行不行得通
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.60,0:08:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个主意很不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.20,0:08:13.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决定了 就这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.64,0:08:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.72,0:08:22.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道啊 总之...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.68,0:08:24.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以乘着这座小岛去追大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.52,0:08:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大的的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.60,0:08:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样先找到伊织他们进去的洞口
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.84,0:08:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们也从同样的洞口进去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.52,0:08:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些是什么？游魂吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.52,0:08:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.88,0:09:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正令人毛骨悚然的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.36,0:09:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是下面开口的那一片漆黑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.52,0:09:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.92,0:09:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心一点 不然会被吞进去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.92,0:09:29.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.36,0:09:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事 回收开始
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.64,0:09:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.76,0:09:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.32,0:09:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.12,0:10:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.00,0:10:05.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然 没有办法回收
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.68,0:10:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们放弃吧 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.60,0:10:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.00,0:10:14.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样 我亲自去回收
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.60,0:10:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.20,0:10:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.32,0:10:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正要放走被抓走的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.32,0:10:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我也来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.64,0:10:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翼闪电
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.96,0:10:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者到底在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.44,0:11:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 不要太勉强
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.64,0:11:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少来烦我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.76,0:11:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.48,0:11:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来 我的原创数码兽就完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.36,0:11:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗地区
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.80,0:11:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你想来就来想走就走的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.28,0:11:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要小看黑暗的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.76,0:11:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,否则的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.64,0:11:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻听？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.20,0:11:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻听的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.28,0:11:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,内容也太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.32,0:11:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身为数码世界之王的我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.52,0:11:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事情办不到？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.80,0:11:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳终于想起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.44,0:12:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前 天使兽不惜牺牲自己的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.20,0:12:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把恶魔兽永远封印在黑暗地区之中的往事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.92,0:12:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候 我一直祈求
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.36,0:12:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是时间可以倒转就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.64,0:12:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是时间永远没有办法回头的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.44,0:12:27.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管你愿不愿意 日子总会继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.24,0:12:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在极度绝望的深渊之中诅咒命运
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.08,0:12:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.56,0:12:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.72,0:12:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太可恶了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.84,0:12:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.12,0:13:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快住手 我再也不想再次看到悲剧发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.68,0:13:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要做个了断
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.56,0:13:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.72,0:13:06.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.96,0:13:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟出什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.64,0:13:12.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.80,0:13:14.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给巴达兽去处理就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.76,0:13:16.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们来放走这些数码兽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.68,0:13:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙又偷跑过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.28,0:13:30.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.36,0:13:34.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了 反正现在也没时间理他们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 刚刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.56,0:13:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下我的原创数码兽完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.12,0:14:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家好像跑得很远的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.52,0:14:06.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点的话会追不上的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.16,0:14:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这座岛...可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.36,0:14:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅会不会生气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.76,0:14:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那也没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.08,0:14:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.64,0:14:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,往我们这边过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.44,0:14:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家小心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.92,0:14:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚好可以试下我的合成数码兽的威力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.96,0:14:30.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟有多大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.48,0:14:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.36,0:14:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.32,0:14:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.00,0:14:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.88,0:15:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者合成各种数码兽的优点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.88,0:15:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所组合而成的合成型完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.96,0:15:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏力非常强大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.20,0:15:08.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「死亡热线」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.36,0:15:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有见过或听过这种数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.16,0:15:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 趁尼菲迪兽 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.40,0:15:18.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和那个家伙对战的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.92,0:15:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们快放被抓的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.08,0:15:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.60,0:15:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.56,0:15:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比多兽的头部是特殊金属做成的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.88,0:15:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有用
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.68,0:15:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.68,0:15:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽 飞龙兽的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.12,0:15:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让他的动作更加敏捷了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.56,0:15:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在轮到我们攻击了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.56,0:15:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加鲁鲁兽的腿再加上角龙兽的尾巴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.16,0:15:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古加兽 丧尸暴龙兽还有恶魔兽的手臂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.12,0:15:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体是暴龙兽的 以及机械暴龙兽的头发
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.44,0:16:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.40,0:16:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我发明的数码兽很厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.36,0:16:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.20,0:16:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我想的一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.32,0:16:21.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种数码兽才够资格当大王我的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.56,0:16:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而不是像你这种懦弱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.40,0:16:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是最后的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.96,0:16:39.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也赶快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.40,0:16:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是阿岳他...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.72,0:16:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们自己会想办法的 赶快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.44,0:16:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 要决斗等以后再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.64,0:16:53.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在还有别的事情要做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.04,0:17:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看不出你挺厉害的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.56,0:17:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然潜入控制黑暗力量的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.00,0:17:08.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大王的基地里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.35,0:17:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.00,0:17:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.83,0:17:22.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种征服世界的游戏还要玩多久？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.92,0:17:23.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好玩吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.44,0:17:27.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你口口声声说什么黑暗力量的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.11,0:17:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实你并不了解
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.00,0:17:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道 对不对？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.56,0:17:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受了伤 那可划不来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.44,0:17:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点长大吧 不要再这么孩子气了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.32,0:17:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没用的东西...没用的东西...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.72,0:17:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是只会说这一句话呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.32,0:17:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你...闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.48,0:17:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴说不过人家就只好用暴力吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.36,0:18:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.56,0:18:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗？算了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.32,0:18:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟你争这个也没什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.08,0:18:08.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说完了 是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.60,0:18:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那请你小心了 现在轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.32,0:18:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.48,0:18:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.16,0:18:36.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.44,0:18:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴风之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.64,0:18:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,罗塞塔之石
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.72,0:18:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.88,0:18:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黏黏网
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.12,0:18:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,空气炮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.12,0:18:59.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想打架啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.12,0:19:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不许你们动小贤一根寒毛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.56,0:19:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.36,0:19:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是我创造的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.96,0:19:17.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽 很厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.88,0:19:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你们的全部力量加起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.68,0:19:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也打不过他的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.28,0:19:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.92,0:19:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.96,0:19:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.20,0:19:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.32,0:20:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 下次再找你一决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.88,0:20:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.00,0:20:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是没用的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.28,0:20:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.28,0:20:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.88,0:20:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 天马兽 谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.24,0:20:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽好像突然停下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.32,0:20:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们趁现在赶快全部撤退吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.76,0:20:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.44,0:20:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.40,0:20:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然有这种事 真可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.20,0:20:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是我可以飞就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.04,0:20:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别说了 虽然你不能飞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.08,0:20:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们有我们自己的战斗方式
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.68,0:20:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 休息一下再继续追暴龙改造者吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.88,0:20:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.28,0:20:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.80,0:20:59.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是滨名湖了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.92,0:21:03.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明明说我要去山中湖的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.36,0:21:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.36,0:22:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用亚古兽他们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.72,0:22:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起潜入暴龙改造者的基地
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.88,0:22:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是在战斗中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.52,0:22:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽们一只只的败下阵来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.68,0:22:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直觉得世界很诡异的虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有决不放弃的大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.64,0:22:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在几乎要绝望的情形之下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.00,0:22:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.76,0:22:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.64,0:22:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「超绝进化 金甲龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.03,0:23:04.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}超绝进化 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.36,0:22:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了

