[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.58,0:01:34.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光从现实世界中突然消失
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.66,0:01:38.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 巴达兽 迪路兽前往救援
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.41,0:01:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是他们却发现
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.91,0:01:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是孩子们从未去过的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.66,0:01:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是个什么样的地方呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.91,0:01:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住在那里的人又是什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.58,0:01:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一切还只是个谜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.74,0:02:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}疾风 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.25,0:02:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 see you tomorrow
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.90,0:02:21.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,see you
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.23,0:02:26.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.50,0:02:31.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照道理说 不用D3暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.66,0:02:33.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不可能进入数码世界的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.58,0:02:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是为什么小光却可以
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.66,0:02:39.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算小京能够扩充DT暴龙机的功能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.91,0:02:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不可能有那么大的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.91,0:02:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许小光真有什么特别的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.99,0:02:47.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有信
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.25,0:02:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这附近好像没有装甲数码蛋的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.50,0:02:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.75,0:02:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说 你们今天要回来了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.08,0:03:00.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们还要再找一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.50,0:03:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.50,0:03:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正那一带也没黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.08,0:03:05.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再找一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.41,0:03:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美国那边的大门还开着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.25,0:03:12.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道美美有没有发觉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.00,0:03:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时间美国才刚天亮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.00,0:03:18.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？不管了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.83,0:03:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好饿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.50,0:03:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有巧克力吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.16,0:03:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的肚子也好饿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.25,0:03:29.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是早上多带点点心就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.66,0:03:31.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连啾啾营养包都没了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.00,0:03:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子这么饿根本就没法战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.75,0:03:38.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然我们还是先回去下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.16,0:03:39.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.33,0:03:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也只好这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.75,0:03:42.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.33,0:03:45.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里的湖边有一家不错的餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.91,0:03:46.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.83,0:03:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.33,0:03:49.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃饱了 又可以战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.08,0:03:54.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.41,0:03:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的没想到数码世界 竟然可以吃到这么好吃的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.58,0:04:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.08,0:04:03.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我就注意到一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.75,0:04:06.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里 我们以前好像来过的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.41,0:04:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.16,0:04:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得来过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.16,0:04:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我们要买单
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.25,0:04:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.91,0:04:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问多少钱啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.41,0:04:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一共是美元87块
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.83,0:04:24.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总共是87美元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.66,0:04:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问 换算成日币是多少钱啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.83,0:04:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 多少日币
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.75,0:04:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我们只收美元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.00,0:04:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 有什么问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.75,0:04:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他说要87美元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.50,0:04:37.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美元？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.41,0:04:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们根本就没有美元啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.58,0:04:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有美元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.08,0:04:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们想要白吃白喝吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.58,0:04:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我们有带钱啊 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.58,0:04:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只收美元
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.00,0:04:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他的都是废纸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.66,0:04:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真过分 有什么关系嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.75,0:04:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美元和日币一样都是钱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.75,0:04:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里会一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.00,0:04:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不付美元就是白吃白喝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.83,0:04:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,气死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.75,0:05:00.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欠的钱就让你们在店里打工偿还好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.58,0:05:02.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这句话我好像在哪里听过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.08,0:05:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我们工作是无所谓啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.33,0:05:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们留下来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.25,0:05:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就不能回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.91,0:05:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你回不了家是你的事 与我无关
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.25,0:05:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正付不了钱就要打工来抵...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.00,0:05:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来付钱好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.00,0:05:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.41,0:05:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问...你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.33,0:05:21.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Hello 你们大家都好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.66,0:05:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:25.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐 好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.33,0:05:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 你怎么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.08,0:05:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在美国
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.66,0:05:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发现通往这里的大门时开着的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.33,0:05:31.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,睡的正甜的时候被光子郎叫醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.66,0:05:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是就来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.66,0:05:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过既然来就带麦克一起来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:39.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这位是我的朋友 他叫比特兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是比特兽 请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.33,0:05:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比特兽 性格温和敦厚的两栖类数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.33,0:05:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦被激怒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.50,0:05:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便会发出100万伏特的电流炸毁敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.66,0:05:50.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.50,0:05:51.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里没有关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.08,0:05:53.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你保护的区域怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.33,0:05:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经跟光子郎联系过了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.91,0:05:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请甲虫兽代班才来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.41,0:05:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.66,0:06:01.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么麦克也可以到数码世界来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.91,0:06:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他跟我们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.83,0:06:06.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是被选召的孩子之一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.41,0:06:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.41,0:06:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的神圣计划和太一他们的一样耶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.33,0:06:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去年
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.16,0:06:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 听说2001年的时候很轰动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.41,0:06:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麦克从那个时候开始就很羡慕我们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.16,0:06:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他还很不好意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.75,0:06:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来美国也有跟我们一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.58,0:06:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.33,0:06:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.16,0:06:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他国家也可能有啰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.16,0:06:28.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麦克好帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.83,0:06:33.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是1999年在纽约看见数码兽的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.91,0:06:35.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时看到的是成熟期的金刚兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.58,0:06:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是吸血魔兽侵略东京时所发生的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.41,0:06:42.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 现在想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.66,0:06:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我成为被选召的孩子的一个契机
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.00,0:06:46.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,契机？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.33,0:06:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说道契机 1999年的那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.00,0:06:53.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正好坐在飞机上...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.25,0:06:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我被吸血魔兽抓到东京国际展示场了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.58,0:07:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,1999年夏天的事件 跟我没有直接的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.25,0:07:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过2000年春天 超恶魔兽战斗的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.75,0:07:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正在传电子信
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.08,0:07:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来大家多多少少都有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.50,0:07:12.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,缘分太奇妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...你们沉醉在回忆里的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.25,0:07:16.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰你们很不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.50,0:07:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我现在就付你钱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.25,0:07:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 蛋蛋兽就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.50,0:07:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时哥哥和阿丈被迫在这里打工还钱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.25,0:07:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为当时蛋蛋兽是吸血魔兽的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.75,0:07:30.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才害他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.33,0:07:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以他是邪恶数码兽的手下啰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.33,0:07:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我以前的确曾经很坏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.75,0:07:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是自从黑暗四天王被打败后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.50,0:07:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就认真过着脚踏实地的生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.25,0:07:45.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 原来你已经改邪归正了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.75,0:07:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能永远保持现在这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.00,0:07:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们这么夸奖我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.75,0:07:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实在给我很大的鼓励
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.50,0:07:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗四天王是什么东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.25,0:07:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.75,0:07:57.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是当时跟我们作对的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.83,0:08:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没有听阿岳或小光提起过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有耶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.50,0:08:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没有时间讲到那里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.83,0:08:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我实在不愿回想那个时候的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.08,0:08:08.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你已经改邪归正了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.75,0:08:11.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过刚才你硬要说我们白吃白喝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.25,0:08:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我实在不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.75,0:08:14.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你那个样子好像守财奴哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.08,0:08:17.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且外表很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.83,0:08:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看不清你的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.00,0:08:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.25,0:08:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 并不是所有人都可以了解我的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.83,0:08:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没...没有那回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.75,0:08:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都知道你是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.50,0:08:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不对 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.00,0:08:30.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.75,0:08:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛 就算没有人了解你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.50,0:08:34.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要自己实实在在的做人也就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.58,0:08:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算没人了解我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.25,0:08:39.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要自己实实在在的做人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.00,0:08:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 你说的一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.25,0:08:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.50,0:08:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 谢谢你们的鼓励
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.00,0:08:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.00,0:08:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你总是无条件相信别人的个性
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.00,0:08:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很能给人勇气 我要学习
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.25,0:08:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就慢慢学吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.58,0:08:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们的感情真好 对不对？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.50,0:08:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连麦克都只注意到美美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.75,0:09:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不好玩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.50,0:09:03.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.08,0:09:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是从湖那边传来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.75,0:09:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.25,0:09:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是金刚兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.33,0:09:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金刚兽 绝招是「超力攻击」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.75,0:09:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.00,0:09:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是黑色魔戒不是用在完全体身上的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.50,0:09:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道是不是有很多成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.58,0:09:31.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是被黑色魔戒所控制
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.50,0:09:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.75,0:09:56.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.33,0:10:06.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽他居然保护我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.58,0:10:08.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金刚兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.33,0:10:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.00,0:10:12.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里交给我们就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.08,0:10:14.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比特兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.24,0:10:15.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.25,0:10:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比特兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.25,0:10:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.75,0:10:35.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.83,0:10:37.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有着像蛇一样长的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.58,0:10:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住在水中的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.33,0:10:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「海龙冰箭」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.08,0:10:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水里面可就是我们的地盘了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.00,0:11:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.25,0:11:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.50,0:11:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快去帮助海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.08,0:11:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.50,0:11:22.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.00,0:11:25.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仙人掌兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:33.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尖尖碰碰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.08,0:11:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 仙人掌兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.33,0:11:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.50,0:11:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才还你被打真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.00,0:11:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也是不得已的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.50,0:11:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回到你原来的地方不要再来这了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.75,0:11:55.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脱离控制之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.25,0:11:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实他不是坏的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.58,0:11:58.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.33,0:12:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来就没有邪恶的数码兽呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.75,0:12:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是因为黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.25,0:12:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麦克 这就是我以前跟你提到过的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.33,0:12:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者造的孽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:13.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者跟我们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.33,0:12:15.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是个孩子却妄想主宰数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.75,0:12:16.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是大错特错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.83,0:12:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.25,0:12:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麦克真的好帅哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.83,0:12:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才有说话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.08,0:12:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.58,0:12:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.33,0:12:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对耶 刚才他替我们挨打了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.00,0:12:30.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在一定受了伤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.58,0:12:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道在什么地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.75,0:12:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们到上面去找找看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.50,0:12:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也到附近找找看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.99,0:12:42.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.33,0:12:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽 你还好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.75,0:12:53.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还好 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.75,0:12:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他刚才救了大家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.33,0:12:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要跟他道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.08,0:12:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才挨了一记飞了好远
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.75,0:13:01.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易 才走回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.00,0:13:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真是谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.25,0:13:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你救了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.75,0:13:06.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.25,0:13:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得他跟刚才不太一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.58,0:13:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次换你们尝尝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.25,0:13:16.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞的很远是什么滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.00,0:13:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.75,0:13:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽 完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.50,0:13:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外形是一颗蛋 其实是外露的骨骼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.25,0:13:25.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此所有的攻击对他都不起作用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.25,0:13:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「迷之心」和「噩梦症候群」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.25,0:13:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.75,0:13:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.58,0:13:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.83,0:13:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.58,0:13:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.58,0:13:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.83,0:13:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.50,0:13:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.08,0:14:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.83,0:14:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.08,0:14:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.00,0:14:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.25,0:14:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.25,0:14:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.00,0:14:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.75,0:14:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这招怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.75,0:14:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全没事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.58,0:14:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样 我们双管齐下如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.50,0:14:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.08,0:14:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.00,0:14:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你们暂时停止攻击蛋蛋兽好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.75,0:14:54.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.75,0:14:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽 赶快找回你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.00,0:14:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你现在会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.00,0:15:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是有人在操纵你的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.25,0:15:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.83,0:15:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能有谁可以操纵我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.50,0:15:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的真面目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.75,0:15:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.33,0:15:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不是？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.00,0:15:11.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 你跟他说这么多干嘛？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.25,0:15:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要好好跟他说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.25,0:15:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽一定会醒过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.25,0:15:16.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.25,0:15:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是呀 不可能的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.50,0:15:18.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你们安静一点好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.75,0:15:20.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.83,0:15:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了一个不是伙伴的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.83,0:15:24.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本是不可能的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.33,0:15:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你不是也说了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.33,0:15:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算都没有人了解你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.25,0:15:31.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要自己实实在在做人就够了 是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.50,0:15:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.00,0:15:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们这么轻易就相信了 太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.08,0:15:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了松懈你们的戒心才说的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.33,0:15:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.25,0:15:41.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.33,0:15:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算全世界得人都不相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.00,0:15:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我还是相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.00,0:15:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 你为什么要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.25,0:15:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.33,0:15:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再说这么自欺欺人的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.25,0:15:55.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我就是要说 一定要说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.25,0:15:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你不想听我也要说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.00,0:16:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有完没完啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.74,0:16:02.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.57,0:16:02.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.24,0:16:03.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.00,0:16:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.50,0:16:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你一定要找回真正的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.83,0:16:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.50,0:16:16.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的自己...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.58,0:16:23.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了...烦死了...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.33,0:16:25.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的烦死了...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.08,0:16:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.08,0:16:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的脑袋里到底在想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.50,0:16:30.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你居然会攻击美美
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.25,0:16:32.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美跟我不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.83,0:16:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她从一开始就相信你已经改邪归正了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.58,0:16:37.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我干脆把话说清楚好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.00,0:16:39.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我第一眼看到你的时候就很讨厌你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.75,0:16:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到你就烦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.75,0:16:42.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我根本就不晓得你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.08,0:16:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才金刚兽来攻击我们的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.00,0:16:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你替我们挨了一拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.75,0:16:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有那么一下子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.50,0:16:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的觉得你是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.83,0:16:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 现在怎么样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.08,0:16:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你居然背叛了我们对你的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.25,0:16:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.33,0:16:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你一直都在怀疑我 是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.83,0:16:58.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我当然怀疑过你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.58,0:17:00.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我常常都是以外表来判断一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.25,0:17:02.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.58,0:17:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为好看的人一定都是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.00,0:17:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我就是喜欢长的好看的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.75,0:17:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就是喜欢像麦克这样长的很帅的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.25,0:17:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这有什么办法呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.25,0:17:15.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管别人要这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.50,0:17:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是真正的我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.33,0:17:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.83,0:17:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.50,0:17:32.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是纯真的徽章吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.25,0:17:34.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.08,0:17:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定刚才小京那一段
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.75,0:17:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发自内心的告白引起反应了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.75,0:17:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说发自内心的告白？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.33,0:17:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我的 第二个...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.58,0:17:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.08,0:17:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.83,0:17:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.50,0:18:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉涌般的纯真 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.00,0:18:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽 麻鹰兽装甲进化而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.08,0:18:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装甲体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.50,0:18:25.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「草薙」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.33,0:18:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.75,0:18:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些攻击都是没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.00,0:18:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恶梦症候群
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.25,0:18:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.58,0:18:37.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.25,0:18:41.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.50,0:18:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.58,0:18:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.75,0:19:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别放过他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.83,0:19:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.58,0:19:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.58,0:19:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.50,0:19:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.00,0:19:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色魔戒在他的蛋壳里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.50,0:19:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.58,0:19:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他把黑色魔戒吐出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.08,0:19:32.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.50,0:19:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蛋蛋兽 你还好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.58,0:19:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你们救我的 是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.58,0:19:45.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是小京救了你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.33,0:19:47.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.75,0:19:49.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里 真是的 我很不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.08,0:19:54.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才说讨厌你 对不起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.00,0:19:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 请不要放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.33,0:19:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后我一定要更坦率的面对自己
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.08,0:20:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的 我觉得你已经够坦率了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.75,0:20:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.00,0:20:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.00,0:20:08.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都要感谢你传给我的纯真徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.08,0:20:11.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会很谨慎的继承这个特质
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.25,0:20:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.25,0:20:17.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 跟我约会好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.08,0:20:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧 你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.08,0:20:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐果然很不一样耶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.50,0:20:31.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.75,0:20:33.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定可以聚在一起并肩作战的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.00,0:20:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 到那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.75,0:20:37.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定变的比现在更强
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.58,0:20:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走了 麦克 再过不久
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.25,0:20:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门马上就要关了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.50,0:20:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.25,0:20:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还有好多话要跟你们说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.33,0:20:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,see you again 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.08,0:21:01.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.58,0:21:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.33,0:21:08.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次见了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.58,0:22:40.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,躲在暗处意图不明的伊贺兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.08,0:22:42.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小城街上 怪蛙兽们仓皇逃命
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.83,0:22:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京的麻鹰兽进化为忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.74,0:22:46.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺身而出对付伊贺兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.08,0:22:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.33,0:22:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,疾风忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.49,0:22:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽中的忍者
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.24,0:22:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.08,0:22:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和恶者 伊贺兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.99,0:22:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即将展开一场大对决
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.99,0:22:54.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.24,0:22:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「忍者兽的武功秘籍」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.82,0:23:00.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}忍者兽的武功秘籍
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.24,0:22:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了

