[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.48,0:01:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.20,0:01:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了实现征服数码世界的野心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.68,0:01:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决定长期留在数码世界不再回来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.68,0:01:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他抓走了太一的伙伴数码兽 暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且利用黑暗神圣计划 让他进化为完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.84,0:01:56.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到暴龙兽却不听使唤 变成丧尸暴龙兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.80,0:01:59.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者终于知道黑色魔轮的力量也有限
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.47,0:02:09.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}与机械暴龙兽为敌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.04,0:02:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.68,0:02:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有五分钟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种题目...我做不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.56,0:02:29.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.84,0:02:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么那么慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.92,0:02:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.84,0:02:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一学长 不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.64,0:02:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真的不是小光的错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是冈田他们不打扫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.60,0:02:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿着扫把玩才会这么慢的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.44,0:02:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害我刚才也被老师骂了一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.84,0:02:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冈田是谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.76,0:02:47.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是一起打扫的同学啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.52,0:02:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了啦 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.92,0:02:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有阻止他们 我自己也有不对的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.24,0:02:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.20,0:02:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的没有关系 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.36,0:02:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.20,0:02:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 小京呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.04,0:02:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.80,0:03:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有下课吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.20,0:03:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早就已经下课了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.64,0:03:05.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定不知道又混到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.96,0:03:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然知道了 那就快点去找她呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.32,0:03:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.44,0:03:09.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.60,0:03:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.64,0:03:13.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我来迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.88,0:03:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家总算到齐了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.60,0:03:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 拜托大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.44,0:03:21.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 小京 平时的口号
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.76,0:03:23.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.08,0:03:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.44,0:03:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.76,0:03:28.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不说出来 我们怎么会知道呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.24,0:03:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有理由 大概就是不想去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.64,0:03:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不想去就不用勉强 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.80,0:03:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.00,0:03:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别误会 我没有生气
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.92,0:03:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 我也不愿意大家被卷入危险
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.12,0:03:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最槽的情况 也不过就是我跟小光一起去而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.24,0:03:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 小京 这不是强制性的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.00,0:03:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不去也可以 不用在意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.92,0:03:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.88,0:03:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我们每个人都是因为想去才去的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.32,0:03:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉学长 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.12,0:03:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不要去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.44,0:04:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然大家都这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.44,0:04:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里等 有需要的时候再去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.56,0:04:05.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.60,0:04:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 既然你情绪不稳定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.40,0:04:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.32,0:04:13.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是呀 以你现在的心情去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.32,0:04:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反而会给大家带来麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.12,0:04:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们的口号就由小光来喊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.51,0:04:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.24,0:04:25.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.84,0:04:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.32,0:05:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不能控制完全体？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.96,0:05:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为魔轮的力量有限吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.32,0:05:06.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样 那问题在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.52,0:05:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位久等了 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.80,0:05:16.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这里 丧尸暴龙兽就在这里出现
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.64,0:05:20.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 而且他的破坏力非常强大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.48,0:05:21.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 真是气死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.08,0:05:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他明明知道亚古兽是太一的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.80,0:05:25.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还故意抓走他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.48,0:05:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我自己太小看他了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.68,0:05:32.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是没想到 这次竟然会被一个小学生给耍了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.20,0:05:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.36,0:05:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.48,0:05:38.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅 同样身为人类 我以他为耻
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.52,0:05:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.44,0:05:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我的情绪太激动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.76,0:05:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道亚古兽被带到什么地方去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.12,0:05:47.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 这个才是问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.12,0:05:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不用担心 很快就可以找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.04,0:05:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不对 大辅？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.84,0:05:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.76,0:05:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少说风凉话了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.92,0:05:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.52,0:05:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.96,0:06:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这还是我第一次见到他这么生气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.04,0:06:02.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也难怪他要生气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.28,0:06:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,依我看 我们继续待在这里也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.84,0:06:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如到附近的城镇看看能不能收集到情报
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.32,0:06:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 就这么办
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.20,0:06:14.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我单独行动去其他地方收集情报 先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.40,0:06:17.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我们也走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.44,0:06:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.20,0:06:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙兽 黑暗进化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.72,0:06:58.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的问题到底出在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.72,0:07:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.76,0:07:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才哪个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.84,0:07:26.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你知道什么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.64,0:07:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 暴龙兽 黑暗进化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.00,0:07:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏那座高塔 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.00,0:07:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.44,0:07:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是战火中的大树朽木兽 不许你们通过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.04,0:07:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.64,0:07:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我话都还没说完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.92,0:07:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.40,0:07:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.76,0:08:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.92,0:08:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道暴龙改造者往哪个方向去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.24,0:08:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是知道还是不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.56,0:08:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像往那边去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.36,0:08:15.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 好  我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.12,0:08:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我怎么办呀？救救我...救命呀...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.16,0:08:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.84,0:08:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对方是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.64,0:08:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而我却吊儿郎当的 怎么可以呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.72,0:08:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实 我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.28,0:08:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是就是做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.84,0:08:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我猜十有八九 就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.12,0:08:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以请你通知太一他们吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.36,0:08:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.36,0:08:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还是继续去收集情报 再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.80,0:08:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遭到亚古兽了 是不是？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.76,0:08:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果甲虫兽的情报没有错误的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.80,0:09:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我赶快去通知大家 地点呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在一个叫做乐可魔镇的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.20,0:09:04.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.16,0:09:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 这个魔轮的形状对付成熟期还可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.28,0:09:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是要完全控制完全体 必须处理更多的资料才行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.52,0:09:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我必须要扩充它的机能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.40,0:09:38.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还要改变形状才行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.60,0:09:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的字典里没有不可能这三个字
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.08,0:09:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里一定就是乐可魔镇了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.36,0:09:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里好像一座放置废弃铁轨的城镇一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.12,0:09:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等我 亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.88,0:09:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会救你出来的 相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.76,0:10:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得救了 可是为什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.68,0:10:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我得赶快离开这里才行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.68,0:10:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 处理能力虽然提高了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.08,0:10:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是还是不够
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.96,0:10:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.64,0:10:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要这个就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.44,0:10:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我一开始都没有想到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.12,0:10:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的数量就是力量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.28,0:10:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样处理能力提高了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.48,0:10:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收讯能力也增加了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.52,0:11:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算没有黑暗之塔发射能量也无所谓了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.52,0:11:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 就试试这个黑色魔戒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.96,0:11:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.72,0:11:10.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在要往哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.08,0:11:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要分头去找
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.44,0:11:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得分头比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.88,0:11:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火车来了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.00,0:11:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.48,0:11:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.72,0:11:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.84,0:11:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.16,0:11:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗？亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.72,0:11:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一...真的是太一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.36,0:11:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然是我呀 亚古兽你没事真的太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.36,0:11:47.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.60,0:11:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 你是不是受伤了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.60,0:11:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我很快就会好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.80,0:11:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 我们要赶快走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.24,0:11:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁着暴龙改造者还没有来攻击我们之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.56,0:12:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 我们好不容易追到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.60,0:12:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要在这个时间回去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.84,0:12:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你不用担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他这样对付亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.56,0:12:09.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会就此罢休的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.32,0:12:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会找机会讨回公道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.52,0:12:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们应该把亚古兽带到一个安全的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.20,0:12:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然太一学长都这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.72,0:12:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么可能会跑掉的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.64,0:12:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.12,0:12:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽居然跑掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.48,0:12:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他到底怎么弄掉黑色魔轮的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.44,0:12:31.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.96,0:12:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.48,0:12:35.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用管亚古兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.24,0:12:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可以利用我做进化实验啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.60,0:12:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以进化的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.12,0:12:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以进化为你战斗呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.52,0:12:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托用我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.76,0:12:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道是你故意放他走的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.00,0:12:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...因为我是小贤的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.16,0:12:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我一定可以进化的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.52,0:12:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你研究我 好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.68,0:12:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.80,0:12:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说你可以进化成什么厉害的角色吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.72,0:13:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你 你只不过是我的伙伴而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.76,0:13:04.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对 你怎么配做我暴龙改造者的伙伴呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.88,0:13:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你只不过是一只不起眼的绿色毛虫而已罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.28,0:13:07.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.20,0:13:12.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你叫我小贤也让我很不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.00,0:13:15.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫做暴龙改造者 你听到了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.52,0:13:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 小...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.76,0:13:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 暴龙改造者大王 拜托你 用我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.12,0:13:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.56,0:13:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.28,0:13:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的同伴来救他了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.00,0:13:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.48,0:13:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天算你走运
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.76,0:13:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.72,0:13:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽 你的伤还会不会痛？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.44,0:13:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会 太一 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.92,0:13:42.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.44,0:13:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你们叫我暴龙改造者 可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.36,0:13:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁要这么叫你 小贤 小贤 小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.72,0:13:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.08,0:13:52.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是真的想惹火我 是不是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.52,0:13:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是该我说的话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.28,0:13:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把亚古兽害成这样 你觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.16,0:14:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,中学生的大哥哥居然会对一个小学生大发脾气
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.68,0:14:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是太不像话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.16,0:14:05.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我的年龄比你小
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.20,0:14:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我还是看不起你 你是人类之耻
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.88,0:14:15.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没用的家伙 不管你说什么 我都不会介意的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.48,0:14:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.56,0:14:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.20,0:14:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.64,0:14:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧的勇气 烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.12,0:15:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要进化 让我进化上场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.48,0:15:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.48,0:15:05.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.08,0:15:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.72,0:15:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.76,0:15:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.64,0:15:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.44,0:15:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.00,0:15:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.00,0:15:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.72,0:15:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.52,0:15:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.68,0:15:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.92,0:15:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.12,0:16:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.48,0:16:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.44,0:16:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.04,0:16:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.84,0:16:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣针雨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.52,0:16:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.36,0:16:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是我了...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.60,0:16:37.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.96,0:16:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是可惜 你们动作太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.80,0:16:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我新发明的 黑色魔戒已经完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.72,0:16:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.72,0:16:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是改良黑色磨轮而成的控制器 黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.12,0:16:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:16:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 他被控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.12,0:17:00.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.92,0:17:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽 黑暗进化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.20,0:17:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是机械暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.72,0:17:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.16,0:17:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽 完全体数码兽 绝招是「究极破坏炮」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.16,0:17:23.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为属于病毒型 所以是蓝色的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.24,0:17:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正如我所料 这次进化成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.35,0:17:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.28,0:17:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一学长 危险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.08,0:17:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我 你知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.72,0:17:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你和他说话也没有用
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.16,0:17:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他现在已经不是你的伙伴了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.00,0:17:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他现在是我的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.84,0:17:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽 让他们见识见识完全体的厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.72,0:17:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.60,0:17:46.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快阻止机械暴龙兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽 上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.96,0:17:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.76,0:17:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.28,0:17:58.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.24,0:17:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你问我 我也不知道该怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.76,0:18:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽 有没有办法只攻击黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.92,0:18:05.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是目标太小了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.92,0:18:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且他一直在动 非常不容易瞄准
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.84,0:18:10.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.48,0:18:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.08,0:18:13.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.76,0:18:15.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手 不要攻击亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.48,0:18:17.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这样 我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.00,0:18:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点想办法不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.72,0:18:22.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经到极限了 只好试试看再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.32,0:18:26.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 拜托你们 再等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.12,0:18:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能再等了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.64,0:18:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 太一学长叫你们等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.80,0:18:30.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就等 听到没有？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.48,0:18:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.00,0:18:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.68,0:18:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极破坏炮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.96,0:18:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全体果然厉害 一下子就解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.44,0:18:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽 有你的帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.92,0:18:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信很快就可以征服数码世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.16,0:18:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.48,0:19:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 机械暴龙兽 到下一个地区去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.40,0:19:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经追不上了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.44,0:19:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 机械暴龙兽真的好厉害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.88,0:19:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.52,0:19:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们怎样才能就回亚古兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.44,0:19:22.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.40,0:19:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.24,0:19:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我太任性了 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.64,0:19:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里 我早就知道你一定会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.36,0:19:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幸好小京留下来 我才知道当地发生了什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.00,0:19:36.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 这里的情况现在怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.28,0:19:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.52,0:19:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.76,0:19:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.80,0:19:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大和学长 你为什么要打他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.60,0:19:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽被带走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.80,0:19:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一学长受到很大的打击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.60,0:19:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还打他？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.48,0:19:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.52,0:20:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.32,0:20:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.60,0:20:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里 你不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.40,0:20:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你这一拳让我清醒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.24,0:20:10.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我不应该犹豫的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.16,0:20:13.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是平常的战斗也没有绝对的胜算
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.24,0:20:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,何况我又犹豫 那一定赢不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.96,0:20:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我知道了 如果不尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.68,0:20:21.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是救不回亚古兽的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.40,0:20:24.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我想亚古兽一定也是这么希望的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.80,0:20:28.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与其被暴龙改造者控制 被他利用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.32,0:20:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不如认输比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.48,0:20:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.44,0:20:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 拜托你们一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.68,0:20:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再跟机械暴龙兽对阵的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.76,0:20:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请大家尽量战斗 不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.04,0:20:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.76,0:20:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一说的一点也没错 各位知道了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.48,0:20:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们真的为亚古兽好 下手就绝对不能犹豫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.68,0:20:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了...知道了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.24,0:20:49.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.20,0:20:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我忘了 这是小京负责的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.76,0:20:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,, 被选召的孩子 出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.68,0:21:03.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们两个到底怎么回事呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.96,0:21:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是搞不懂耶
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.40,0:22:38.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了要就回亚古兽 必须要打到他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.36,0:22:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 大辅的犹豫却减弱了他自己的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.80,0:22:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到伙伴们全力攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.36,0:22:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅的内心涌出热切的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.12,0:22:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的心情引来了新的装甲反映
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽产生了新的进化
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.68,0:22:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.04,0:22:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「蓝色闪电 雷龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.85,0:23:00.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}蓝色闪电 雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.92,0:23:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了

