[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.72,0:01:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了阻止持续侵略的移动要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.68,0:01:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借助亚古兽他们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.32,0:01:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们潜入要塞内部
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.28,0:01:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在基米拉兽压倒式的力量下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.24,0:01:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽们一一败退下来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此时 在永不放弃的大辅面前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.80,0:01:51.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黄金的装甲数码蛋出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.32,0:01:54.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽装甲进化成了金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.76,0:01:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那真是奇迹般的进化啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.40,0:02:09.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,330)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}再见了 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.12,0:02:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.28,0:02:16.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.56,0:02:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹的光芒 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.56,0:02:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进...进化了...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.36,0:02:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金...金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.48,0:02:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.52,0:02:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽利用奇迹的数码装甲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.84,0:02:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化而成的装甲体圣骑士型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.60,0:02:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是从装甲上散发出的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.64,0:02:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「极限圣战」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.04,0:02:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.88,0:02:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.96,0:02:53.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽进化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.96,0:02:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽进化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.48,0:02:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.68,0:03:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.64,0:03:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的数码兽从未见过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.36,0:03:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是新的装甲进化？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.48,0:03:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊 因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.56,0:03:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,徽章应该已经没有了才对
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.04,0:03:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和平时的不同
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.24,0:03:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许是什么特别的进化也说过不定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们这帮家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.08,0:03:30.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底要阻扰我到什么时候才够
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.96,0:03:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.28,0:03:34.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们决一胜负的时刻已经到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.64,0:03:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的力量...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.24,0:03:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.76,0:03:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:03:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.76,0:04:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 这里交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.60,0:04:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.72,0:04:12.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情 今天一定要结束
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.28,0:04:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.16,0:04:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里很危险 快点逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.36,0:04:28.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.36,0:04:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的基米拉兽已经回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.08,0:04:34.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙已经不听小贤的指挥了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.72,0:04:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.76,0:04:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.28,0:04:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨星拳击
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.84,0:04:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.36,0:04:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.44,0:04:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨星飞踢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.76,0:05:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经没有多少时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.44,0:05:09.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要塞正在慢慢崩溃中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.08,0:05:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.60,0:05:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者那个家伙会逃走的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.60,0:05:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.76,0:05:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在瞄准哪里啊 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.28,0:05:51.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在你明白了吧 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.08,0:05:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.76,0:05:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们彻底的错了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.52,0:05:58.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,错了？不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.44,0:06:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做的事怎么可能有错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.84,0:06:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是很完美的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.72,0:06:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次和以前都不一样了 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.00,0:06:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少罗嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.56,0:06:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这只是一个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:13.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此最后的赢家一定是我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.96,0:06:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到现在你还在说这种话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.00,0:06:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做的基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.08,0:06:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会输给你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.60,0:06:29.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在可不是讨论游戏胜负的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.00,0:06:33.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么认为创造数码兽是正确的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.20,0:06:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把所有的数码兽的资料收集起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.40,0:06:38.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变成自己的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.20,0:06:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太可笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.32,0:06:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽可不是玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.52,0:06:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看这些数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.84,0:06:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽也是有生命的 活生生的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.08,0:06:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我们所珍惜 无可替代的搭档
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.12,0:06:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明明是被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.48,0:07:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么就是不明白呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:03.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那只数码兽 不是你的搭档吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.20,0:07:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.56,0:07:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我相称的数码兽是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.20,0:07:15.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.20,0:07:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这座要塞已经完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.48,0:07:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想死的话 你们就悠闲的留在这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.96,0:07:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.44,0:07:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.68,0:07:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 我们也逃出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.04,0:07:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们不累吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.12,0:07:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系 包在我们身上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.44,0:07:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家没有问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.16,0:08:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.20,0:08:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.08,0:08:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.88,0:08:32.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.28,0:08:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.96,0:08:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.52,0:08:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.04,0:09:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.40,0:09:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.12,0:09:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.88,0:09:28.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.36,0:09:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等离子射线
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.28,0:09:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.88,0:10:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.52,0:10:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,极限圣战
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.12,0:10:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.40,0:10:27.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经到极限没有力气了...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.68,0:10:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.76,0:10:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 把他捏碎 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.72,0:10:41.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.24,0:10:42.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.56,0:10:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 到现在你还不明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.44,0:10:52.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前的小贤不是这样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.48,0:10:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当初一起和我探索数码世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.52,0:10:58.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.60,0:11:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起欢笑 一起哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.76,0:11:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前的小贤是非常温柔的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.52,0:11:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而第二次遇到的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.60,0:11:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你却让我叫你「暴龙改造者」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.24,0:11:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫我怎么接受呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.84,0:11:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为无论变成什么样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.52,0:11:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤就是小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.84,0:11:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以在你变成暴龙改造者之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.32,0:11:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管你做了多么过分的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.24,0:11:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信总有一天 你会变回以前的小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.92,0:11:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为相信 我才会留下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.44,0:11:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这...这个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.32,0:11:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从今往后我也会一直相信小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.12,0:11:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的小贤不是暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.52,0:11:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的小贤是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.96,0:11:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常温柔的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.40,0:12:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽 你...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.92,0:12:16.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救救小贤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.64,0:12:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.96,0:12:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.20,0:12:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救救小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.96,0:12:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽的力量...流进了我的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.24,0:12:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,极限圣战
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.52,0:12:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的基米拉兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.04,0:12:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被打败了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.32,0:13:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.56,0:13:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.52,0:13:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...输了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.80,0:13:37.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.04,0:13:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明一切都应该完美无缺才对的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.56,0:13:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子...是最差的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.48,0:13:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最坏的战斗结局
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.76,0:13:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 只有从头再来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.60,0:13:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何 重新设定数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.80,0:13:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么...重新设定数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.96,0:14:00.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以...所以现在要先回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.48,0:14:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把电脑中所有的资料都删除
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.76,0:14:05.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后...然后就可以重新再来一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.52,0:14:08.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你...在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.96,0:14:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的这样认为吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的以为删除电脑的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.12,0:14:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以重新设定数码世界吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.88,0:14:16.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.84,0:14:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把数码世界当成什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.56,0:14:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.44,0:14:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这又不是游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.76,0:14:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重设数码世界是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.52,0:14:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.24,0:14:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时侯 在足球场那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.24,0:14:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是你们这些数码兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.16,0:14:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不仅仅是电脑中的资料啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.04,0:14:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽和我们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.16,0:14:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是活生生的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.20,0:14:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽也有...生命？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.76,0:15:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说 我一直以来所做的事...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.16,0:15:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会做出那么多过分的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.32,0:15:17.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界不是梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.28,0:15:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是幻想中的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.96,0:15:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我们所居住的世界一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.88,0:15:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是另一个真实的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.64,0:15:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.88,0:15:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.92,0:15:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点气息
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.72,0:15:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于变回了以前的小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.72,0:15:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.52,0:16:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子比较适合你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.88,0:16:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说 以前的贤？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.80,0:16:11.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在动力室里面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:14.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像从那个徽章上听到了什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.12,0:16:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说是想回到真正的主人的手里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.64,0:16:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.16,0:16:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是小贤的 温柔的徽章啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.72,0:16:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的...温柔徽章...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.96,0:16:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温柔能够绽发出金黄色的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.88,0:16:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巫师兽所说的就是这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.68,0:16:42.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为 小贤很温柔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.12,0:16:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.72,0:16:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 怎么会 这么轻啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.48,0:16:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 小...贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.04,0:17:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.72,0:17:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.31,0:17:08.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死...了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.68,0:17:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.44,0:17:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 小智 小智...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.20,0:17:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不应该变成这样的...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.80,0:17:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是为了忘掉这些
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.00,0:17:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才回来到这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.00,0:17:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 应该回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.08,0:17:55.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为还有为你担心 等你回家的家人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.56,0:18:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要回家去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.36,0:18:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Ya~Ho~ 阿和~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.88,0:18:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂...正常人会追到这里来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.32,0:18:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和 你很过分哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.16,0:18:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然扔下我一个人跑来树林
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.60,0:18:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为...这个...怎么说呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.80,0:18:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.24,0:18:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一 大辅他们去哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.28,0:18:35.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大...大辅他们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.68,0:18:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎 大辅他们去哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.72,0:18:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我去找一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.76,0:18:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此 怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.40,0:18:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.36,0:19:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家没有一起行动吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.32,0:19:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然是在一起啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.84,0:19:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能在那边的树林里面玩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.48,0:19:11.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 那边那边
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.24,0:19:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.00,0:19:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是就在那里吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.40,0:19:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么姐姐也回来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.72,0:19:23.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.80,0:19:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么跟什么嘛 我好不容易才到的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.24,0:19:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就要回去了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.04,0:19:33.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们几个累的再也玩不动了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己要跟来 不要任性了行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.80,0:19:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好困 好困
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.36,0:19:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.28,0:19:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.64,0:19:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这车载不了这么多人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.60,0:19:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 不是说还有另一辆车的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.44,0:19:50.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另一辆车昨天已经回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.56,0:19:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和 你坐巴士回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.80,0:19:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.28,0:19:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.00,0:19:58.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊 阿和
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.64,0:19:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 路上请小心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.12,0:20:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等一下...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.88,0:20:05.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我和阿和一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.08,0:20:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.04,0:20:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是让我上车
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.36,0:20:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.28,0:20:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.44,0:20:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下面这条新闻是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.52,0:20:25.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从5月开始就行踪不明的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.84,0:20:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天才少年一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.16,0:20:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才在自己的家中被找到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.92,0:20:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无故失踪三个月的少年
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.92,0:20:34.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会奇迹的出现在自己家中
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.16,0:20:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在真相还不明了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.44,0:20:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之数码世界的危机暂时解除了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.20,0:20:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 大家真的很努力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.52,0:20:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 和暴龙改造者的战斗结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.68,0:20:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的被选召的孩子吗们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.28,0:20:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完成了他们第一次的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.32,0:20:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.64,0:20:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了...老公
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.20,0:21:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于一乘寺贤而言
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.92,0:21:06.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有些应该做的事 正在等着他
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.04,0:22:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和平降临的数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.48,0:22:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮组其重建的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.00,0:22:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及非常在意
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.92,0:22:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光和阿岳关系的大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.44,0:22:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.60,0:22:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要多展示自己酷酷的一面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.52,0:22:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和小光搞好关系
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.40,0:22:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅和V仔兽的恋情进化大作战开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.24,0:22:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.64,0:22:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「豪勇进化 V仔兽EX」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.39,0:23:00.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}豪勇进化 V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了

