[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.20,0:01:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者回收了黑暗的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.52,0:01:38.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于完成了基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.48,0:01:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在它恐怖的攻击下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.24,0:01:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他们不得不暂时撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:01:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们能够战胜暴龙改造者和基米拉兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.59,0:02:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}超绝进化 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.44,0:03:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 逃跑吧 恐惧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.44,0:03:27.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界落入我手也是理所当然的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.00,0:03:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.76,0:03:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是小贤所希望的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.16,0:03:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.64,0:03:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽真是可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.08,0:03:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底打算横行到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.96,0:03:51.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是可怕的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.84,0:03:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何目标
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.16,0:03:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了攻击而攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.52,0:03:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要把我们的数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:03:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在把所有都毁灭之前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.48,0:04:01.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎不打算停止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.20,0:04:02.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.16,0:04:03.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.80,0:04:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然制作出那样的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.76,0:04:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.44,0:04:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何必须要阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.68,0:04:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.12,0:04:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是要怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.36,0:04:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以现在我们的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.56,0:04:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从正面挑战基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.44,0:04:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是绝对没有胜算的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.12,0:04:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这帮人到底打算去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.76,0:04:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.68,0:04:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个就是基米拉兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.08,0:04:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比多兽的头部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.96,0:04:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外加天使兽合飞龙兽的翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.80,0:04:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,角龙兽的尾巴 加鲁鲁兽的腿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.84,0:05:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体是暴龙兽的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.12,0:05:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽的头发
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.16,0:05:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有古加兽 丧尸暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.24,0:05:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及恶魔兽的手臂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.20,0:05:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为小光给我传来了各个角度的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.68,0:05:15.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它是怎样构成才那么容易看清
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.92,0:05:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.04,0:05:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打算自己做造物主吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.72,0:05:22.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的想法未免过于天真可笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.44,0:05:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该怎么反击？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.16,0:05:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先 应该想办法停止那个移动要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.44,0:05:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是要怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.96,0:05:31.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.48,0:05:35.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织发来的邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.88,0:05:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要塞移动的方向那里发现了输油管
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.00,0:05:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法可以利用那些管子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.44,0:05:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,输油管？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.96,0:05:45.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里连过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.72,0:05:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.16,0:05:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是了 是从海底油田那里来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.04,0:05:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,输油管 石油...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.04,0:05:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.60,0:06:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想到什么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.76,0:06:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,顺利的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.80,0:06:03.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许可以停止移动要塞的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.24,0:06:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.16,0:06:08.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 很快亚古兽他们就会和你们会合
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.28,0:06:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 就可以开始作战计划了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.40,0:06:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.80,0:06:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.36,0:06:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.64,0:06:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经攻击一整夜都没有睡觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.84,0:06:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.08,0:06:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成为黑暗的一部分之后 就逃不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.88,0:06:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.04,0:06:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.00,0:06:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好好看看自己的脚下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.32,0:07:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.32,0:07:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 那还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.92,0:07:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.40,0:07:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.96,0:07:12.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很快就会成为
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.52,0:07:15.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个数码世界名副其实的皇帝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.44,0:07:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶上了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.08,0:07:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会进行顺利吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.48,0:07:35.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎说时间掌握好就没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.64,0:07:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是基米拉兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.60,0:07:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常有气势的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.96,0:07:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.32,0:07:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.00,0:08:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小型火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.08,0:08:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爆炎火焰弹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.28,0:08:16.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会起火
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.88,0:08:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点灭火
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.52,0:08:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 趁暴龙改造者现在慌乱的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.03,0:08:40.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一口气冲击要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.12,0:08:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里就是要塞的入口
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.28,0:08:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊 雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.20,0:08:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是第一个登陆的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.12,0:08:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我们的突击队长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.48,0:08:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只不过有一股傻劲而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.96,0:09:06.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能帮到这点忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.04,0:09:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.08,0:09:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.16,0:09:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来进行的很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.36,0:09:16.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是混入敌人的大本营没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.08,0:09:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在能做的只有等待
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.08,0:09:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信他们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.36,0:09:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来今晚将成为不眠之夜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.52,0:09:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于我们 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.24,0:09:31.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有那个暴龙改造者来说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.56,0:09:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是下一个入口
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.52,0:09:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什...什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.48,0:10:08.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个 那个就是动力室
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.08,0:10:10.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 到了那里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.88,0:10:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以把这个蠢笨的大家伙停下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.56,0:10:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 那些家伙来了...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.44,0:10:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.16,0:10:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.12,0:10:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 不好好欢迎一下 还不行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.64,0:10:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.08,0:10:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的受到了非常热烈的欢迎呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.56,0:10:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.80,0:10:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.32,0:10:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能让你们阻扰我们的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.60,0:10:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.16,0:10:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.20,0:10:50.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.56,0:10:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼罗宝光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.20,0:10:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣针雨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.76,0:11:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 快走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.12,0:11:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.24,0:11:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像飞机仓库哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.88,0:11:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有三层楼高吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.52,0:11:18.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.32,0:11:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.92,0:12:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 离动力室只差一点点了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.24,0:12:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 下来躲好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.20,0:12:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽非常强大
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.60,0:12:13.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不集合全员的力量 绝无胜算
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.16,0:12:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 这里交给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.80,0:12:17.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.92,0:12:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.56,0:12:20.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.28,0:12:21.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.80,0:12:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.28,0:12:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.44,0:12:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.76,0:12:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.56,0:12:36.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.76,0:12:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赤红太阳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.04,0:12:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼罗宝光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.64,0:12:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣针雨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.40,0:12:53.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:12:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.36,0:13:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.48,0:13:20.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这力量太强大了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.96,0:13:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明都躲开了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.84,0:13:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打中队友也没有关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.04,0:13:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.48,0:13:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整座要塞都会被会坏的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.40,0:13:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.00,0:13:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.88,0:13:33.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.16,0:13:35.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴风之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.72,0:13:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星光线
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.88,0:13:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,罗塞塔之石
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.88,0:13:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干掉了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.80,0:13:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招居然完全无效
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.28,0:13:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好恐怖的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.12,0:13:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.60,0:14:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然连个伤痕都没有留下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.48,0:14:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害 厉害过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.76,0:14:05.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们几个什么都做不了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.24,0:14:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去只是在白费精力而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.48,0:14:26.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.24,0:14:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奥柏兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.00,0:14:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.56,0:14:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.84,0:14:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.76,0:14:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.00,0:14:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也已经
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.32,0:14:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.24,0:14:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.00,0:14:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这帮小家伙 好像在哪里...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.84,0:15:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.12,0:15:05.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些是有生命的个体
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.08,0:15:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光凭那些攻击是不可能战胜的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.52,0:15:08.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.72,0:15:12.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有生命的个体...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.12,0:15:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,活着的？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.44,0:15:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽 停止攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.76,0:15:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽停下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.36,0:15:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在把大家抢回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 我要亲手击溃他们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.16,0:15:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤... 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.28,0:15:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.32,0:15:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.36,0:15:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去也无法战斗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.12,0:15:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作战失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.04,0:15:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暂时撤退 以后在等待时机吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.48,0:15:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 除此之外 我们别无他法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.72,0:15:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.12,0:15:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.44,0:15:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.24,0:15:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用说'以后'什么的这种悠闲的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.80,0:16:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在我们撤退的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.44,0:16:04.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙一定会继续无情攻击的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.28,0:16:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道能不能再次潜入这座要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.48,0:16:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在是唯一的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.00,0:16:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这太乱来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.40,0:16:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.08,0:16:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家可都是退化到幼年期啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.88,0:16:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.60,0:16:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 大家不是都看到了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.36,0:16:22.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,镇子被毁坏的场面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.72,0:16:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能沉默的看着却无能为力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.88,0:16:28.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的场面我不想再看到第二次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.56,0:16:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能再让这些家伙肆意妄为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.88,0:16:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就算只有我 我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.72,0:16:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能在这里放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.20,0:16:40.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经到了这里 我们没有退路了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.72,0:16:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.68,0:16:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.72,0:16:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅去的话 我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.88,0:16:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 豆丁兽 抓紧了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.83,0:17:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是千钧一发
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.64,0:17:08.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 拜托可靠一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.76,0:17:10.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.31,0:17:10.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.44,0:17:13.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能光让大辅一个人耍帅出风头嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.52,0:17:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他毕竟是突击队队长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.11,0:17:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽 开始攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.24,0:17:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.80,0:17:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里 基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.96,0:17:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.64,0:17:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.96,0:17:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 小贤 振作起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.00,0:17:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.76,0:17:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不怕 黑暗的力量有什么好怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.36,0:17:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是这个世界的王
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.76,0:17:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗力量什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.04,0:17:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天我会把你击溃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.00,0:18:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然在回收黑暗资料的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.80,0:18:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再坚决一些阻止他就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.24,0:18:08.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以保护小贤的除了我之外
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.20,0:18:10.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有别人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.48,0:18:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙想要利用黑暗力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.48,0:18:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反而被利用了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.80,0:18:16.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.64,0:18:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在我们也一口气冲向动力室
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.16,0:18:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里就是动力室了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.92,0:18:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是...暴龙改造者的...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.80,0:18:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.04,0:18:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点跟上 你不是在找动力室吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.60,0:18:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要告诉我啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.48,0:18:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是陷阱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.56,0:18:44.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我只是想要救小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.92,0:18:46.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,基米拉兽的力量强大恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.60,0:18:48.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那股力量总有一天会将
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.40,0:18:51.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤拖到我力不可及的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.76,0:18:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点阻止基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.88,0:18:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会酿成无法挽回的大错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.12,0:19:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.80,0:19:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.08,0:19:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.08,0:19:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.48,0:19:10.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.48,0:19:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.72,0:19:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像是非常强大的力量的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.56,0:19:21.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.36,0:19:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是从那块黑色石头上散发出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.96,0:19:26.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是小贤找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.68,0:19:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这块石头在移动这座要塞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.24,0:19:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 只要移除这块石头
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.92,0:19:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以停止要塞了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.48,0:19:34.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要怎么做呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.64,0:19:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,动力被...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.48,0:19:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅成功了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.68,0:19:51.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是...怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.08,0:19:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 快看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.32,0:20:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化了...为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.68,0:20:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...黄金的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.16,0:20:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才好像听到什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.32,0:20:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的装甲数码蛋吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.48,0:20:32.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 来试一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.24,0:20:33.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.48,0:20:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.04,0:20:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.76,0:20:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹的光芒 金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.52,0:20:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.96,0:20:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.40,0:20:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.72,0:20:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是奇迹般的进化
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.00,0:21:04.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像初升的太阳那般美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.68,0:21:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将世界照亮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.44,0:22:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正义的力量涌出
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.92,0:22:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闪耀着奇迹的光芒的金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.72,0:22:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是在拥有黑暗力量的基米拉兽面前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.44,0:22:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这光芒会褪色吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.40,0:22:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了自己最喜欢的一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.16,0:22:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在黑暗的根源基米拉兽的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.08,0:22:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽做出了行动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.68,0:22:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.64,0:22:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「再见了 小贤」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.35,0:23:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}再见了 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.88,0:23:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
