[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.16,0:01:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们收到了神秘女子发来的邀请函
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.20,0:01:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明知是陷阱 却还是选择跳入其中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.44,0:01:44.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后在巨大房屋被昆虫兵团围攻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.76,0:01:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更糟的是飞虫兽和钢钻兽被敌人所控制
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.60,0:01:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们命悬一线
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.55,0:02:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}蜘蛛女王的失误
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.20,0:02:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手臂...动不了...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.68,0:02:21.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.56,0:02:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.36,0:02:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求你清醒过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.12,0:02:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.84,0:02:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.84,0:02:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.88,0:02:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.28,0:02:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 叫你呢 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.16,0:02:58.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手能动的只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.04,0:03:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点通过邮件和大家取得联系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.52,0:03:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但...但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在犹豫什么 快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.56,0:03:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.88,0:03:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很想去救你们...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 抓紧我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.60,0:03:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.48,0:03:38.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我们实在没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.44,0:03:46.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳呢 小光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.00,0:03:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.92,0:04:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边似乎可以暂时抵挡一阵子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.88,0:04:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这样没法去救大辅他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.24,0:04:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他们也来不了...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.60,0:04:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 如果没有被控制的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.92,0:04:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经没希望了...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.24,0:04:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能放弃！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.32,0:04:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明他是离蜘蛛最近的...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.32,0:04:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要想想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.40,0:04:58.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个 想办法启动空调
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.28,0:04:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后利用那阵风
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.64,0:05:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.28,0:05:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用这个启动遥控器
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.64,0:05:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.96,0:05:15.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我进
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.76,0:05:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.80,0:05:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.44,0:05:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX 这边 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.36,0:06:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.60,0:06:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃到里面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.20,0:06:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要把抽屉关上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.32,0:06:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.24,0:06:37.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Lucky
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.52,0:06:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.28,0:06:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到钢钻兽居然变为敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.16,0:06:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 谁来解释一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.40,0:06:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么笛声可以控制昆虫型数码兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.60,0:06:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是声音啊 空气的震动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.92,0:07:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以消除那个声音就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.24,0:07:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是想抢到那把笛子没那么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.28,0:07:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 有没有听过飞蛾与蝙蝠的故事？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.68,0:07:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个我听说过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.00,0:07:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞蛾因为可以听见蝙蝠发出的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.68,0:07:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以它可以逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.52,0:07:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是可以听到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.92,0:07:24.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞蛾自己也可以发出声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.76,0:07:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通过声音干扰蝙蝠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.32,0:07:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从而让蝙蝠攻击他时失去方向感
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.20,0:07:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个人真是见多识广啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.40,0:07:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 只要可以干扰的那个笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.00,0:07:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以让昆虫型的数码兽复原？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.68,0:07:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.04,0:07:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们可以发出干扰的声音吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.52,0:07:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个似乎不大可能
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.24,0:07:49.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我们也不清楚那个笛声的波长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.64,0:07:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然知道了解决办法 却无法实行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.96,0:07:58.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 如果是这样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.20,0:08:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这的确是我擅长的领域 可是没有电脑...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.44,0:08:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要电脑的话 这里...书房里有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:19.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光的所在之处是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.92,0:08:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去左边的门
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.60,0:08:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.48,0:08:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳和小光去支援小京
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.44,0:08:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.44,0:08:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Bingo
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.64,0:08:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.72,0:08:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电脑怎么用就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.04,0:08:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.08,0:08:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.36,0:08:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为对音乐不感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以对这些相关的软件
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.40,0:09:04.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道要怎么用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.72,0:09:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.24,0:09:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为小京是这方面的专家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.80,0:09:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我大姐在话剧部
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.88,0:09:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是专门负责音效的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.48,0:09:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也和泉学长一起帮忙制作阿和的乐团--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.20,0:09:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,摇滚少年狼的音乐的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.48,0:09:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.76,0:09:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以明明只有四个人的乐团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.00,0:09:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却可以发出那么多的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 明明没有管乐器 我却听到了管乐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.76,0:09:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还以为自己听错了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.12,0:09:44.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 现在不是悠闲聊天的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.00,0:09:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.96,0:09:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.36,0:09:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳负责连接电脑和麦克风的线
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.96,0:09:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽负责保护阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.80,0:09:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.84,0:10:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们走吧 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.20,0:10:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光来帮忙推动电脑的鼠标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.20,0:10:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.04,0:10:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点...快点...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.20,0:10:14.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.20,0:10:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 请快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.16,0:10:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.24,0:10:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Stop
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.56,0:10:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你那里呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.68,0:10:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.08,0:10:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停 开始录笛子的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.96,0:11:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停止录音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.16,0:11:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从这里开始...一直到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.28,0:11:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.64,0:11:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,选定测量范围
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.52,0:11:33.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去除不需要的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.28,0:11:35.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,留下来的重复波纹形态
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.72,0:11:37.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保存为声音文件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.32,0:11:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,存好后播放出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.88,0:11:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.68,0:11:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...我没有听懂...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.00,0:11:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.36,0:11:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过这样的话应该没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.60,0:11:51.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.40,0:11:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 现在开始播放
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.24,0:11:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始啰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.52,0:12:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,顺利...实施了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.84,0:12:18.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是这么认为的...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.80,0:12:25.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.36,0:12:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.60,0:12:30.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.52,0:12:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另外 为什么我们会在这种地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.24,0:12:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 你们什么都不记得了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.40,0:12:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有啦 不要放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.20,0:12:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 那个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.60,0:12:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看你的丑态
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.44,0:13:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从那种地方跳下来居然毫发未伤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.76,0:13:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难不成你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.24,0:13:10.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想说我不是人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.16,0:13:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.68,0:13:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.44,0:13:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.84,0:13:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.92,0:13:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被称为蜘蛛女王的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.88,0:13:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生性邪恶残忍的完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.92,0:13:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「蜘蛛吐丝」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.16,0:13:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到我的真身不知道是你们的幸运呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.96,0:13:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不幸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.16,0:13:45.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.68,0:13:47.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦我以蜘蛛的形态出现
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.04,0:13:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是赢不了我的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.52,0:13:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛吐丝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.92,0:14:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.24,0:14:22.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.32,0:14:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,强力攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.08,0:14:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛丝可不只一根
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.60,0:14:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个数码兽是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.40,0:14:40.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 大家有危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.76,0:14:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.92,0:14:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.04,0:14:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:14:58.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,硫酸烟雾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.68,0:15:01.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛吐丝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.52,0:15:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家不是他的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.80,0:15:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.48,0:15:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.84,0:15:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.04,0:15:15.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.72,0:15:19.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.36,0:15:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.12,0:15:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.04,0:15:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算进化你们也赢不了我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.68,0:15:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.68,0:15:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.64,0:15:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X刺钉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.52,0:15:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.76,0:15:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能输啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛吐丝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.40,0:16:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.04,0:16:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.96,0:16:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起助阵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.64,0:16:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.72,0:16:13.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们来制造陷阱吧 去餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.44,0:16:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.00,0:16:17.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们先过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让机甲龙兽诱导对方到餐厅来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.60,0:16:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.24,0:16:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.68,0:16:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你输了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.64,0:16:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁输啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.84,0:16:35.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽 转移战场
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.28,0:16:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.84,0:16:38.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.00,0:16:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.72,0:16:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.68,0:16:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.00,0:16:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你尝尝这个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.72,0:17:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厉害的还没开始
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.44,0:17:08.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正餐来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.35,0:17:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.00,0:17:14.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.20,0:17:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.11,0:17:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我消停一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.88,0:17:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们并不想夺走你的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.00,0:17:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要破坏数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.60,0:17:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回答我们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.52,0:17:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多么无聊且没有意义的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.08,0:17:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.24,0:17:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问我「为什么要进行破坏？」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.48,0:17:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为破坏才是我生存的目的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.76,0:17:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么可以把黑暗之塔变成数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.76,0:17:47.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 又是没有意义的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.08,0:17:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们根本不了解黑暗之塔的真正意义
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.80,0:17:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算解释给你们听也不会明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.88,0:17:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 怎么办各位
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.28,0:17:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她并不打算反省
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.16,0:18:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错 如果放任不管的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.60,0:18:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一定会继续破坏的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.48,0:18:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 就算这样...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.44,0:18:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这件任务交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.52,0:18:08.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不必弄脏你们的手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.72,0:18:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要装酷了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.80,0:18:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不找个地方把她关起来怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.84,0:18:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.60,0:18:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这份天真一定会害死你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.36,0:18:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.64,0:18:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家退下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.48,0:18:26.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有这种程度吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.32,0:18:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.72,0:18:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎真的很想做个了断
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.72,0:18:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.08,0:18:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.24,0:18:38.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们打算怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.08,0:18:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.24,0:18:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吗？我是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.04,0:18:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙也是数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.20,0:18:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来救你了 亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.96,0:18:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.60,0:18:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.56,0:18:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.44,0:19:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊外形的完全体不死身型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.84,0:19:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.76,0:19:12.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绷带蛇击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.64,0:19:19.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就到这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.80,0:19:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走了 亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.36,0:19:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽居然还有同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.24,0:19:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.08,0:19:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们的真正目的又是什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.52,0:19:40.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是说了吗 就是破坏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.76,0:19:41.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是这么说了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.40,0:19:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和那种家伙战斗 我做的到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.92,0:19:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.60,0:19:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易还清你的救命之恩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.56,0:19:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到又欠上了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.76,0:19:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.56,0:19:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发现空调的不是你吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.68,0:20:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我吗扯平了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.28,0:20:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 那个不算
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.72,0:20:05.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以欠你的人情我一定会还的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.68,0:20:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.16,0:20:10.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 伊织 你还真倔强呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.84,0:20:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所谓的人情是什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.08,0:20:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是什么来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.04,0:20:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为伊织和一乘寺之间的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.28,0:20:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,互相帮助够得上借贷关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.68,0:20:21.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢 芝高兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.20,0:20:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织一定和大辅一样害羞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.36,0:20:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.52,0:20:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你受的伤还痛吗？ 亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.72,0:20:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这还用问吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.08,0:20:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来我多问了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.00,0:20:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去之后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.64,0:20:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会好好检查你全身的伤口并且上药的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.20,0:20:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 像傻瓜似的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.40,0:20:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起救我来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.28,0:20:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不趁机解决那些小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.20,0:20:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我不对 对不起 我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.76,0:20:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这种小问题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.92,0:20:58.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔更麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.28,0:21:01.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再被破坏的话就不妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.64,0:22:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不甘心被打败的亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.88,0:22:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有着像冰一样冷酷的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有徽章的孩子们陷入了恐慌之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.24,0:22:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.00,0:22:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使的最可怕的恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.04,0:22:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的数码兽诞生了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.60,0:22:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.96,0:22:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗究极体 黑暗战斗暴龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(195,150)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗究极体
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(360,380)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
