[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.96,0:01:34.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用奇迹的装甲数码蛋而装甲进化的金甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.56,0:01:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借用虫虫兽的力量消灭了基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.20,0:01:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗结束之后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.24,0:01:46.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于了解到自己罪孽深重的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.84,0:01:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者变回了一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.52,0:01:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这也是一直为小贤着想的虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.12,0:01:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与其离别的时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.56,0:01:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失去了一切的一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.32,0:02:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从数码世界消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.60,0:02:09.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}豪勇进化 V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.00,0:02:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这样保住了国家的命脉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.04,0:02:16.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国王牺牲了自己保住了国家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.32,0:02:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是国王的死
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.84,0:02:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在国民的心中留下了深刻的伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.32,0:02:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后这道深刻的印记
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成为了永垂不朽的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.84,0:02:31.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是可歌可泣的国语课啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.28,0:02:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把这个液体倒在试管里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.28,0:02:37.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再加上别的化学液体
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.88,0:02:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后放在酒精灯上用小火加热
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.64,0:02:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要再等3分钟就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.60,0:02:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都觉得很危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.84,0:02:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.16,0:03:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个不行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:17.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.96,0:03:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么跳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.08,0:03:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们自己要好去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.20,0:03:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重要的篮球比赛要开始啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.16,0:03:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 做的好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.28,0:03:58.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,投篮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.60,0:04:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.80,0:04:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好球
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.80,0:04:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种程度大辅也做的到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.20,0:04:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.00,0:04:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,投中了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.72,0:04:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳这家伙 就知道耍帅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.36,0:04:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.80,0:04:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 投篮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.68,0:04:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么好笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.56,0:04:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们再重新跳一遍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.04,0:04:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.08,0:04:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.68,0:04:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在生什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.00,0:04:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.52,0:04:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.16,0:04:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了 太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.76,0:05:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 大辅从刚刚开始心情就不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.24,0:05:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点打开大门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.44,0:05:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.16,0:05:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.08,0:05:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算没有了暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.84,0:05:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们照样可以来数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.44,0:05:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.00,0:05:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易数码世界才迎来了和平
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.16,0:05:35.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该趁此机会好好玩一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.08,0:05:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,额...这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.28,0:05:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光也这么想的 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.36,0:05:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊...是啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.48,0:05:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京说的也有道理
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.20,0:05:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们今天也不是来玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.04,0:05:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.44,0:05:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不就是重建数码世界的义工吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界会变成现在这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.84,0:05:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们多少得负点责任
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.00,0:06:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 数码世界的损毁状况怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.76,0:06:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...我查一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.36,0:06:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,山岳地带...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.24,0:06:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方交给我们好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.44,0:06:18.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.96,0:06:21.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 那么山岳地带交给阿岳负责
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.76,0:06:22.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是城市
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.56,0:06:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里的受损程度也相当严重
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.88,0:06:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要去 我要去！一定要去！伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.80,0:06:40.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！穿山兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.04,0:06:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完了 被抢先了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.36,0:06:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是田园地带
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.60,0:07:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该到我们了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.44,0:07:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.72,0:07:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想去那里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.04,0:07:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.80,0:07:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那么用猜拳来决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.40,0:07:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.68,0:07:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始吧 剪刀 石头 布
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.92,0:07:12.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊！输掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.76,0:07:14.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一个是湖泊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.08,0:07:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,湖泊 我和V仔兽去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.20,0:07:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的只有海岸地带了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.96,0:07:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 只能我们两个去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.08,0:07:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不工作的没有饭吃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.08,0:08:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让开让开 鼻涕兽 挡到路了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.24,0:08:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.08,0:08:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.20,0:08:18.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.56,0:08:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 怎么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.16,0:08:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳说有一件他很担心的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.64,0:08:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要说出去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.64,0:08:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在担心什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以来到数码世界意味着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.28,0:08:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为数码世界现在需要我们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.60,0:08:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.24,0:08:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 现在呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.91,0:08:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是需要我们还不确定
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.76,0:08:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是数码世界或许需要我们帮助重建
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.88,0:08:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是帮助重建什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.32,0:08:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到底只是我们自愿做的义工
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.28,0:08:52.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们还可以来到数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.52,0:08:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说明数码世界还需要我们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.84,0:08:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有着潜伏的危机
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.64,0:08:59.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是会有新的敌人？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.12,0:09:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这我还不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.40,0:09:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我认为这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.20,0:09:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉大家会比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:09.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个人都没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.44,0:09:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很奇怪 大家都去哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.84,0:09:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要躲着了 出来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.40,0:09:19.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.08,0:09:20.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.36,0:09:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.00,0:09:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你大概已经注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.08,0:09:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么阿岳和小光关系会这么好呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.64,0:09:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.24,0:09:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 投中了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.16,0:09:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和迪路兽的关系也很好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.12,0:09:45.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.00,0:09:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.00,0:09:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候我们两个应该齐心合力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.44,0:09:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,齐心合力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.92,0:09:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好地表现一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.80,0:09:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,表现一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.12,0:09:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像和小光要好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.60,0:10:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想和迪路兽那么要好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.60,0:10:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.80,0:10:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 为了这个目标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.20,0:10:25.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要进化到成熟期才行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化到成熟期？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.12,0:10:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比如说 变成超级天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.24,0:10:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就变成超级天使兽给你看看！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.20,0:11:22.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.56,0:11:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.00,0:11:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 进化为成熟期吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.88,0:11:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.56,0:11:35.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.56,0:11:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.64,0:11:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这样就可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.56,0:11:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以了 真是谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.16,0:11:44.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.84,0:11:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你们专程来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.24,0:11:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.72,0:11:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 都是你不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.24,0:11:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是我不好啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.84,0:11:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正就是你不好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.44,0:12:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛！我生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.68,0:12:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经生气了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.24,0:12:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.04,0:12:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅你给我站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.88,0:12:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一个作战计划
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.40,0:12:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先惹V仔兽生气
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.44,0:12:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着把这个吊桥毁坏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.52,0:12:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后我就会陷入致命的危机
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.48,0:12:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后V仔兽就可以
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.20,0:12:30.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化为成熟期的完美作战计划
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.56,0:12:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.76,0:12:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:40.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.72,0:12:41.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.28,0:12:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 快点进化为成熟期啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.36,0:12:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽...进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.44,0:13:05.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？这些都是为了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.36,0:13:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我进化到成熟期的计策？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.56,0:13:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来是想如果我陷入危机
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.60,0:13:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽就会进化到成熟期来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.12,0:13:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是好像不是很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.00,0:13:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.00,0:13:19.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是V仔兽的错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.88,0:13:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？那么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.52,0:13:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？那么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.36,0:13:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该回大家那里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.28,0:13:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点逃 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.08,0:13:32.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是你成熟期进化的练习计划吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.00,0:13:34.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.80,0:13:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.44,0:14:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他小便的样子被看得一清二楚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.92,0:14:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他好像生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.04,0:14:06.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.04,0:14:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,背上有很多尖刀的武装陆上乌龟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.00,0:14:10.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,属于爬虫类数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.16,0:14:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「甲骨飞刀」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.16,0:14:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是在生气
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.80,0:14:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管是谁都会生气的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.92,0:14:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来正心情很好的在小便
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.44,0:14:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却被别人看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:23.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们又不是故意去偷看的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.92,0:14:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 你觉得他会接受我们的道歉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.36,0:14:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不太可能
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.36,0:14:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道这也是为了进化而做的练习？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.08,0:14:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是练习啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.48,0:14:35.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.64,0:14:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅和V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.96,0:14:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在练习如何进化为成熟期？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.84,0:14:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅真是的 到底在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.60,0:14:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.32,0:14:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.92,0:14:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？这么慌张
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.24,0:15:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不小心看到多达兽惬意的小便的样子？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.72,0:15:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是大辅和V仔兽的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.08,0:15:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.52,0:15:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:13.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是看都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.56,0:15:14.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.24,0:15:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有人会想看那个的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.64,0:15:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有看到的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.24,0:15:34.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟没有人愿意被别人这样参观
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.36,0:15:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是没有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.48,0:15:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.12,0:15:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这样放着大辅他们不管
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.40,0:15:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.96,0:15:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多达兽不是换人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.80,0:15:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.60,0:15:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.80,0:15:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.48,0:15:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.24,0:15:55.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.84,0:15:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.56,0:15:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.04,0:15:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.72,0:16:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅还有V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.76,0:16:01.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.12,0:16:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.56,0:16:10.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不...不是我的剑道可以战胜的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.00,0:16:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.60,0:16:12.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.48,0:16:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还好没有出手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.52,0:16:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果真是不可战胜的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.40,0:16:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.84,0:16:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.08,0:16:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.12,0:16:33.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经从伊织那里收到了邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.84,0:16:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可没有闲玩的时间哪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.28,0:16:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.64,0:16:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对没有玩！没有！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.16,0:16:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很碍事哎！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.28,0:16:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点走开 去...去...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.84,0:16:51.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她居然叫我们走开
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.68,0:16:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 你好无情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.64,0:17:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊 不要再追了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.96,0:17:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 多达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.60,0:17:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在你攻击之前我有话想说...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.52,0:17:32.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？遗言吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.60,0:17:37.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到你小便的样子是我们的错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.52,0:17:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在才道歉太晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.12,0:17:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是在你攻击我们之前...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.72,0:17:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击之前？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.60,0:17:45.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请先洗手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.76,0:17:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.40,0:17:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要攻击我们 先洗好手再来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.44,0:17:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你在说什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.76,0:17:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽也觉得这样比较卫生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.48,0:17:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.76,0:18:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是现在也管不了是否卫生了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.92,0:18:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 他现在更生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.44,0:18:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.16,0:18:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.24,0:18:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.12,0:18:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 进化吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.36,0:18:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.28,0:18:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.48,0:18:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.52,0:19:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽终于进化为成熟期了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.12,0:19:04.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.32,0:19:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽用自己原本的力量进化而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.36,0:19:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成熟期幻龙型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.04,0:19:10.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「X光线」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.60,0:19:29.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甲壳飞刀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.24,0:19:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.24,0:19:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赢了 V仔兽EX 干得好！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.12,0:20:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.12,0:20:19.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有看到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.00,0:20:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多达兽这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.00,0:20:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好地在洗手哎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.60,0:20:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个可以沟通的家伙嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.28,0:20:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于玩够了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.36,0:20:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不是在玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.00,0:20:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.68,0:20:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化为成熟期V仔兽EX了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.24,0:20:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样重建工程可以早些完成了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.64,0:20:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不让大辅和V仔兽EX 多干点可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.00,0:20:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.00,0:22:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肥皂泡飞走了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.56,0:22:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里面有幼年的小贤和哥哥智的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.24,0:22:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,文武双全的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.44,0:22:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼中只有哥哥的父母
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.16,0:22:49.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞 悲伤 还有愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.92,0:22:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在翻来覆去的梦中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.48,0:22:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以看到一乘寺贤的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.12,0:22:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.40,0:22:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「神圣计划被黑暗污染之时」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(215,160)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}神圣计划被
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(425,360)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗污染之时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了

