[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.34,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.34,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.40,0:01:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将黑暗之塔变成数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.40,0:01:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并希望破坏数码世界的神秘女子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.36,0:01:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是大辅的V仔兽EX和小贤的飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.24,0:01:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化成了机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.64,0:01:52.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们破坏了神秘女子的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.44,0:01:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为计划失败而心有不甘的神秘女子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.64,0:02:00.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次会用什么手段攻击过来呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.33,0:02:09.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,330)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}昆虫使者的陷阱！！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.68,0:02:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.80,0:02:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.20,0:02:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,碎裂角
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.88,0:02:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,锁链尾锤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.24,0:02:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厉害 厉害 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.40,0:02:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 久等了 大家都辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.48,0:02:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.56,0:02:56.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.08,0:02:58.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙也在努力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.00,0:03:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快看 豆丁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.36,0:03:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 合体进化的时候是什么感觉啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.64,0:03:06.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么感觉啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.88,0:03:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该就是内心深处有力量涌出的感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.40,0:03:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像是成长期进化到成熟期那样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.64,0:03:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 比那还厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.24,0:03:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么当时的意识呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是说虽然身体合二为一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.20,0:03:20.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是意识还是分开的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.36,0:03:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有感到有两种意识
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.60,0:03:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.12,0:03:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像是意识在脑海里结合的感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.00,0:03:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,意识结合？ 到底是怎样的感觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.24,0:03:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然数码兽们才是最关心合体进化的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.88,0:03:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们才是当事人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.80,0:03:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么大辅呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.44,0:03:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时有没有什么感觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.84,0:03:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然有感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.44,0:03:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺心脏跳动的声音...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.64,0:03:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咚...咚...每一声都听的到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.20,0:03:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就意味你们的心跳也同步了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.84,0:03:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的心脏和一乘寺的心脏齐步走？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.04,0:04:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京的意思不是你们的心脏齐步走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.56,0:04:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指你们心跳速度合拍的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.20,0:04:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对 对 就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.68,0:04:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 为什么是大辅和一乘寺的数码兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.76,0:04:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说这样不好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.28,0:04:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 就是组合
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.92,0:04:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在想其他的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.64,0:04:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是也可以合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.72,0:04:20.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比如...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.16,0:04:23.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX和天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.40,0:04:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多其他组合的可能
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.48,0:04:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX和迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.40,0:04:33.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX和亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.60,0:04:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX和战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.40,0:04:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.12,0:04:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说「咦」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.84,0:04:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道是对我们的数码兽合体进化有意见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.28,0:04:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.32,0:04:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得不要勉强去合体进化也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.92,0:04:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又不...喜欢战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.64,0:04:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么话就直说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.24,0:04:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.08,0:04:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化什么的...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.40,0:04:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说不要咕咕哝哝的了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.48,0:05:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天女兽和亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.48,0:05:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽和迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.72,0:05:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.80,0:05:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.04,0:05:15.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.52,0:05:17.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.44,0:05:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.44,0:05:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要得到完全体那样强大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.12,0:05:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相应的就会消耗相当巨大的能量
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.52,0:05:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 这是一种非常沉重的负担
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.88,0:05:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会缩短你的寿命
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.04,0:05:34.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.92,0:05:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并没什么证据
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.04,0:05:39.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到底也只是我的推测而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:40.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.08,0:05:44.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果小贤不希望我冒险的话 我就不去做了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.72,0:05:47.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你是在担心我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.20,0:05:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吧 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.28,0:05:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.08,0:06:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道小贤是绝对不会说谎的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.16,0:06:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于他们成为同伴还是感到很矛盾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.20,0:06:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我可以等的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.48,0:06:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等的小贤愿意的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.84,0:06:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.16,0:06:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.92,0:06:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那群小鬼以为自己
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.04,0:06:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是正在进行运动比赛的选手吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.12,0:06:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,次元不一样 这是次元的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.48,0:06:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.16,0:06:53.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个女的到底在哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.88,0:06:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然破坏了黑暗之塔很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.40,0:06:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是实在太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.72,0:07:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要想办法抓住那个女的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.96,0:07:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能够让她继续的破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.24,0:07:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个女的到底在哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.20,0:07:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然破坏了黑暗之塔很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.80,0:07:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是实在太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.00,0:07:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要抓住我？想要让我住手？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.60,0:07:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,未免太小看我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.72,0:07:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此 那就来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.56,0:07:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你们好好见识一下自己是多么的天真
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.88,0:07:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.88,0:07:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果想见我的话 欢迎到巨大房屋来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.60,0:07:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像很有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.04,0:07:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这一定是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.12,0:07:39.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.32,0:07:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是总有一天会和她正面对上的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.76,0:07:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.20,0:07:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 事先申明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.84,0:07:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦发生危险 要马上撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.20,0:07:52.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.64,0:07:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.04,0:08:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出售  巨大房屋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.84,0:08:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么回事啊 这座房子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.44,0:08:14.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大啊 大过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.20,0:08:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有普通房子的30倍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.00,0:08:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们简直就像是在格列佛游记中的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.00,0:08:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨人国中迷路了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.80,0:08:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是回去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.20,0:08:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.32,0:08:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里一看就是个陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.84,0:08:32.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我也想这么认为...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.20,0:08:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你们都这么认为了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.88,0:08:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么请回吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.00,0:08:39.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们那边也收到邮件了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.44,0:08:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说 我以为只有我收到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.64,0:08:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到也发给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.04,0:08:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从敌人的立场来说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.32,0:08:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她是想把我们一网打尽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.88,0:08:51.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.92,0:08:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 你们就更不应该去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.08,0:08:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这么说是打算自己一个人去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.48,0:09:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样太危险了 还是一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.60,0:09:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.00,0:09:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之前不是约定好先观察一下情况吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.76,0:09:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.72,0:09:13.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟大辅还有一乘寺先进去打探一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.88,0:09:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他人留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.76,0:09:18.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.92,0:09:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 一起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.00,0:09:27.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是不能只把小光和小京留在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.52,0:09:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你们也留在这里比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.88,0:09:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.44,0:09:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为合体进化的搭档 当然要一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.76,0:09:38.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一出事 那不就完蛋了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.60,0:09:40.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然啰嗦了些
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.28,0:09:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是请你们不要轻举妄动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.96,0:09:44.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心 我会盯着他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.72,0:09:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 那么先锋队出发
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.36,0:09:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明知是陷阱 却自投罗网
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.08,0:09:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真是自寻死路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.36,0:10:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想陪小鬼们浪费时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.32,0:10:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在你们打倒我之前 先解决你们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.00,0:10:08.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为此我会不择手段的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:38.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才伊织说什么格列佛游记
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.84,0:10:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果真如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.08,0:10:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算这样说 我还是不明白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.52,0:10:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,格列佛游记是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.08,0:10:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,格列佛游记说的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.08,0:10:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沿着豆子的藤蔓爬上云端
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.00,0:10:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便可到达巨人国了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.60,0:10:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 你说的是杰克与豌豆的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.40,0:10:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,杰克和格列佛不是一个人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.00,0:10:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.48,0:11:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.68,0:11:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个还是进屋刺探下敌情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.28,0:11:05.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.60,0:11:06.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是幻觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.36,0:11:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.96,0:11:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 的确
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.36,0:11:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里好像有什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.48,0:11:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.88,0:11:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么有种不祥的预感...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.12,0:11:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是蟑螂兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.16,0:11:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.04,0:11:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.44,0:11:30.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有没有听见什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.64,0:11:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有听见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.08,0:11:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪 是错觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.16,0:11:34.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难...难道是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.92,0:11:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好多啊！来攻击我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.64,0:12:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.60,0:12:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.52,0:12:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.80,0:12:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.68,0:12:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.88,0:12:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.76,0:12:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.24,0:13:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们连绵不断的攻击过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.28,0:13:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去可没完没了了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.64,0:13:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.96,0:13:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 合体进化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.56,0:13:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.60,0:13:12.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没有听见吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.44,0:13:15.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.52,0:13:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.20,0:13:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.36,0:13:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看看敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.64,0:13:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并未被黑色魔轮和黑色魔戒控制啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.16,0:13:25.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.32,0:13:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有证据吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.16,0:13:30.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种...东西...没有...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.56,0:13:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以还是先逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.48,0:13:33.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.04,0:13:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.56,0:13:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 大家快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.28,0:13:45.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙到底什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.32,0:13:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你问这个？他们是黄蜂兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.04,0:13:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这我当然知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.16,0:13:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是问他们为什么攻击我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.60,0:13:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个我就不知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.00,0:13:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.72,0:13:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.20,0:14:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黄蜂兽加上螳螂兽 数量太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.36,0:14:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是巨大房屋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.52,0:14:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃到里面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.76,0:14:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.04,0:14:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好 V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.56,0:14:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把蟑螂兽全部淹掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.84,0:14:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又有别的东西接二连三的出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.16,0:14:43.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古尼兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.12,0:14:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身有闪电花纹的幼虫型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.88,0:14:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「闪光电击」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.36,0:14:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.56,0:14:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.36,0:15:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.52,0:15:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,, 战甲兽 装甲进化成潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.80,0:15:08.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.52,0:15:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.56,0:15:26.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.56,0:15:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永不止息的诚实 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.52,0:15:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 潜鲨兽 出发
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.04,0:15:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出发啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.24,0:15:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽 抓紧了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.84,0:16:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 出水吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.96,0:16:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点找到大辅他们的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.36,0:16:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是他们到底在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.48,0:16:27.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们分头找会快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.72,0:16:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.92,0:16:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样怎么找啊？ 光逃都来不及了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.48,0:16:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.68,0:16:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 谢谢你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你救了我 穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.24,0:16:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.16,0:16:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 不要误会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.08,0:16:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是为了偿还从闪电球兽那里救了我的恩情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.88,0:16:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.56,0:16:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.88,0:16:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 还是要谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.68,0:16:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫 再磨蹭的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.88,0:17:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的敌人又要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.92,0:17:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得对 快点离开这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.20,0:17:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女皇之光
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.44,0:17:21.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.56,0:17:22.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看样子是书房
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.44,0:17:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃到书桌后面去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.48,0:17:40.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是刚才听到的笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.96,0:17:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的确有笛子的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.36,0:18:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.40,0:18:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天要和你一决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.88,0:18:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平时废物一样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.24,0:18:08.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天好像特别的伟大耶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.92,0:18:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是想在朋友面前装酷耍帅？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.08,0:18:11.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.60,0:18:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「为什么非是我不可？」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.76,0:18:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用一辈子的时间去想这个问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.92,0:18:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.88,0:18:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然这样...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.08,0:18:22.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫 合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.28,0:18:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.80,0:18:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.44,0:18:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.32,0:18:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么！飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.84,0:18:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那个笛声...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.24,0:18:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个笛声控制了飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.24,0:18:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼 你竟然注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.44,0:18:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 把那个笛子夺过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.60,0:18:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.20,0:18:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.28,0:19:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.44,0:19:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.68,0:19:32.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 连钢钻兽也...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.84,0:19:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.48,0:19:37.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你侥幸发现了笛子的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.96,0:19:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是进化的形态似乎搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.64,0:19:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.36,0:19:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊！我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.04,0:19:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个笛子只能控制昆虫型的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.52,0:19:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来攻击我们的蟑螂兽和古尼兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.76,0:19:51.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也都是昆虫型的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.76,0:19:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以早点注意到的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.68,0:19:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管早晚 结果都是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.80,0:19:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.68,0:20:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.44,0:20:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.20,0:20:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 给我适可而止啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.76,0:20:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,动不了了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.72,0:20:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是蜘蛛网！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.56,0:20:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么看 这里都是你们的坟墓了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.56,0:20:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怪就怪你们自己不自量力
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.96,0:20:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闯进这个陷阱里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 蜘蛛兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.60,0:22:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向大辅他们逼近的蜘蛛兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.80,0:22:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被控制的飞虫兽和钢钻兽也在攻击孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.96,0:22:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回响的笛声被小京用电脑分解
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.60,0:22:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于神秘女子现出了她可怕残忍的真身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.32,0:22:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后新出现的谜之黑影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.00,0:22:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.36,0:22:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「蜘蛛女王的失误」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:03.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,330)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}蜘蛛女王的失误
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.88,0:23:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
