[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.32,0:01:35.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变回数码蛋再次诞生的虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.24,0:01:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被生命的光芒所感动的小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.16,0:01:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于回到了现实的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.36,0:01:55.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是小贤和大辅他们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.16,0:01:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在通往光明的道路上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.92,0:02:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有可能迷失方向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.51,0:02:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}大地装甲 战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.80,0:02:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 要再添些吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.59,0:02:25.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.88,0:02:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,够了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.92,0:02:29.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还在长身体呢 多吃一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.28,0:02:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 这个很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.96,0:02:40.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.88,0:02:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 要多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.40,0:02:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点点就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.12,0:02:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我也要添饭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.36,0:02:56.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:58.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.40,0:03:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃的有点撑了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.28,0:03:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为爸爸妈妈都很开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.52,0:03:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们希望我像其他健康的男孩一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.76,0:03:09.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃很多很多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.88,0:03:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明可以不用勉强自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.04,0:03:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并没有勉强自己
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.12,0:03:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.44,0:03:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要爸爸妈妈开心就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.88,0:03:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 吃完饭之后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.48,0:03:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,运动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.32,0:03:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,运动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.12,0:03:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,运动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.12,0:03:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,运动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.88,0:03:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂！不要在床上玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.28,0:03:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.96,0:03:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.64,0:03:54.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经没有利用价值了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:04:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你没有用了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.48,0:04:03.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.44,0:04:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.96,0:04:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.16,0:04:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在精神上失去了自由
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.39,0:04:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同情你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.84,0:04:26.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.04,0:05:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就做到这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.16,0:05:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.28,0:05:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多很多被损坏的房子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.16,0:05:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.08,0:05:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是这座城镇
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.80,0:05:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他的地方也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.48,0:05:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个真够碍眼的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.60,0:05:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是把它毁掉算了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.44,0:05:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.64,0:05:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在还是以重建城镇为优先吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.24,0:05:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.68,0:05:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.36,0:05:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后他怎么样了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.96,0:05:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是说一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让那家伙也来帮忙就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.52,0:05:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.76,0:05:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.92,0:05:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他或许再也不会来数码世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.76,0:05:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.96,0:05:53.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想数码兽们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.00,0:05:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕无法原谅那家伙所做过的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.28,0:05:58.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.32,0:06:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.84,0:06:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我无法原谅他所做的事情！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.08,0:06:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.84,0:06:08.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饭团 饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.72,0:06:13.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 今天我要上剑道课
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.08,0:06:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里分别吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.56,0:06:18.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剑道加油
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.08,0:06:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.40,0:06:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织家的饭团...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.16,0:06:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.68,0:06:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.04,0:06:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...面...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.76,0:06:55.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就到此为止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.12,0:07:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.28,0:07:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.40,0:07:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要来包「啾啾」呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.40,0:07:20.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的口感
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.72,0:07:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来我以为所有的果冻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.96,0:07:25.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是用勺子一勺勺挖来吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.60,0:07:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有想到还有这样吸的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.28,0:07:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次吸这个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.32,0:07:34.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉得不过瘾 想要再吸一包
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.48,0:07:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有这种感觉呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.40,0:07:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个... 差不多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.44,0:07:53.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微往右一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.76,0:07:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,右？啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.28,0:07:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 极乐世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.36,0:08:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么样啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.32,0:08:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.80,0:08:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完蛋了！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.20,0:08:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是屡教不改啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.64,0:08:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.03,0:08:41.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好慢哦 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.88,0:08:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是麻烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.24,0:08:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又没做什么 早点放了我不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.76,0:08:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.08,0:08:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,踢了会足球 结果不小心把玻璃...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.52,0:08:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明道歉了 可是就是不肯放过我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.48,0:08:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又闯祸了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.68,0:08:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为大辅总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.12,0:08:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.00,0:09:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连小光都...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.12,0:09:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了 别想这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.36,0:09:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.68,0:09:11.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.72,0:09:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些小家伙是哪里来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.20,0:09:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类 人类！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.44,0:09:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好有趣！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.24,0:09:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起玩吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.04,0:09:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的幼稚园
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.72,0:09:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为修好了 所以小朋友都回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.36,0:09:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有这么多人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.56,0:09:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些孩子就是幼稚园的学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.56,0:09:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 城镇重建之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.64,0:09:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽们就会回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.64,0:09:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真有精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.52,0:09:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超死人了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.76,0:09:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.40,0:09:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.68,0:10:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅态度转变的太快了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.24,0:10:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 今天也振作精神准备开工了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.80,0:10:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.76,0:10:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.52,0:10:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.24,0:10:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.16,0:10:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.84,0:10:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 再来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.72,0:10:51.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.80,0:10:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.36,0:11:04.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化不了啊 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.84,0:11:06.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你干劲不足的关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.48,0:11:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要有决心 有决心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.56,0:11:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化！V仔兽EX！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.92,0:11:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.64,0:11:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪 昨天明明可以进化的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.52,0:11:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你哪里不舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.40,0:11:26.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.48,0:11:28.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在刚才太不停的吃零食呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.24,0:11:30.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃太多了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.84,0:11:31.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.84,0:11:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近都没有什么战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.32,0:11:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,运动量不足的缘故吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.80,0:11:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外加吃的太多
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.44,0:11:37.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要节食 节食减肥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.96,0:11:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.20,0:11:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,试试装甲进化看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.08,0:11:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.80,0:11:46.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 不能进化也没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.88,0:11:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我们几个装甲进化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.28,0:11:51.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.96,0:11:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 我们去哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.36,0:11:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有些在意昨天修好的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.08,0:11:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马上就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.04,0:12:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.00,0:12:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 你们有别的工作哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.24,0:12:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.76,0:12:08.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.92,0:12:10.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也试一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.76,0:12:11.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.44,0:12:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.92,0:12:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.12,0:12:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.64,0:12:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连巴达兽都不能进化
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.44,0:12:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.56,0:12:48.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道之前的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.96,0:12:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又开始干扰我们了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.80,0:13:28.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 给
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.96,0:13:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们就继续昨天的地下工程
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.04,0:13:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.24,0:13:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我们要负责照顾孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.16,0:13:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总要有人照看他们才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.76,0:13:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看他们也挺喜欢大辅的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.92,0:13:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.28,0:13:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.92,0:13:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.64,0:13:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是「大」下去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.40,0:14:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看球 看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.68,0:14:05.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样子控球的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.48,0:14:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.84,0:14:09.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.12,0:14:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起去追那个球
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.52,0:14:18.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 停球！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.36,0:14:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.40,0:14:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看球去那边了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.24,0:14:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做的好 继续加油
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.48,0:14:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 接着努力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.48,0:14:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.20,0:14:38.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来进行的很顺利啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.68,0:14:40.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托他照看小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.08,0:14:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是明智的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.60,0:14:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跑起来 跑起来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.72,0:14:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅在数码宝宝当中仍然是个孩子王呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.24,0:14:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 怎么样了 原因知道了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.68,0:14:58.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 另外我们也无法进行普通进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.20,0:14:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.48,0:15:02.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了 先暂停观察一阵子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.88,0:15:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.60,0:15:08.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都被埋在地底下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.00,0:15:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者那家伙还真是作恶多端
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.40,0:15:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.04,0:15:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始吧 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.16,0:15:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.40,0:15:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.32,0:15:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闪电球兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.60,0:15:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体上永远充满电的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.04,0:15:34.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然身体小
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.08,0:15:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却能发出1000万伏特的电流进行攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.12,0:15:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「闪电球」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.68,0:15:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会攻击我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.36,0:15:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明没有黑色魔轮和黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.36,0:15:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我们应该怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.12,0:15:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 应该战斗吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.00,0:16:00.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.28,0:16:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.00,0:16:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么无缘无故的攻击我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.44,0:16:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难不成是暴龙改造者？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.16,0:16:17.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...又不能战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.36,0:16:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.56,0:16:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.44,0:16:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:01.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化了...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.12,0:17:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.44,0:17:06.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身披覆铠甲般硬壳的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.16,0:17:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突击攻击的破坏力超强
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.04,0:17:10.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是腾空飞起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.80,0:17:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再以巨大的身体把敌人压扁的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.35,0:17:13.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「万吨压力」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.59,0:17:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有用尾巴上的铁球猛力捶打敌人的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「锁链尾锤」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.35,0:17:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我能够进化了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.80,0:17:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.96,0:17:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.88,0:17:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才V仔兽明明不能进化啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.04,0:17:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之我们先出去再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.80,0:17:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织先去躲起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.32,0:17:36.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要战斗了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.36,0:17:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要想法赶走他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.88,0:17:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.40,0:17:46.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.56,0:17:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.72,0:18:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个数码兽是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.24,0:18:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有见过耶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.20,0:18:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.24,0:18:06.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.72,0:18:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.56,0:18:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.60,0:18:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.16,0:18:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个数码兽该不会是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.36,0:18:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 穿山兽进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.52,0:18:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进化了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.80,0:18:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.20,0:18:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 那个呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.00,0:18:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.84,0:18:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个绿色的刚才救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.40,0:18:32.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺丁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.56,0:18:42.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.44,0:18:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.88,0:18:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.44,0:18:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他再次回到数码世界了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.72,0:19:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.84,0:19:07.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.00,0:19:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽也可以进化了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.48,0:19:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙...救了伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.80,0:19:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.68,0:19:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 球来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.04,0:19:28.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跑起来 跑起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.76,0:19:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.84,0:19:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很有人气嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.60,0:19:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.92,0:19:36.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 冲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.44,0:19:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.96,0:19:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.80,0:19:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白天还在那里的黑暗之塔不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.44,0:19:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.40,0:19:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候被...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.44,0:19:56.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才能进化的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:19:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.48,0:20:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.04,0:20:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让那个家伙逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.56,0:20:07.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.28,0:20:09.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次还有机会的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.16,0:20:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.48,0:20:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.88,0:20:26.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,面...面...面...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.44,0:20:25.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会救我 为什么要救我 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.28,0:20:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 面不是剑道的全部
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.28,0:20:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.88,0:20:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你需要更柔和的心和头脑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.56,0:20:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像「啾啾」果冻那样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.56,0:20:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 被抢先了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.44,0:22:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤明明已经成了同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.80,0:22:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京的表现却很犹豫
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.92,0:22:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.20,0:22:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤选择与大家并肩作战
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.44,0:22:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京的迷茫消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.12,0:22:47.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对小贤的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.12,0:22:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让麻鹰兽飞上天空进化为新的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.80,0:22:53.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.20,0:22:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「天空骑士 亚古拉兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.23,0:23:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}天空骑士 亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.04,0:22:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
