[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:19.28,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.30,0:00:24.22,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:31.70,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.81,0:00:36.45,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:43.05,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.23,0:00:47.64,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:57.20,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.90,0:01:03.72,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.87,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.90,0:01:16.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.46,0:01:21.47,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.16,0:01:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将伊织和战甲兽从危机中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.16,0:01:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救出来的迷之数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.91,0:01:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的真身是虫虫兽的成熟期 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.50,0:01:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们因为这个事实而感到惊讶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.41,0:01:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时也引起了骚乱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}天空骑士 亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.75,0:02:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么看来一乘寺贤也有优点嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.41,0:02:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.58,0:02:22.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他可是救了我们唉！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.83,0:02:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就结果来看是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.08,0:02:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说他别有用心？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.75,0:02:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.58,0:02:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你说你不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.75,0:02:32.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.25,0:02:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还想再观察一阵子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.75,0:02:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他以前的确做过不少错事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.50,0:02:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是过去的事就算原谅他也...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.16,0:02:50.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不行啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.16,0:02:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能做得到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.33,0:02:58.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想想那些被暴龙改造者折磨的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.33,0:03:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽们的心情感受...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.08,0:03:04.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是他已经不是过去的一乘寺贤了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.33,0:03:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.58,0:03:07.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.83,0:03:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然在虫虫兽死去的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.08,0:03:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他应该察觉到数码兽也有生命这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.33,0:03:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是在最近的这场战斗中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.41,0:03:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他却一言不发的杀死了数码兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.83,0:03:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我无法理解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.33,0:03:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样也能说他和以前不一样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.25,0:03:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.16,0:03:40.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.66,0:03:43.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他想让一乘寺贤成为我们的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.66,0:03:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我反对...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.41,0:03:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.66,0:03:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正一乘寺贤也没有这个意思吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.50,0:03:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人不是说变就会变的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.16,0:03:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 一乘寺贤改变了这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.25,0:03:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为大辅说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.16,0:03:58.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.00,0:04:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我更想知道黑暗之塔为什么会恢复功能呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.91,0:04:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有为什么会无故消失
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.25,0:04:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.16,0:04:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成绩一落千丈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.08,0:04:14.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不是向来不在意学校的考试吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.66,0:04:15.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是指他故意的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.83,0:04:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是看起来不像
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.33,0:04:19.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.08,0:04:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找我有事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.33,0:04:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.16,0:04:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不打算向大家以及数码兽们道歉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.83,0:04:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然 如果你有道歉的意思的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.16,0:04:45.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机会的话 我帮你准备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.75,0:04:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.33,0:04:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.33,0:04:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你答应了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.41,0:04:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的 还好我跟你提了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.16,0:04:57.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我道歉就会被原谅吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.83,0:05:00.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能没有办法马上被接受
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.66,0:05:03.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是大家一定会理解你的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.58,0:05:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.16,0:05:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.41,0:05:10.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们都是被选召的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.00,0:05:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.00,0:05:15.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.75,0:05:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.91,0:05:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.83,0:05:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 成为伙伴这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.75,0:05:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.25,0:05:26.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.00,0:05:27.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.41,0:05:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.75,0:05:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同意道歉却不愿成为伙伴 为什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.91,0:05:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他可能需要时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等他梳理好自己的心情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.66,0:05:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅好有干劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.75,0:05:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.75,0:05:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是刚才他的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.66,0:05:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经不像之前那样轻视别人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.08,0:05:58.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒好像下了什么决定似的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.50,0:06:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生了什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.25,0:06:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之大辅的意思我都能明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.66,0:06:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.83,0:06:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个人说的是真心话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.58,0:06:17.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.66,0:06:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.00,0:06:21.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是比起那个 你的想法更加重要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.00,0:06:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的想法？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.75,0:06:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是真的想原谅那个男生呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.16,0:06:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本周双子星座 又是AB血型的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.25,0:06:31.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要可以坦诚说出自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.91,0:06:33.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恋爱运就会很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.00,0:06:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 不要误会啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.75,0:06:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是男朋友的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.75,0:06:39.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了 不管是什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.16,0:06:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要不后悔就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.25,0:06:45.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己的想法...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.16,0:06:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己的想法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.25,0:06:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么在意的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.58,0:06:53.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,直接去找一乘寺贤谈下不就得了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.00,0:06:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.75,0:06:57.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是一乘寺的电话号码
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.25,0:06:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和他的电子邮箱我都不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.25,0:07:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电子邮箱地址的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.50,0:07:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上次的杂志报道中不是登出来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.58,0:07:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.00,0:07:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 一乘寺到底是怎么想的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.33,0:07:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.50,0:07:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.25,0:07:26.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽的成熟期进化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「终结刺丁」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.75,0:07:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做的话 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.25,0:07:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.83,0:07:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.08,0:07:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦 美美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雪球兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.33,0:08:03.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身披覆着雪白毛皮的幼年期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.50,0:08:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「砖石星辰」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.75,0:08:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？你们喜欢吃我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.00,0:08:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 巴鲁兽真是的 跑哪里去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.50,0:08:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点回来 棉花糖可要被吃光了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.00,0:08:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把这个放到茶中的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.58,0:08:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美一定也会很高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.08,0:08:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类 并且还是大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.33,0:08:35.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了孩子居然还有人可以来到数码世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.50,0:08:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这...这个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.00,0:08:57.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏这座水坝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.00,0:09:00.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让下游的城镇体会下水乡泽国的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.25,0:09:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大事不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.08,0:09:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美...美美...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.25,0:09:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.83,0:09:10.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 快点 我要进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.33,0:09:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽 发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.75,0:09:21.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.00,0:09:24.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是高力兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.00,0:09:26.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高力兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.00,0:09:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身由岩石组成的矿石型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.75,0:09:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「曲线追击」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.08,0:09:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真是好危险
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.75,0:09:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.50,0:09:41.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽 你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.08,0:09:44.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快点...阻止的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.50,0:09:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙...要破坏水坝...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.25,0:09:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了...那个水坝被破坏的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.00,0:10:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点...联系...大家...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.25,0:10:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.58,0:10:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.75,0:10:17.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴们 救命啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.33,0:10:19.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.50,0:10:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.58,0:10:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.25,0:10:32.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.00,0:10:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.33,0:10:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 打算破坏水坝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.50,0:10:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.58,0:10:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是高力兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.25,0:10:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 请保护我们的小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.58,0:10:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小镇？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.00,0:10:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水坝被破坏的话 我们的家...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.58,0:10:51.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 交给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.50,0:10:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴们 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.50,0:11:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先把他从水坝上弄下来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.75,0:11:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.50,0:11:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.50,0:11:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.58,0:11:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.08,0:11:14.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.08,0:11:17.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.00,0:11:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好强大的...力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.25,0:11:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家瞄准黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.50,0:11:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.33,0:11:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没看到什么黑色魔戒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.00,0:11:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 他没有被控制？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.25,0:11:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 不是和闪电球兽一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.25,0:11:47.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.25,0:11:48.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.25,0:11:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.83,0:11:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.25,0:12:01.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.75,0:12:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.33,0:12:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.83,0:12:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.33,0:12:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水坝被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在该怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.25,0:12:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的家...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.00,0:12:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 先保护小镇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.25,0:12:50.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.50,0:12:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,罗塞塔之石
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.83,0:13:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.00,0:13:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊 伙伴们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.50,0:13:16.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.58,0:13:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.58,0:13:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使合击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.00,0:13:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.58,0:13:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.00,0:13:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.08,0:13:54.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.08,0:13:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高力兽他...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.83,0:14:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.08,0:14:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是认真的...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.00,0:14:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,认真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.08,0:14:05.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是真的想要破坏水坝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.00,0:14:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他这么做到底是为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.00,0:14:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.00,0:14:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他打算破坏这个小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.25,0:14:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.25,0:14:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有住在那里的数码兽们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.75,0:14:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个我知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.50,0:14:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.00,0:14:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做那么过分的事情呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:24.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对方是认真的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.33,0:14:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也要全力应战
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.75,0:14:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全力应战 怎么全力啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.08,0:14:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竭尽全力打到他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.00,0:14:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是说要杀死他？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.50,0:14:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.00,0:14:37.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你先冷静下来 理性的思考下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.08,0:14:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来又能怎么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.25,0:14:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.75,0:14:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么 先守住水坝再说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.25,0:14:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不打倒敌人怎么守住水坝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.50,0:14:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会有办法的 一定会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.00,0:14:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.25,0:14:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们可以暂时阻止对方的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.33,0:14:52.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是坚持不了多久
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.50,0:14:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了打到他 没别的办法吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.58,0:14:59.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道我们只能像一乘寺那样做吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.00,0:15:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他可以做到呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.58,0:15:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为只有这条路可走吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.50,0:15:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我们的想法太天真了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.25,0:15:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.83,0:15:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果这么做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.75,0:15:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们和那些家伙有什么区别
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.00,0:15:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.75,0:15:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.75,0:15:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织你误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.50,0:15:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙会打倒敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.00,0:15:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肯定有不得不打到对方的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.50,0:15:24.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你能够这么想呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.50,0:15:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你相信他已经改过自新了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.50,0:15:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.25,0:15:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有没有人知道一乘寺贤的邮箱地址
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.00,0:15:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.25,0:15:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.83,0:15:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他一定也有DT暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.00,0:15:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.75,0:15:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向那个家伙求救？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.33,0:15:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.83,0:15:49.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这倒不是 但是他会来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.25,0:15:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我是希望他来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.50,0:15:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是无法坦诚的说出来...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.00,0:16:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.50,0:16:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.25,0:16:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 这座水坝被毁掉的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.00,0:16:24.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小镇一定会完蛋的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.08,0:16:30.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.00,0:16:34.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.50,0:16:37.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他来救我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.33,0:16:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 谢谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 他真的是个不错的伙伴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.75,0:16:46.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许就像大辅说的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.50,0:16:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他一定知道些什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.25,0:16:50.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以...所以才会...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.08,0:16:56.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴鲁兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.75,0:16:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你终于醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.58,0:17:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美美 那个家伙在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.00,0:17:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在飞虫兽正在从高力兽手中保护水坝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.25,0:17:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不是高力兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.25,0:17:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙不是高力兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.08,0:17:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.50,0:17:15.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙虽然是数码兽的外表
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.50,0:17:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实是黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.00,0:17:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谜底解开了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.83,0:17:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上次闪电球兽出现的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.50,0:17:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还在奇怪为什么黑暗之塔会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.33,0:17:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来那是黑暗之塔变的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.75,0:17:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.50,0:17:43.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以那次他才会杀死敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.00,0:17:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.58,0:17:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都误会他了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.00,0:17:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连我也误会他了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不是以前的他了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.58,0:17:53.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是暴龙改造者了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.83,0:17:55.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在他 是伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.00,0:18:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊？奇怪...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.25,0:18:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.75,0:18:05.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道是怎么回事...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.00,0:18:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.33,0:18:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.08,0:18:45.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.25,0:18:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有千里眼般的好眼力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.25,0:18:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以发现远处的敌人的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.25,0:18:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨鸟型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.50,0:18:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「碎裂角」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.50,0:18:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.08,0:18:58.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙的真身是黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.08,0:19:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.58,0:19:01.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.50,0:19:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了这样我就不会留手了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.25,0:19:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲击镭射
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.00,0:19:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,准备了 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.50,0:19:25.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺丁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.50,0:19:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我制住他了 亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.50,0:19:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,碎裂角
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.83,0:19:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.33,0:19:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.33,0:19:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想辩解 以前的事真的非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.00,0:20:03.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 你知道那个女人到底是谁吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.50,0:20:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.50,0:20:07.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我只知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.83,0:20:10.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他可以将黑暗之塔变成数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.08,0:20:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要她一靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.58,0:20:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔就会恢复以前的功能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.00,0:20:17.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你明明知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.75,0:20:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么却不告诉我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.75,0:20:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.83,0:20:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们要自己收拾残局啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.25,0:20:26.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就因为这样才更让人不爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.75,0:20:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我愿意负起所有的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.00,0:20:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才不能成为伙伴吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.25,0:20:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.25,0:20:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂...一乘寺...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.83,0:21:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我期待你能成为伙伴的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.08,0:21:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.83,0:21:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等片刻让我看看你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,完全和昨天不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看 让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至侧影也像是大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,等待着你 等待着你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,即使是分别也能用语言理解的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,倘若在这世上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,万事皆无可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧！和煦的空气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,现在！想要深呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,无法自拔 难以抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,希望打开这世上的门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明天一定会吹着我的风
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,将你的懦弱猛烈般化为乌有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,这华丽灿烂的人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.81,0:21:19.85,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと待ってみて誰だって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.67,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,昨日とまるでちがう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.62,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 見て 見て
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.46,0:21:28.56,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,横顔のシルエットも大人さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.81,0:21:30.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと 君 君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:34.53,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,言いわけを したい気持ちもわかる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.75,0:21:38.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だって世の中 これじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.61,0:21:40.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,まるで なってないじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:46.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,だねっ！気持ちいい空気を
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.98,0:21:49.69,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,今っ！吸いたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.77,0:21:52.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがない しょうがない
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.91,0:21:58.23,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:22:04.57,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中のドア 開けておいて欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.73,0:22:10.04,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,アシタハアタシノカゼガフクカラネ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.42,0:22:19.25,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,君の その弱虫を モウレツに 吹き飛ばすよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:29.58,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ゴージャスな人生を！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.58,0:22:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始暴走的黑暗能量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.49,0:22:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迫近的大爆炸的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.24,0:22:43.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打算亲自处理自己留下的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.99,0:22:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而一个人挺身而出的小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.83,0:22:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要和小贤一起战斗的大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.08,0:22:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两个人的想法一致的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX和飞虫兽也合为一体了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.74,0:22:54.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.99,0:22:57.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「合体进化 现在、两心合一」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,150)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:04.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(380,390)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}现在、两心合一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.33,0:23:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
