[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.16,0:01:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石一块块的被破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.36,0:01:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织因阿岳对黑暗那强烈憎恶而慌张不已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.48,0:01:43.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是在听了阿和的话后 伊织受到启发
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.32,0:01:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.88,0:01:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为坚定阻止他的伊织的话语被扰乱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.76,0:01:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了摆脱这一切 他击碎了圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.44,0:01:53.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并飞向了远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.40,0:02:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仅存的圣石只有一颗了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.28,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}钢铁天使 古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.88,0:02:31.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是从一乘寺那里发来的邮件哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.12,0:02:33.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说他会稍微迟到一会
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:02:35.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我们先过去 在那里会合
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.20,0:02:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.44,0:02:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.28,0:02:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很快就回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.16,0:02:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.36,0:02:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好慢哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.84,0:02:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好慢啊 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.44,0:02:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今天是打扫教师办公室的值日生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.52,0:02:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后一块圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.92,0:02:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和打扫老师办公室相比
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.56,0:02:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底哪个比较重要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.80,0:02:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是那个问题吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.52,0:02:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.32,0:03:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.24,0:03:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.96,0:03:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.12,0:03:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗龙卷风
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.88,0:03:43.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人陶醉的破坏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.12,0:03:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.04,0:03:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会迷上黑暗战斗暴龙兽了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.20,0:03:52.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别说这种蠢话！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.96,0:03:56.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.40,0:04:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.24,0:04:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该就在附近了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.52,0:04:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底在哪里呢 圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.04,0:04:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果圣石真的在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.04,0:04:14.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也无法幸免啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.44,0:04:16.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽！木乃伊兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.80,0:04:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽 亲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.00,0:04:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.96,0:04:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.88,0:04:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到了这里应该就安全了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.72,0:05:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是被中国菜的味道吸引来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.76,0:05:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是数码世界的唐人街啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.92,0:05:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.60,0:05:26.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情不管是谁看了都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.48,0:05:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这种多余的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.48,0:05:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要动不动就打我啊 会打笨的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.24,0:05:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.28,0:05:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是中国菜的香味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.68,0:05:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽也闻闻看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.36,0:05:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽 一起去吃拉面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是 就算是为了和被选召的孩子们战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.16,0:05:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不能空着肚子上战场啊 要储备力气
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.20,0:05:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.76,0:06:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叉烧面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.56,0:06:14.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴古兽  又被称为吃梦动物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.32,0:06:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外形很像貘一样的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.20,0:06:17.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招和蛋蛋兽一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.88,0:06:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「恶梦症候群」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.60,0:06:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混沌面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.64,0:06:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就要这个好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.56,0:06:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.04,0:06:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.04,0:06:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然听说黑暗战斗暴龙兽就在附近 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.20,0:06:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺没问题吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.08,0:06:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽也和他在一起一定没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.92,0:06:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.08,0:06:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 要喝吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.32,0:06:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢 这个水真的很好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.88,0:06:51.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我家店里的推销产品哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.48,0:06:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,含有丰富矿物质 非常有利于健康哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.48,0:06:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次去阿伊商店务必购买此商品
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.92,0:06:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.24,0:07:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们真卖力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.96,0:07:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自从他们合体进化了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.92,0:07:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关系变得越来越好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我们总有一天也能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.72,0:07:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.36,0:07:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽和穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.08,0:07:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎已经有合体进化的预兆了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.68,0:07:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达穿山
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.32,0:07:19.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.80,0:07:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达穿山
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.48,0:07:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.08,0:07:28.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有没有闻到一股很香的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.76,0:07:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的 是好喝的中国汤的香味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.60,0:07:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.28,0:07:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.52,0:07:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易来到数码世界的唐人街
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.56,0:07:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就一起去吃中国菜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.44,0:07:48.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.84,0:07:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么定了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.76,0:07:56.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃什么呢 我嘛 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.36,0:08:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你怎么了 有什么不对劲的地方吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.76,0:08:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和黑暗战斗暴龙兽战斗之前居然去吃中国菜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.64,0:08:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家太不严肃了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.48,0:08:11.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是...我只是觉得愤怒而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.56,0:08:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...我肚子也饿了...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.32,0:08:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.88,0:08:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许正是因为我这份过于认真的紧张感
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.16,0:08:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才让我无法和阿岳一起合体进化吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.28,0:08:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个拉面真是超级好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.96,0:08:34.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是这汤　堪称极品
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.32,0:08:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,店员
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.20,0:08:38.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,茶点面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.55,0:08:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们的汤是怎么做的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.55,0:08:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点心面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.48,0:08:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,汤汁是什么做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.20,0:08:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,炸酱面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.12,0:08:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和你没法沟通
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.00,0:08:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把你们管事的叫来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.76,0:08:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,热汤面？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.52,0:08:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是本店主厨 蛋蛋兽是也
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.04,0:09:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么好喝的汤是用什么做出来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个可不能外传
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.56,0:09:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.84,0:09:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是商业机密！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.16,0:09:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把我们当成什么人了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.68,0:09:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.84,0:09:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恩？蛋蛋兽 是你在经营中华料理店嘛？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.92,0:09:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,经营西餐馆的是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.80,0:09:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我从他那里听说过你们的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是被选召的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.72,0:09:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 打招呼就打到这里为止
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.52,0:10:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.64,0:10:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.80,0:10:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.24,0:10:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.40,0:10:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.36,0:11:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.96,0:11:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.20,0:11:24.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.84,0:11:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.68,0:11:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.56,0:11:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.56,0:11:54.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-冲击...  \N-女皇...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.24,0:11:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,硫酸烟雾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.56,0:12:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-万吨... \N-X光...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.92,0:12:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.80,0:12:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是飞虫兽不在这里...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.44,0:12:33.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.44,0:12:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺这家伙在干什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.32,0:12:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 就算只有我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.52,0:12:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.32,0:12:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.36,0:12:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.00,0:13:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.88,0:13:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.28,0:13:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.24,0:13:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.36,0:13:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.56,0:13:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽和迪路兽肯定是因为肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.48,0:13:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有可以合体进化的力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.68,0:13:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.28,0:13:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.36,0:13:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.84,0:13:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.72,0:13:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那汤到底是用什么做的啊 告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.36,0:13:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.60,0:13:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.48,0:13:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.52,0:13:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让亚基利兽和木乃伊兽逃掉了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.44,0:13:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是那帮家伙...去追吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.32,0:13:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.68,0:14:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们真正的敌人不是亚基利兽和木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.08,0:14:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打败黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.32,0:14:10.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须要有足够的能量用以进行合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.48,0:14:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃拉面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.88,0:14:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.16,0:14:21.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就按照伊织所说的去做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.76,0:14:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉面 拉面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.44,0:14:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是蛋蛋兽他们已经逃走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.32,0:14:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们自己动手做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做吧 做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.44,0:14:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把汤加热...我来煮面...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.32,0:14:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来切洋葱...多放点叉烧...还有面...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.32,0:14:49.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.68,0:14:56.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想加速 可是加速器负荷太大 无法启动了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.32,0:14:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.84,0:15:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去引擎会烧起来的！水...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.12,0:15:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.80,0:15:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽...木乃伊兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.96,0:15:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽...啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.16,0:15:15.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别出声
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.48,0:15:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要吓我啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.88,0:15:28.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以听见了...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.76,0:15:30.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.76,0:15:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水滴的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.32,0:15:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.04,0:15:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.64,0:15:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.96,0:15:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这股好闻的香味...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.60,0:16:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面写着「中华料理汤池」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.12,0:16:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个好吃的汤...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:07.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家料理店用来做拉面的汤汁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.56,0:16:09.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是从这里取的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.96,0:16:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻婆面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.36,0:16:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不准喝神圣的中华料理汤池的汤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.96,0:16:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个原来躲在这种地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.84,0:16:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看那个！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.00,0:16:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,禁止擅自喝中华料理汤池的汤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.96,0:16:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擅自喝的话 会受到惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.84,0:16:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样子写只会让人更加想去喝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.84,0:16:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先要惩罚你们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.96,0:16:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.48,0:17:04.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.72,0:17:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.36,0:17:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做的真好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.12,0:17:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这个汤料好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.36,0:17:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的手艺也很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.24,0:17:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 真的非常好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.96,0:17:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.96,0:17:50.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.68,0:17:58.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定我们可以合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.40,0:18:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有这个预感
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.32,0:18:05.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.44,0:18:06.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.84,0:18:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想不到居然会在这种地方发现圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.92,0:18:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽 救命！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.76,0:18:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.68,0:18:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.60,0:18:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好重！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.56,0:18:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后一块圣石...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.68,0:18:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.04,0:18:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要破坏它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.48,0:18:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.88,0:18:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会保护好最后一块圣石的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.16,0:18:53.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底要吃几次苦头才会罢手？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.40,0:18:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是难缠的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.48,0:18:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽 干掉他们！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.28,0:19:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也给我快点消失！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.36,0:19:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我们合体进化的时刻终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.12,0:19:09.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.92,0:19:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽 这真是让人期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:13.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽 一起加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.92,0:19:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.96,0:19:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.28,0:19:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.24,0:19:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.40,0:19:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.64,0:19:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.84,0:19:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.64,0:19:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.48,0:19:46.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.44,0:19:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.36,0:19:53.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.96,0:19:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.96,0:20:06.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.48,0:20:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.84,0:20:18.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.32,0:20:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.60,0:20:24.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿出自信来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.16,0:20:25.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.08,0:20:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.92,0:20:34.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.96,0:20:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.48,0:20:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.28,0:20:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽？成功啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.08,0:21:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的战斗 现在才刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.52,0:22:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽的力量恰巧克制黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.64,0:22:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 他的脚步却不曾停下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.00,0:22:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们下定决心保护好圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.00,0:22:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是和天空所相连的耀眼光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.96,0:22:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从天空的彼岸召唤出了青龙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.16,0:22:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.52,0:22:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「巨大究极体 青龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.62,0:23:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}巨大究极体 青龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.12,0:23:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
