[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.16,0:01:37.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.00,0:01:40.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳的巴达兽和伊织的穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.44,0:01:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化成了古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.76,0:01:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同机甲龙兽以及人面战鹰兽一起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.28,0:01:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三只合成体一起对抗黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,340)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}巨大究极体 青龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.44,0:02:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.24,0:02:12.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.04,0:02:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿出自信来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.48,0:02:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.40,0:02:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.36,0:02:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.12,0:02:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.60,0:02:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.56,0:02:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.76,0:02:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽和天使兽合体进化而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.72,0:02:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然变异型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.24,0:02:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得意技是「古神魂」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.64,0:02:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「荒御魂」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.44,0:02:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.28,0:02:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于可以和机甲龙兽以及人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.36,0:02:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起并肩作战了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.76,0:02:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.72,0:02:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了 古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.00,0:02:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.64,0:03:05.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我从那里...让开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.08,0:03:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.00,0:03:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.40,0:03:10.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗从现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.56,0:03:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这么做没有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.72,0:03:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 强行驱散你们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.56,0:03:22.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要被干掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.24,0:03:23.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.12,0:03:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.36,0:03:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.72,0:03:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.84,0:03:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸收了黑暗战斗暴龙兽的黑盖亚能量炮！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.68,0:03:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.96,0:03:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒御魂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.32,0:03:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.80,0:03:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都不会让你破坏圣石的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.96,0:03:55.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.92,0:03:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音速二重击
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.44,0:04:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.40,0:04:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.60,0:04:17.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么就算屡战屡败仍然不断挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.32,0:04:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神魂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.72,0:04:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是为了保护圣石?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.68,0:04:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是为了保护这个数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.36,0:04:32.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.32,0:04:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们可以没有任何迷茫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.96,0:04:37.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如此直接的行动呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.72,0:04:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.16,0:04:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.92,0:04:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.52,0:04:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这帮家伙身上有什么东西是我缺少的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.56,0:04:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.88,0:04:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 为什么可以那样生存
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.20,0:05:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我 我是为何而生的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.44,0:05:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我和你们完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果无法了解真相
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.00,0:05:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使毁灭这个世界我也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.12,0:05:16.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.32,0:05:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他很悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.28,0:05:20.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无尽的悲伤...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.72,0:05:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要去破坏圣石...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.52,0:05:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,答案肯定就在那里！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.40,0:05:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.00,0:05:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.04,0:05:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 无法阻止他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.80,0:05:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果圣石被破坏了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.52,0:05:43.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个数码世界就...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.52,0:05:45.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.24,0:05:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们生活的现实世界也会被...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.28,0:05:49.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.28,0:05:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就想办法移动它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.32,0:05:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.84,0:05:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁机甲龙兽阻止黑暗战斗暴龙兽时
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.52,0:05:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们把圣石搬到其他地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.32,0:06:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情怎么可能做得到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.68,0:06:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不试试怎么知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.28,0:06:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 先试了再说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.28,0:06:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我们不能就那样袖手旁观
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.40,0:06:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情 你们根本就做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.56,0:06:13.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.16,0:06:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 蜘蛛女
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.72,0:06:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会让你的计划得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.08,0:06:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么狂妄的语气说话没关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.60,0:06:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.72,0:06:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要结果你们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.28,0:06:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,双重恶梦症候群
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.40,0:06:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玷污神圣的中华之汤泉的人 绝对无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.20,0:06:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.48,0:06:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们 圣石就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.16,0:06:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.88,0:06:49.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们 蛋蛋兽 巴古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.52,0:06:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.16,0:06:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 应该怎么做...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.12,0:06:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.00,0:07:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把D3对着它试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.00,0:07:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那阵光是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.24,0:07:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从四面八方集合过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.96,0:07:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.28,0:07:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢着 这到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.96,0:07:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这样问 我也不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.44,0:08:09.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.20,0:08:11.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.00,0:08:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.68,0:08:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第四颗圣石被击碎的时候看见的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.20,0:08:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然有如此巨大的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.08,0:08:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽在找的就是他？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.56,0:08:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.52,0:08:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等待与你相遇的这一天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.79,0:08:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有被诅咒的黑暗灵魂的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.60,0:08:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「诅咒的黑暗灵魂」？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.00,0:08:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.40,0:08:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.44,0:08:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要破坏圣石呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.80,0:08:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了和你战斗才到这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.24,0:08:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你比我到现在见到过的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.68,0:08:57.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,任何数码兽都要强大 不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.60,0:09:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是什么人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.16,0:09:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道 也没必要知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.48,0:09:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吾名为青龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,青龙兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.52,0:09:10.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吾乃这个世界的东方护法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.08,0:09:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光与希望之魂的拥有者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.56,0:09:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你破坏了圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.04,0:09:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界的平衡已经被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.68,0:09:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你了解过自己所做的事的后果吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.60,0:09:23.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情对我来说无关紧要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.20,0:09:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我战斗吧 青龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.00,0:09:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.44,0:09:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你破坏圣石只是为了和我交战吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.88,0:09:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个黑暗的存在本身封印了我的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.48,0:09:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时也破坏了这个世界的平衡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.12,0:09:41.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说「存在本身」？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.44,0:09:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还没有发现吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.68,0:09:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,树立在东方的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.08,0:09:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是封印住我的力量的真凶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.92,0:09:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为聚集一百座黑暗之塔而诞生的你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.72,0:09:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,则是不折不扣的黑暗存在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.80,0:09:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.00,0:09:58.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔能够封印力量？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.12,0:10:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果真是那样 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.84,0:10:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.36,0:10:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿帮了 没办法啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.40,0:10:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽我所能的多建一些黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.80,0:10:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏这个世界的平衡扰乱世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.68,0:10:15.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.56,0:10:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此才将我变成暴龙改造者加以利用的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.92,0:10:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是为了建成黑暗之塔！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.80,0:10:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.96,0:10:25.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易利用你建了那么多黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.28,0:10:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你哪根筋搭错了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.88,0:10:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然和被选召的孩子们一起破坏黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.16,0:10:34.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才会制造出你来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.56,0:10:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然纠结什么「生存的意义」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.44,0:10:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是愚蠢之极
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.24,0:10:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔制造出的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.60,0:10:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不需要所谓的意识和灵魂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.20,0:10:47.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命 我...我没有恶意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.84,0:10:49.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也没有办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.04,0:10:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是你与生俱来的宿命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.68,0:10:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「宿命」？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.28,0:10:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我又为什么会来这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.48,0:10:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些你也要归罪与宿命吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.40,0:10:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.56,0:11:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个问题 没有人可以给你答案
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.76,0:11:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.00,0:11:04.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「我自己」？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.52,0:11:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管你得出了什么样的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.96,0:11:11.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你都有你存在的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.16,0:11:15.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我的存在也是有意义的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.12,0:11:16.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.56,0:11:21.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是只能靠你自己来寻找这个意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:41.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.08,0:11:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我能够传达给你的也只有这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.76,0:11:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.24,0:11:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够遇见你真的很走运
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.72,0:11:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你让我了解到我的存在也是有意义的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.72,0:12:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽管这个结果不是我想要的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.96,0:12:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.36,0:12:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里也不是的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.68,0:12:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「哪里也不是的地方」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.80,0:12:18.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.08,0:12:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要走了 木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.36,0:12:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.28,0:12:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然是去阻止他了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.16,0:12:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.84,0:12:26.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们走着瞧 我不会善罢甘休的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.68,0:12:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厚脸皮 手下败将还嘴硬
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.36,0:12:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.40,0:12:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.40,0:12:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了这个世界的安定而存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.72,0:12:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,四只究级体数码兽其中一只
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.80,0:12:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我守护着东方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.52,0:12:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听着很像京都耶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.04,0:12:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.56,0:13:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的 我想或许曾经提起过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.56,0:13:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听说京都东西南北有四只圣兽在守护
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.64,0:13:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.60,0:13:11.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们这个世界和你们的世界有很多相似的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.20,0:13:14.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们经过了长期的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.24,0:13:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果被黑暗四天王分别的封印了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.96,0:13:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此时
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.68,0:13:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八个被选召的孩子中有七个来到了这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.84,0:13:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着 在那七个孩子第一次回去之后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.20,0:13:30.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗四天王
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.24,0:13:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对这个世界进行了一次分解和再统一
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.56,0:13:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指黑暗龙卷山吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.60,0:13:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八个孩子和八只数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.68,0:13:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合力打倒了黑暗四天王
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.84,0:13:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是只有那些还无法解开我们的封印
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.20,0:13:44.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.80,0:13:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都被用来恢复这个世界的原貌了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.16,0:13:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要解开我们的封印
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.32,0:13:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便需要借助孩子们徽章的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.56,0:13:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也导致了以后数码兽的完全体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.32,0:14:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须借用我们的力量帮忙才行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.72,0:14:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是除非必要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.44,0:14:04.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,否则无法完全体进化的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.16,0:14:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是之前光子郎解释过的那件事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.72,0:14:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来就是指青龙兽的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.16,0:14:15.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后这个世界开始建立黑暗力量的塔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.52,0:14:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在因为那股黑暗力量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.92,0:14:19.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,导致数码兽们都无法进化的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.44,0:14:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祈望世界平衡的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.92,0:14:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就会自动启用古代的进化力量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.44,0:14:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.72,0:14:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,几个拥有古代力量的数码兽陷入长眠
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了与黑暗力量对抗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.96,0:14:38.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,制造了三个新的神圣计划
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.88,0:14:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且被送到了新的孩子们手中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:44.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是在说我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.20,0:14:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是说大辅和我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.04,0:14:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.84,0:14:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 意料之外的事情发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.16,0:14:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们拥有保存装甲数码蛋的容器
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.40,0:14:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此装甲数码蛋不止一个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:02.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三个数码兽也可以用别的装甲数码蛋进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.32,0:15:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 友情 纯真以及诚实的装甲数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.76,0:15:10.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都在需要的时候出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.40,0:15:12.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.44,0:15:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个力量对于让被黑暗沾染的存在恢复原样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.28,0:15:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在黑暗的包围下的温柔徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.36,0:15:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仅限一次的变为奇迹装甲数码蛋而言也是必要的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.80,0:15:32.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...多么悲伤的声音啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.64,0:15:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,背负着不幸命运而出生的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.88,0:15:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愿你在漫长的岁月中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.16,0:15:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够找到你所追寻的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.48,0:15:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.24,0:15:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,青龙兽便可取回原本的力量了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.08,0:15:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,短时间内是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.12,0:15:53.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界的平衡已经崩溃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.56,0:15:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在粉碎了的圣石所在地
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.28,0:15:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经埋下了光明的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.76,0:16:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「光明的种子」？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.04,0:16:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果种子可以平安的生长的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.08,0:16:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不久就可以发挥和圣石一样的作用了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.68,0:16:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.08,0:16:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以渐渐的恢复平衡了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.40,0:16:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也要加油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.68,0:16:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.92,0:16:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.64,0:16:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 有什么话就说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.24,0:16:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不把那个名为「黑暗」的东西消灭掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.80,0:16:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它便会不断吸取周围的一切从而越变越大
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.96,0:16:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会不会再次诞生出像黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:40.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样悲哀的生物呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.80,0:16:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 你是说...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.48,0:16:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺也在隐喻自己的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.20,0:16:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为自己被黑暗的力量吸引
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.64,0:16:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从而制造出了基米拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.08,0:16:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我并不这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.64,0:17:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗」的确是个恐怖的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.44,0:17:04.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以完全摆脱会让人心安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.68,0:17:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这注定是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.80,0:17:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「不可能」？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.88,0:17:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有光明的地方就一定会存在黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.72,0:17:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明越强 黑暗越盛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.52,0:17:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.28,0:17:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我认为无论身处怎样的黑暗之中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.64,0:17:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要不迷失心中的光芒便不会有事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.68,0:17:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不迷失心中的光芒...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.16,0:17:29.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 那就是希望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.96,0:17:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论身处什么样的黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.92,0:17:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不能迷失心中的光明
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.32,0:17:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这正是希望徽章的真义啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.24,0:17:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,心中的光明？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.84,0:17:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒黑暗四天王并解除我的封印的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.88,0:17:47.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是你们两位的徽章 光明与希望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.28,0:17:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我和阿岳的徽章啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.68,0:17:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当这个世界孕育出黑暗的神圣计划时
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.24,0:17:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有古代力量的只有三只数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.64,0:18:04.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而一起来的旧徽章拥有者的两只数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.76,0:18:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也可以适用古代力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.16,0:18:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时两人的神圣计划意外的改变了形状
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.40,0:18:14.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便是为了适应古代的进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.36,0:18:17.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是天马兽和尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.28,0:18:21.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这两个徽章 光明与希望
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.36,0:18:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不同于其他的徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.68,0:18:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇气 爱心 知识
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.36,0:18:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这些孩子们内心所拥有的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.08,0:18:36.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明  赋予了这个世界生命之光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.36,0:18:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望象征无论身处何种黑暗都永保光明
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.04,0:18:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当大家的心合为一体时便产生力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.36,0:18:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从而使得光明绽放出更强烈的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.40,0:18:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且这束光芒也促进了进化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.60,0:19:03.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.92,0:19:05.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为黑暗战斗暴龙兽离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.92,0:19:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的力量也渐渐会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.88,0:19:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这并不代表眼前的威胁已经解除
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.36,0:19:14.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.96,0:19:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,企图封印我的邪恶意识体并未消失
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.48,0:19:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指亚基利兽他们的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.56,0:19:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 这并不是他们能够想到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.12,0:19:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是更为强大且被憎恨支配的邪恶意志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.80,0:19:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是指暗中操控着亚基利兽他们的人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.64,0:19:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个邪恶意志把我...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.16,0:19:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们的使命还没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.44,0:19:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能松懈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.12,0:19:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 我们会注意 不会掉以轻心的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.96,0:19:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么告辞了 虽然不知日后能否再会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.80,0:19:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.00,0:19:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.56,0:20:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,托大家的福 又可平安的做生意了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.72,0:20:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叉烧面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.44,0:20:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,区区薄礼 不成敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.52,0:20:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.60,0:20:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢着 大辅 我正打算吃那个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.36,0:20:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一样的想法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.48,0:20:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.80,0:20:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.24,0:20:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.56,0:20:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.80,0:20:25.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我 给我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.92,0:20:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.20,0:20:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 和大家一起吃真的好香哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.32,0:20:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.48,0:20:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说我要那些...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.76,0:20:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不给...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.12,0:20:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.28,0:20:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,中国包子真好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.84,0:20:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 你比我多吃了一个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.48,0:20:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还在数吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.96,0:20:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因食物而生的怨恨可是非常可怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.44,0:20:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.36,0:21:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才怎么好像看见了黑暗之塔...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.32,0:21:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 肯定是肉包子吃多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.76,0:21:04.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是错觉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.92,0:21:08.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,错觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.52,0:22:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,镇上正在过圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.28,0:22:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一和亚古兽他们也久违的聚在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.00,0:22:44.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们正在期待可以享受短暂的和平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.64,0:22:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 光丘却出现了黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.44,0:22:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽又来作乱了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.12,0:22:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们究竟能不能够保护御台场呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.12,0:22:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.40,0:22:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「圣诞夜 数码兽大集合！」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.20,0:22:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,160)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}圣诞夜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.20,0:22:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(380,360)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}数码兽大集合！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.92,0:23:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
