[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽将第二颗圣石也破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.80,0:01:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.68,0:01:43.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出现在京都做毕业旅行的小京面前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.40,0:01:51.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京借着D3装甲暴龙机打开大门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.28,0:01:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将数码兽送了回去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.36,0:01:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.48,0:01:58.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们却处于数码世界\N平衡濒临崩溃的忧心之中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.49,0:02:10.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}圣石保卫战
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.72,0:02:14.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要破坏那颗石头呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.32,0:02:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 是那颗石头自己在呼唤我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.00,0:02:25.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在只剩下五颗圣石了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.64,0:02:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽好像很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.32,0:02:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样子我就高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.92,0:02:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可不可以看前面好好开车
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.88,0:02:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京带回来的礼物好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.16,0:02:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都的生八桥饼好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.64,0:02:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个饼是生的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.08,0:02:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是全部吃光了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:49.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是想不到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.40,0:02:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连在京都都会见到黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.44,0:02:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他会去京都呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.08,0:02:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,素娜的爸爸告诉我说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.40,0:03:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都这块土地有四种神圣的动物在保护
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.92,0:03:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且是现实世界距离其他世界最近的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.56,0:03:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以那里很容易出现妖魔鬼怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:09.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此京都设有鬼门
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.44,0:03:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且京都的四方都建了神社或寺庙来保护
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.68,0:03:14.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京好厉害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.88,0:03:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕业旅行还能学到这么多的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.32,0:03:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽居然可以出现在现实世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.00,0:03:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可见数码世界的歪斜扭曲有多么的严重
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.52,0:03:26.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.72,0:03:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你们所说的那个世界的歪斜扭曲的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.40,0:03:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我听不太懂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.40,0:03:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个意思是...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.92,0:03:34.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个代表数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.92,0:03:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后这个代表现实世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.96,0:03:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一旦发生歪斜扭曲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.64,0:03:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就表示世界平衡崩溃了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.60,0:03:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是彼此的世界便会发生错乱的现象
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.80,0:03:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光果然不简单
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.92,0:03:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是迪路兽教我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.00,0:03:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个海又是另外一个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.04,0:03:56.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不只是这样而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.76,0:04:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为一定还有其他我们所不知道的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.56,0:04:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.08,0:04:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像彩虹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.32,0:04:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是如果失去平衡的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.08,0:04:12.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.88,0:04:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后可能所有的世界都会陷入黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.88,0:04:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包括现实世界还有数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.51,0:04:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是闹着玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.24,0:04:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了以防万一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.48,0:04:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要保护好圣石才行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.16,0:04:29.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉学长 你来的正是时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.96,0:04:32.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也买了份礼物要送给学长哦 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.08,0:04:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看我给你们带了些什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.12,0:04:36.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,D3暴龙机跟DT暴龙机借我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.64,0:04:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从DT暴龙机上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.92,0:04:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以直接显示世界的周期变化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.20,0:04:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎 你真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.04,0:04:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以知道黑暗战斗暴龙兽的位置了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.84,0:04:53.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为你们的后援
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.80,0:04:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是尽全力帮忙而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.48,0:04:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,学长 真是太感谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.60,0:04:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 那我们出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.60,0:05:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.64,0:05:05.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 用不着通知一乘寺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.24,0:05:07.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大辅 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.72,0:05:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.52,0:05:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.04,0:05:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.32,0:05:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.44,0:05:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.76,0:05:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.36,0:05:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.88,0:05:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像已经到这附近了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.36,0:05:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.60,0:05:53.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.44,0:06:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.76,0:06:11.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第三个也变成粉末了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.40,0:06:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.92,0:06:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可以感受到一股强大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.84,0:06:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.24,0:06:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那个家伙吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.76,0:06:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的对手就是他吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.24,0:06:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个东西到底是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.32,0:06:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.88,0:06:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 破坏那块石头之后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.32,0:06:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,引起的骚乱好像比我们想的还要大是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.72,0:06:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.84,0:07:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.40,0:07:08.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我们来晚一步
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.04,0:07:10.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 这么一来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.96,0:07:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的也会被黑暗战斗暴龙兽破坏的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.52,0:07:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让他得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.40,0:07:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诞生于黑暗之塔的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.32,0:07:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然凭着黑暗的力量扭曲数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.16,0:07:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不允许这样的事情发生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.76,0:07:26.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前也发生过类似的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.24,0:07:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我们一定要想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.12,0:07:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比黑暗战斗暴龙兽先找到那些圣石才行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.64,0:07:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去问问附近的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.04,0:07:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看会在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.12,0:07:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直非常冷静的阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.36,0:07:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如此激进的阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.00,0:07:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底哪个才是真正的他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.80,0:07:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.12,0:07:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要跟他决一死战
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.88,0:08:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.36,0:08:05.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天还要继续加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.44,0:08:11.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你不去剑道班吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.56,0:08:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去的 那我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.64,0:08:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天不是没有剑道课吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.00,0:08:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.36,0:08:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅和一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.36,0:08:29.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京和小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.96,0:08:33.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定某天和我合体进化的就是阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.15,0:08:37.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人家说好酒沉瓮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.76,0:08:38.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.64,0:08:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我对阿岳根本一点都不了解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.64,0:08:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 怎么才能跟他合体进化呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.56,0:08:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.04,0:08:49.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要你拿出和剑道一样的精神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.64,0:08:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就一定没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.08,0:08:53.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你也教我剑道好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.72,0:08:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我也有超人一样的集中力
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.56,0:09:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,集中 集中 精神统一
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.00,0:09:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.72,0:09:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.12,0:09:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.40,0:09:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.24,0:10:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽们会不会知道圣石的所在地呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.36,0:10:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家分头去问问看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.60,0:10:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.36,0:10:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 我们也去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.16,0:10:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加布兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.72,0:10:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 圣石就在这座山那边的山谷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.72,0:10:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你专程来这里通知我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.08,0:10:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我接到甲虫兽的指令
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.16,0:10:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一代正好是我负责保护的区域
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.84,0:10:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:29.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.60,0:10:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽告诉我...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.32,0:10:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽好像有心的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.88,0:10:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有心？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.92,0:10:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道他不是黑暗之塔变的？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.64,0:10:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他好像正在为此烦恼不已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.28,0:10:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不明白为什么他没有生命却有一颗心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.52,0:10:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.52,0:10:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.24,0:10:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要跟我们作对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.88,0:10:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又为什么要破坏圣石呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.24,0:10:55.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.00,0:10:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.92,0:10:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有心的数码兽是无法打倒的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.84,0:11:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的事...我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.52,0:11:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.80,0:11:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我们一定要打倒黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.12,0:11:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,某则的话 黑暗的势力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.52,0:11:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会变的比现在更可怕更强大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.80,0:11:33.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们要小心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.52,0:11:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 加布兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.48,0:11:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.16,0:11:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.08,0:11:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你本可以坐天马兽跟大家一起走的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.16,0:11:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.36,0:11:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走了 加布兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.04,0:11:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要小心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.60,0:11:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.20,0:11:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.04,0:12:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我忘了你接受过剑道训练了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.76,0:12:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对我多加照顾的阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.68,0:12:12.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要打倒拥有心的黑暗战斗暴龙兽的阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.48,0:12:16.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他...是不是拥有双重人格呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.08,0:12:24.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.32,0:12:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次总算是我们先到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.00,0:12:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.84,0:12:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.96,0:12:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化准备
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.48,0:12:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.44,0:12:59.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.92,0:13:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.24,0:13:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.40,0:13:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 可以了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.68,0:13:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了小京
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.52,0:13:24.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.68,0:13:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.04,0:13:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.48,0:13:35.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.40,0:13:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.88,0:13:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别挡路 闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.20,0:13:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.24,0:14:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让你继续破坏圣石了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.84,0:14:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X刺钉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.60,0:14:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会看着你破坏数码世界的平衡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.24,0:14:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音速二重击
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.64,0:14:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.72,0:14:17.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.68,0:14:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们一定要这样阻扰我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.64,0:14:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.32,0:14:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们用不着你来出手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.36,0:14:34.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这几个家伙是我们的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.80,0:14:52.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.76,0:14:54.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易比他们先找到...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.92,0:14:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:14:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们休想
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.76,0:15:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在可没功夫陪你玩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.16,0:15:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.28,0:15:24.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽 全力攻击吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.00,0:15:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这样下去 圣石又要被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.68,0:15:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳...阿岳...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.40,0:15:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.80,0:15:49.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.96,0:15:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.64,0:15:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.68,0:16:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.36,0:16:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.56,0:16:15.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.12,0:16:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐龙克星
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.32,0:16:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.72,0:16:30.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真的有心吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.92,0:16:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.08,0:16:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本就不可能合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.76,0:16:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.48,0:16:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.20,0:16:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖 憎恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.24,0:16:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战栗 黑暗！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.84,0:16:58.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么允许通过这种手段改变世界！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.80,0:17:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至企图控制这个世界！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.64,0:17:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.96,0:17:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 别发呆了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.07,0:17:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 我感觉到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.20,0:17:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是永远都无法打倒的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.92,0:17:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体...不
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.16,0:17:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.48,0:17:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.60,0:17:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣天使兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.24,0:17:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变成完全体了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.40,0:18:08.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.60,0:18:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 去吧 神圣天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.88,0:18:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉到黑暗的意识了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.76,0:18:24.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以再留在数码世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.76,0:18:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.96,0:18:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的存在岂是你所能否定的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.28,0:18:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我听说你有一颗心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.56,0:18:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以跟那些黑暗之塔的数码兽不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.80,0:18:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.56,0:18:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你生来只是为了让黑暗势力利用的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.96,0:18:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就非打倒你不可
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.80,0:18:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天国之门
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.76,0:18:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让黑暗回归于黑暗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.92,0:19:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会离开数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:12.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我一定要跟他决一死战！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.24,0:19:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.36,0:19:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就击碎了圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.64,0:19:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.84,0:19:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果圣石又...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.16,0:19:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.28,0:19:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.40,0:19:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.32,0:19:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他好像很痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.96,0:20:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙马上就要现身了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.52,0:20:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.68,0:20:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.12,0:20:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 干嘛说的那么勉强
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.32,0:20:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.00,0:20:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.32,0:20:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.20,0:20:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.88,0:20:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳为什么那么痛恨黑暗的力量呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.52,0:20:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我所痛恨并不是黑暗能量的本身
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.36,0:20:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 快点过来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.28,0:20:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可不可以别这么幼稚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.68,0:20:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.08,0:20:59.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.52,0:22:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后一块圣石也被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.56,0:22:42.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同大辅等人分别之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.56,0:22:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为阿和的话 伊织终于明白阿岳的心了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.92,0:22:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在有了新的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.96,0:22:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织决定站出来与黑暗战斗暴龙兽对决
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.88,0:22:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.04,0:22:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「乘胜追击！黑暗战斗暴龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.74,0:23:00.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}乘胜追击！黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.36,0:22:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
