[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.68,0:01:37.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽凭他强大的力量破坏了圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.84,0:01:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就连凭着圣石发出的光芒进化的神圣天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.64,0:01:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是黑暗战斗暴龙兽的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.72,0:01:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.36,0:02:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正准备破坏第五颗圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}乘胜追击！黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.52,0:02:30.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为凭着一招半式
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.52,0:02:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可以打败所有敌人了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.92,0:02:37.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石到底藏在什么地方？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.52,0:02:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点回答我 啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.92,0:02:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.04,0:02:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你们教给毛人兽反抗的念头吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.36,0:03:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石到底在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.44,0:03:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁会老实回答你的问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.84,0:03:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又不是傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.48,0:03:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家要小心 那个家伙来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.16,0:03:19.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.64,0:03:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你们的样子就知道藏在哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.44,0:03:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.84,0:03:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.52,0:03:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雪山居然就这样不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.32,0:03:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.16,0:03:48.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.56,0:04:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.72,0:04:06.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你终于出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.20,0:04:10.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等着吧 看我怎么收拾你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.92,0:04:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.16,0:04:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来圣石就破坏的差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.24,0:04:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就快成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.48,0:04:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙每破坏一颗圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.64,0:04:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量就往上增强一点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.84,0:04:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 别磨蹭了 快追
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.16,0:04:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我们又输了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.88,0:04:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么都打不过他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.24,0:04:45.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没时间后悔了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.64,0:04:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.76,0:04:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真的好险
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.68,0:05:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是圣石又被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.60,0:05:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易可以合体进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.88,0:05:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然一次都没赢过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.00,0:05:21.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽那混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.52,0:05:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是 怎么都赢不了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.48,0:05:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他太强了 真的太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.16,0:05:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.80,0:05:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用黑暗的力量造成他人的不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.08,0:05:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.52,0:05:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕 不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.48,0:05:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖 憎恶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.24,0:05:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战栗 黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.44,0:05:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以通过这种手段来改变世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.40,0:05:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,甚至企图控制整个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.32,0:05:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.00,0:05:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.08,0:06:05.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.00,0:06:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对了 小贤的家是在西町啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.16,0:06:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.76,0:06:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.44,0:06:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要到我家吃饭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.32,0:06:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何我都要打败黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.40,0:06:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想...你一定会有好主意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.92,0:06:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想打败黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.60,0:06:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另外...绝对不能饶恕亚基利兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.04,0:06:34.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.92,0:06:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚好明天就是星期天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.60,0:06:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如现在就去我家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.08,0:06:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 我先打个电话回家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.28,0:06:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 就这么决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.44,0:06:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 一会我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.64,0:06:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.60,0:06:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真...真的吗 小光 你要去我家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.48,0:06:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那大家吃好晚饭来我家集合吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.88,0:06:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.72,0:06:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我不能去 先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.64,0:07:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.96,0:07:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 对于黑暗力量的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.08,0:07:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么如此在意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.20,0:07:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.64,0:07:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是住同一栋大楼的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.88,0:07:10.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 待会见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.24,0:07:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好 一乘寺家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.20,0:07:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.56,0:07:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 今天朋友想请我吃晚饭 可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.88,0:07:25.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？你朋友要请你吃晚饭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.88,0:07:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能会晚点回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.56,0:07:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系 玩的开心点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.28,0:07:35.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次也可以请责问朋友到我们家来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.32,0:07:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.28,0:07:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他就是一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.92,0:07:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你们都知道那就不用再介绍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.24,0:07:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个天才少年居然是你的朋友！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.52,0:07:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.84,0:07:58.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你教我这个笨儿子读书的方法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.92,0:08:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,寿司 我们一定要订最上等的寿司
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.08,0:08:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们还是不要理我们好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.32,0:08:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,石田 有人找你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.68,0:08:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有人找我？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.84,0:08:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 暴龙改造者制造基米拉兽的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.44,0:08:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳也这么愤怒过？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.16,0:08:19.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.28,0:08:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这件事他从来都没有跟我提过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.60,0:08:27.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后现在又出现了黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.00,0:08:30.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳...痛恨利用黑暗的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.80,0:08:33.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,制造不幸生命的亚基利兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.88,0:08:34.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他恨他们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.67,0:08:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的力量和生命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.40,0:08:39.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想以前一定发生什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.91,0:08:42.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我希望可以更了解阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.84,0:08:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 的确是有过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.12,0:08:48.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我永远也忘不了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.76,0:08:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们跟第一个敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.56,0:08:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恶魔兽最后一次决战的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.12,0:08:58.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为黑暗的力量逐渐增强
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.20,0:09:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无人能敌的恶魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.28,0:09:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却被天使兽打倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.24,0:09:09.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是以自己的性命为代价获取的胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.44,0:09:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那也是巴达兽的初次进化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.64,0:09:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,初次相会之后 他们又分开了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.08,0:09:23.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳开始重新孵化数码兽的数码蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.08,0:09:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了再次见到巴达兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.28,0:09:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳之所以了解黑暗的可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.56,0:09:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和生命的可贵便是因为天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.08,0:09:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亲眼看着自己的数码兽伙伴死去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.00,0:09:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说 一乘寺和虫虫兽也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.92,0:09:48.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 阿岳和一乘寺有着相同的经历
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.88,0:09:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 他们对于利用黑暗力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.32,0:09:53.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,轻易制造生命的行为决不饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.88,0:09:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.36,0:09:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,换成是我 也无法接受奥柏兽遇到这样的下场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.16,0:10:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于伙伴数码兽的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.32,0:10:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.20,0:10:05.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这么一说 我现在终于明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.96,0:10:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在乐团练习时 突然前来打扰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.20,0:10:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.00,0:10:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳这孩子...居然还有这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.80,0:10:18.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.12,0:10:22.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在想真的非打倒黑暗战斗暴龙兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.12,0:10:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.92,0:10:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在终于了解阿岳的心情了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.32,0:10:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我知道圣石被破坏后 一定会出事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.36,0:10:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.52,0:10:36.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他有了颗不该有的心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.92,0:10:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以去打倒他的话 一定会遭到反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.56,0:10:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织的个性就是太温和了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.48,0:11:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.56,0:11:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 谢谢你专程打电话来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.96,0:11:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.80,0:11:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.88,0:11:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实他大可不必特地跑去问我哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.60,0:11:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,直接来问我不就好了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.48,0:11:23.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这一点到很符合他的个性
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.96,0:11:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经有五颗圣石被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.16,0:11:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还剩下两颗圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.56,0:11:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要保住
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.16,0:11:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们以后要怎么做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.32,0:11:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们请甲虫兽继续去寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.80,0:11:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石的具体方位在什么地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.40,0:11:40.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以先找到 那就有胜算了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.76,0:11:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我们一定要提升我们的战斗力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.64,0:11:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道可以集结到多少同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.72,0:11:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天 我们一起去数码世界看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.72,0:11:51.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 有伙伴真好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.64,0:11:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.08,0:11:53.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.16,0:11:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和更强大的对手交战
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.96,0:11:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,值得和我交战的对手在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.84,0:12:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里 下一颗圣石在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.64,0:12:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好不容易才建好的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.00,0:12:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快住手 黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.32,0:12:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你冷静点 冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.76,0:12:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 休想命令我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.88,0:12:29.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.96,0:12:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.84,0:12:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙完全不受控制
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.76,0:12:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让开
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.84,0:12:45.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.88,0:12:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像刚出生的小婴儿一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.76,0:12:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找不到玩具就哇哇大哭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.32,0:12:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是个超级巨婴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.92,0:12:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？是婴儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.16,0:12:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那他不就是你跟我的孩子了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.60,0:12:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别在那做梦了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.52,0:13:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不快追
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.76,0:13:02.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.96,0:13:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗 就算毁掉所有的圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.36,0:13:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔不保 就完全没有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.56,0:13:11.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才要阻止他的行为啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.92,0:13:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到了 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.08,0:13:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我投降了 我们现在已经束手无策了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.76,0:13:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙怎么还没发觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.36,0:13:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他还不明白自己是为何而生的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.68,0:13:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 昨天我在大辅家留宿...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.72,0:13:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.64,0:13:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.72,0:13:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要吵 我还想要再睡一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.40,0:14:04.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 小光的电话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.40,0:14:06.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光的电话...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.96,0:14:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽说他知道第六颗圣石的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.48,0:14:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是甲虫兽通知他的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.96,0:14:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且黑暗战斗暴龙兽正在前往那里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.64,0:14:29.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 我们要立刻出发
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.64,0:14:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 海里的事就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.68,0:14:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我会和海狮兽合作一起保护圣石的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.40,0:14:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.16,0:14:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.16,0:14:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能让黑暗战斗暴龙兽靠近海域
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.12,0:14:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 不能再让他破坏圣石了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.56,0:14:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要尽全力阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.56,0:14:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超海龙兽也来帮忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.72,0:15:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海豚兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.64,0:15:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,栖息在海里的成熟期数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.64,0:15:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是从口中发射出的超音波
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.60,0:15:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「海王冲击波」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.12,0:15:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜鲨兽也来助阵了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.88,0:15:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来 胜利一定属于我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.96,0:15:15.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 还不能大意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.92,0:15:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以小看那家伙的战斗力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.12,0:15:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.68,0:15:35.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉到了...圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.24,0:15:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.12,0:15:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.84,0:15:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.60,0:15:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.60,0:16:08.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.76,0:16:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.08,0:16:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.84,0:16:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.08,0:16:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里阻止他前进
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.04,0:16:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家通力合作阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.48,0:16:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.80,0:16:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.84,0:16:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音速二重击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.56,0:16:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.08,0:16:47.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.24,0:16:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.36,0:17:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鱼叉机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.48,0:17:07.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高压氧气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.64,0:17:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.28,0:17:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.88,0:17:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.20,0:18:00.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海...海水分开了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.92,0:18:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.88,0:18:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手 快点住手啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.96,0:18:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想活命就滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.16,0:18:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 绝对不走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.68,0:18:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.68,0:18:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要逞强啊 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.40,0:18:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快离开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.16,0:18:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.60,0:18:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果轻举妄动 伊织会有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.48,0:18:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.24,0:18:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你是黑暗之塔制造出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.52,0:18:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是你却有一颗心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.12,0:18:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你不要再继续破坏圣石了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.44,0:18:35.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这件事我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.16,0:18:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果不破坏它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.88,0:18:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就不能跟更强大的对手战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.28,0:18:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我是为何而活的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.08,0:18:42.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.88,0:18:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现实世界和数码世界之间的平衡了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.60,0:18:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴 你说什么都没有用
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.48,0:18:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我只考虑如何破坏圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.80,0:18:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不愿思考
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.32,0:19:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不要有任何烦恼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.24,0:19:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的话说完了 你快点离开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.48,0:19:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝不
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.52,0:19:05.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.84,0:19:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你有心 所以我不想跟你战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.00,0:19:13.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...为什么用这种眼神看我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.32,0:19:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会想到那朵花
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.00,0:19:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.60,0:19:23.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于杀死这个小鬼会犹豫不决
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.40,0:19:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我有心的缘故吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.80,0:19:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真的是我所想的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.40,0:19:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.20,0:19:35.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不想要什么心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.84,0:19:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点离开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.20,0:19:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.56,0:19:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗龙卷风
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.48,0:20:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.72,0:20:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.72,0:20:33.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不可以让数码兽跑到这个世界来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.84,0:20:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要全力阻止这种事情发生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.96,0:20:41.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.32,0:20:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果数码兽都像奥柏兽这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.40,0:20:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同样是生命 也有好坏之分
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.08,0:20:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果生命只是单纯的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.08,0:20:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生活也就容易多了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了不能合体进化烦恼不已的伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.32,0:22:42.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而 当他坚定信念的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.08,0:22:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽和战甲兽终于成功的合体进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.80,0:22:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们究竟能否守住圣石呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:52.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能否阻止黑暗战斗暴龙兽的破坏呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.16,0:22:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.60,0:22:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「钢铁天使 古神兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}钢铁天使 古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.00,0:23:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
