[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.56,0:01:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继机甲龙兽之后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.40,0:01:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽和亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.08,0:01:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化为人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.92,0:01:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另一方面 由黑暗之塔变成的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.44,0:01:56.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.20,0:01:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一边引起相位的错移
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.88,0:02:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一边继续在数码世界游荡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}迷之遗迹圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.20,0:02:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有能与我战斗的人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.40,0:02:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有没有值得我出手的强大敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.92,0:02:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,长毛象兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.84,0:02:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招为「象牙轰击」的完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.48,0:02:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖回到我身边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.04,0:02:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,简直就是自找麻烦嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.96,0:02:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当初为了他光是珍贵的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.24,0:02:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就用掉了两百座 两百座哎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.28,0:03:00.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太有趣了 可是还不配做我的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.04,0:03:01.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.12,0:03:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.08,0:03:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.80,0:03:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信 瞬间就打倒了四只完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.72,0:03:49.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我宝贵的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.56,0:03:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒的再多...赢的再多...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.60,0:03:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还是感觉很空虚...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.76,0:04:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们并非不堪一击
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.40,0:04:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.80,0:04:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还是感到空虚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.76,0:04:15.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感到空虚？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.07,0:04:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西全是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.68,0:04:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他们没有什么不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.12,0:04:30.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是我用黑暗之塔做出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.16,0:04:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是没有生命的布娃娃而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.04,0:04:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,布娃娃是不会思考 没有感觉的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.36,0:04:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你之所以会有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.92,0:04:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些错觉是因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.68,0:04:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.96,0:04:46.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能是一百座黑暗之塔在合成的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.80,0:04:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有杂质混进我的程式里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.20,0:04:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,程式里有杂质？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.72,0:04:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果仅仅是黑暗之塔数码兽可能还好过点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.52,0:05:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.32,0:05:09.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为不是 所以才会感到痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道我心里的苦也是错觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.04,0:05:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是有办法可以解除你心里的痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.00,0:05:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.96,0:05:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放弃自我听从我们的指挥就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.44,0:05:29.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能听从弱于自己的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.00,0:05:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.60,0:05:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别吵了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.20,0:05:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不会受你的激将
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.16,0:05:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么做随便你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.44,0:05:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正你已经没有用了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.64,0:05:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.92,0:05:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.16,0:05:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们...真的什么感觉都没有吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.88,0:05:52.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们都没有心吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.28,0:05:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回答我！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.76,0:06:01.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 果然是瑕疵品
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.92,0:06:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.32,0:06:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.48,0:06:07.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于那块圣石的传说...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.20,0:06:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你一直在找的那个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.72,0:06:14.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这附近就有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.60,0:06:16.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去看一看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.12,0:06:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个传说可靠吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.88,0:06:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是真的试试不就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.64,0:06:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就全看你的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.44,0:06:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.48,0:06:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道我们的身体里有没有心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.76,0:06:35.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可从没想过这种复杂的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.72,0:06:40.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.84,0:06:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.64,0:06:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的好羡慕你们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.60,0:06:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们不需要思考
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.36,0:06:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好羡慕你哦 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.20,0:07:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了吃喝玩乐其他事一概不理
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.36,0:07:06.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也有很多事情需要思考啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.88,0:07:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很多事 比方说呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.88,0:07:10.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比方说...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.00,0:07:12.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我所想的都是很复杂的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.36,0:07:16.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是想的过多 会用脑过度的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.96,0:07:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也需要不时的放松下自己啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.04,0:07:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你会有什么值得思考的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.16,0:07:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很烦耶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.08,0:07:24.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你自己又怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.32,0:07:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说我啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.68,0:07:28.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.88,0:07:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这颗痘痘代表有人正在想着我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.20,0:07:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和终于接受我对他的心意了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.20,0:07:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的这样就太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.52,0:07:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仔细听我讲话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.84,0:07:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会有这种笨蛋姐姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.40,0:07:47.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你都不听我说话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.48,0:07:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 那个笨蛋姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.40,0:07:55.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 小光寄电子信来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.67,0:08:40.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.76,0:08:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会保护这朵小花
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.60,0:08:53.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这只是朵不起眼的小花
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.24,0:08:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.08,0:09:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.60,0:09:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发现亚基利兽的藏身之处
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.80,0:09:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我多事了 请别介意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.12,0:09:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八神光
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.72,0:09:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太难的了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.00,0:09:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走 幼虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.00,0:09:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们和我完全不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.96,0:09:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们有生命却没有烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.12,0:09:25.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好羡慕你们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.96,0:09:28.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的好羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.44,0:09:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会有痛觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.84,0:09:44.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是一朵小花而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.40,0:09:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？这个痛觉到底是哪里来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.12,0:09:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是心...从心里传来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.28,0:09:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个就是圣石？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.00,0:09:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏那个后就有好戏可看了是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.84,0:10:10.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骑士兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.92,0:10:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身穿戴特殊合金属盔甲的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.72,0:10:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.84,0:10:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「疯狂之剑」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.12,0:10:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 骑士兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.16,0:10:20.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把那块石头破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.20,0:10:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于找到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.76,0:10:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经找你很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.56,0:10:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找我...是为了战斗吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.44,0:10:55.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那要先看我们谈的如何再决定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.20,0:10:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 还没自我介绍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是亚古兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.04,0:11:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的究极体进化就是战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.64,0:11:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你也是黑暗之塔变的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.20,0:11:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 我是从数码蛋里生出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.12,0:11:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 和你谈也没有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.92,0:11:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 可以谈一谈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.24,0:11:26.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是你要先回答我的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.68,0:11:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问题？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.88,0:11:34.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那块石头是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.88,0:11:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个人到底在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.08,0:11:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在练习剑术吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.56,0:11:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是那样的话剑刃不是会钝掉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.12,0:11:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是在用石头磨他的剑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.96,0:11:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.28,0:11:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不对 我感觉到能量了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.32,0:11:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定那就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.84,0:12:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.00,0:12:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.56,0:12:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.76,0:12:05.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过根据传说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.12,0:12:08.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石被破坏的那天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.28,0:12:11.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,便是这个世界发生巨变的时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.84,0:12:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那必须阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.16,0:12:15.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 快去阻止那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.24,0:12:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 赶快联系阿岳他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.76,0:12:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该是在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.04,0:12:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 也许是在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.28,0:12:29.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我也不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.48,0:12:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要询问心的位置呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.36,0:12:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有心的你也不知道它在哪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.20,0:12:39.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,心...真的存在吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.36,0:12:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会不会这仅仅是我的错觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.04,0:12:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.20,0:12:48.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,懂得体谅别人 信任对方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.96,0:12:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种心情怎么可能是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.08,0:12:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.92,0:12:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我问你 我们为什么会有心？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.68,0:12:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样数码兽才会是数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.04,0:13:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类才会是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.04,0:13:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我没有生命 只是物体而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.64,0:13:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这样的我也会有心呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.92,0:13:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你提出的问题真的都好困难
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.92,0:13:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是在不知道该怎么回答你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.20,0:13:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛...是因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.32,0:13:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.12,0:13:28.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 可以再说一次你的问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.28,0:13:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.76,0:13:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银色光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.40,0:13:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.24,0:13:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们来支援你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.64,0:13:55.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.52,0:13:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要来阻扰我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.92,0:14:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.88,0:14:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是以生物的形式存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.88,0:14:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的我居然有心 那我可以得到什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.92,0:14:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得到什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.56,0:14:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了 你可以得到伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.12,0:14:14.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.40,0:14:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 如果你真的有心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.00,0:14:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就不是一般的物体了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.36,0:14:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是和我们一样的生命体了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.96,0:14:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就可以成为伙伴了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.44,0:14:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙伴 还有呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.76,0:14:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外还有什么作用？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.68,0:14:36.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.64,0:14:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想要什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.92,0:14:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.28,0:14:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也不知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.00,0:14:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然也不是为了众人眼中的名誉和金钱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.84,0:14:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该有更重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.64,0:14:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 就是我之所以存在的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.64,0:14:54.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你之所以存在的理由？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.96,0:14:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我来到这个世界是为了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.76,0:15:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对 我存在的意义是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.40,0:15:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我到这个世界上只是为了战斗的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.96,0:15:09.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就只专注于打败敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.40,0:15:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.20,0:15:18.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为有心的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.68,0:15:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而阻碍我战斗的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.44,0:15:25.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就干脆把他丢掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.64,0:15:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.04,0:15:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千万不能把心丢掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.56,0:15:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接招
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.64,0:15:38.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我动弹不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.48,0:15:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽 合体...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.88,0:15:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.96,0:15:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我身上的盔甲可是刀枪不入的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.96,0:16:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了 怎么可以用剑敲我的盔甲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.84,0:16:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.32,0:16:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我拉紧一点勒死你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.12,0:16:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺丁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.84,0:16:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.16,0:16:32.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.68,0:16:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.84,0:16:34.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.08,0:16:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.32,0:16:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.32,0:16:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.20,0:16:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.92,0:16:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.12,0:17:00.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.04,0:17:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.35,0:17:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.40,0:17:11.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.28,0:17:17.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.35,0:17:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万吨压力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.88,0:17:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 我的攻击不是盖的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.59,0:17:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 干的好 战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.92,0:17:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 怎么可以把心丢弃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.76,0:17:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你拥有心绝对不会是巧合
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.84,0:17:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果为了战斗而丢弃自己的心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.00,0:17:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就太蠢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.24,0:17:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为我们可以成为好朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.24,0:17:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你不一定是因为这个才会有心的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.04,0:17:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可以证明这一点吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.28,0:17:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.40,0:18:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过可能需要点时间才行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.24,0:18:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.12,0:18:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.52,0:18:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.92,0:18:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很不舒服 是什么让我如此难受
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.20,0:18:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.40,0:18:43.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣石出现变化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.08,0:18:55.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪？等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.24,0:19:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.16,0:19:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击居然完全无效
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.24,0:19:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.48,0:19:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你事先到底有没有调查啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.96,0:19:16.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不...真可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.36,0:19:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还以为一切都会很顺利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.32,0:19:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.60,0:19:21.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.36,0:19:25.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽 先撤退再说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.60,0:19:26.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.04,0:19:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.00,0:19:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阴谋失败 所以准备逃跑了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.20,0:19:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.96,0:19:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.88,0:19:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.04,0:19:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.88,0:19:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.16,0:19:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.88,0:20:00.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.16,0:20:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.60,0:20:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,路路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.36,0:20:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.00,0:20:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全不是他的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.48,0:20:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.92,0:20:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.24,0:20:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.32,0:20:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快被吸进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.76,0:20:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.04,0:20:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到他居然会做到这个地步呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.36,0:20:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 我没有给他命令啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.64,0:20:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过他对我们的计划似乎很有帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.64,0:21:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...就是我之所以存在的理由吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.56,0:22:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于等到了期盼已久的毕业旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.64,0:22:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,留下钝钝兽的小京出发去了京都
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.80,0:22:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,清水寺 金阁寺 京都还有什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.84,0:22:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...出现在小京眼前的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.20,0:22:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却是神秘的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.84,0:22:52.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.68,0:22:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.96,0:22:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「小京的京都之旅」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.11,0:22:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}小京的京都之旅
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.76,0:22:59.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
