[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.68,0:01:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽不断思考自己诞生的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.56,0:01:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并向亚古兽提出自己的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.64,0:01:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽正在设法寻找保护数码世界的圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.76,0:01:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而就在封印被破坏的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.24,0:01:59.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.65,0:02:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}小京的京都之旅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.52,0:02:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是京都 京都
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.12,0:02:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 快点 车子要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.60,0:02:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.32,0:02:25.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽还好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.88,0:02:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.88,0:02:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你帮我照顾钝钝兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.00,0:02:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕业旅行的第二天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.96,0:02:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来到了京都
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.36,0:02:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我名字你的「京」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.92,0:02:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚好就是京都的「京」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.88,0:02:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都比我想象的要时尚的多
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.08,0:02:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 是因为那片黑暗之海
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.12,0:02:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,东西也很好吃 真是棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.20,0:02:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽 我会带礼物回来的 要乖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.80,0:02:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,改变D3暴龙机的形状
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.68,0:02:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会发生之后的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.36,0:02:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 为了对抗你的暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.80,0:02:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们也必须有相同型号的暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.72,0:03:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们却没有这种型号
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.28,0:03:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙机的形状
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.12,0:03:06.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该是你心里所希望的样子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.68,0:03:09.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他们的暴龙机
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.88,0:03:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是为了和你对抗才会变形的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.04,0:03:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我所希望的样子？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.80,0:03:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在数码世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.72,0:03:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当所有的资料集合的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.76,0:03:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,首先决定的不是别的 正是他的形状
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.32,0:03:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根据暴龙机拥有者心里所读取到的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.68,0:03:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些资料就会进行相应的组合
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.36,0:03:32.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们的服装会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.72,0:03:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能也是这个缘故吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.32,0:03:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来...暴龙改造者的造型
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.44,0:03:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我心里想要的...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.92,0:03:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是潜意思里的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.04,0:03:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问题是 那封信到底是谁写给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.60,0:03:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个我自己也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.64,0:03:53.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定和那个女性外形的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.24,0:03:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.92,0:03:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是亚基利兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.60,0:03:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该跟她有关吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.88,0:04:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 黑暗之塔...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.76,0:04:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他我们所不了解的功能
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.24,0:04:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们还要继续调查下去才行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.72,0:04:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 关于这些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.76,0:04:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的记忆真的非常模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.32,0:04:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你别介意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.96,0:04:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,倒是我们竟然比那个寄信的人还要晚找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.48,0:04:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有想到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.95,0:04:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子竟然就在我们身边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在我们身边？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.16,0:04:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.72,0:04:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是只有我们几个而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.56,0:04:34.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全世界都有 而且为数不少
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.04,0:04:37.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目前详细的情况还不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.12,0:04:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 他们似乎都在1999年的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.68,0:04:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遇见了跑到现实世界里的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.28,0:04:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与其说被选召
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.08,0:04:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不如说是拥有伙伴数码兽的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.28,0:04:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 2000年的8月
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.08,0:04:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就连这个 我也记不太清了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.32,0:05:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽 小京从京都寄了封电子信给你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.12,0:05:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 身体不舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.48,0:05:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是因为和伙伴分开太久的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.08,0:05:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,单独留在现实世界很容易累
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.12,0:05:17.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使我变成虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.80,0:05:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,单独留在这里太久也会很疲倦的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.64,0:05:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.84,0:05:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从小京出去旅行的前一天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.84,0:05:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到现在已经三天了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.48,0:05:26.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽说只有三天
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.96,0:05:28.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是和小京分开后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.40,0:05:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就如此的疲倦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.24,0:05:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来数码兽们...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.44,0:05:34.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要在现实世界生活竟然这么辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.00,0:05:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我带他回数码世界去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.72,0:05:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫他们不是已经先去那边了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.32,0:05:44.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 那就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.40,0:05:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你到那里的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.60,0:05:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,顺便注意下那边世界歪斜扭曲的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.04,0:05:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.68,0:05:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...为什么要告诉我这些呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你想知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.80,0:06:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次到数码世界的时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.44,0:06:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这究竟是个怎样的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.68,0:06:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的心里充满了假设
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.96,0:06:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是那个时候我年纪还很小
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.60,0:06:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收集的资料也有限
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.84,0:06:15.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无法精确的解读
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.80,0:06:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很想知道数码世界的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.88,0:06:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那有助于我更好的了解现实世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.96,0:06:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家两个小时之后在这里集合
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.60,0:06:30.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.64,0:06:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到了京都 首先要买这个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.40,0:06:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是生八桥以及吸油面纸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.52,0:06:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.60,0:06:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要破坏掉...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.28,0:06:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要破坏掉这个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.92,0:07:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会再痛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随便你怎么做 尽管破坏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.56,0:07:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最好全部都破坏掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.04,0:07:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到我们放手不管
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.36,0:07:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他却如此配合我们的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.56,0:07:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.92,0:07:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 还是没赶上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.76,0:07:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,错位了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.48,0:07:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整个都失去平衡了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.16,0:07:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.88,0:07:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要是黑暗战斗暴龙兽经过的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.84,0:07:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都会发生扭曲现象
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.88,0:07:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是因为那块石头被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.80,0:07:40.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以扭曲也更严重了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.32,0:07:42.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽他...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.76,0:07:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.28,0:07:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.00,0:08:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...竟然没有人注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.28,0:08:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红绿灯是怎么回事啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.12,0:08:22.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.48,0:08:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.00,0:08:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孙悟空兽 成熟期
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.56,0:08:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全身金黄色的毛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.60,0:08:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的兽人型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.12,0:08:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「怒发天」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.72,0:08:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.32,0:08:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要赶快通知大家才行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.28,0:09:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 京都出现数码兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.68,0:09:04.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家赶快想想办法！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.60,0:09:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想战斗吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:09.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个根本不够看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.40,0:09:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会输呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.68,0:09:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 V仔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.36,0:09:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.96,0:09:21.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.52,0:09:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:31.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.40,0:09:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.04,0:09:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.36,0:09:43.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.32,0:09:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.08,0:09:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,广明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.76,0:09:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠美子 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.92,0:09:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.08,0:10:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 阿修
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.40,0:10:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.28,0:10:04.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才里面好像有什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.88,0:10:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.56,0:10:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.76,0:10:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是接下来该怎么办呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.64,0:10:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很近了 在那边 飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.20,0:10:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.52,0:10:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.28,0:10:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.80,0:10:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.60,0:10:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.96,0:10:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回头再给你解释
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.88,0:10:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽 那只不是黑暗之塔变的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.24,0:10:50.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以千万不能打倒他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.12,0:10:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.32,0:11:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.96,0:11:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 后面的事就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.76,0:11:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托我什么 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.12,0:11:14.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.80,0:11:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你怎么回来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.52,0:11:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会在这里...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.68,0:11:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到了 教授 在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.92,0:11:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 就是刚才那个说到数码兽的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.52,0:11:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.60,0:11:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你手上抱的那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.80,0:11:33.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他就是数码兽 对吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.12,0:11:55.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忘了介绍了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.04,0:11:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫...武之内春彦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:01.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在东京一说大学里面教民俗学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.08,0:12:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去年才从东京来到京都进行研究
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.04,0:12:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这位是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.72,0:12:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是城户修 大学二年级
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.84,0:12:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来念医学院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.20,0:12:12.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后来听了教授的通识课程后
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.88,0:12:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,转系到了人文学院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.12,0:12:16.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我哥哥是医学院的实习生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.36,0:12:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我弟弟也想当医生 正在为此努力中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.88,0:12:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是...在东京念小学六年级
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.64,0:12:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫井上京 是来京都毕业旅行的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.64,0:12:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然没错 我听我弟弟说过关于你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.32,0:12:37.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也听我女儿提起过你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你们说的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.88,0:12:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,城户丈和武之内空他们吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.00,0:12:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Bingo
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.32,0:12:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.52,0:12:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在换你尝尝我的厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.92,0:12:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.48,0:12:58.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.48,0:13:01.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等你很久了 一乘寺 我们合体吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.00,0:13:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.16,0:13:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.00,0:13:12.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.40,0:13:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.28,0:13:21.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.48,0:13:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...就是从事这种研究的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.48,0:13:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以一直在日本国内到处跑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.20,0:13:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有时为了研究也需要到国外
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.36,0:13:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且常常一去就很久不能回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.56,0:13:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以有段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.60,0:13:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我太太跟我女儿为此非常的反对
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.24,0:13:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是三年前我女儿的态度突然改变了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.40,0:13:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一问之下才知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.88,0:13:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是数码兽改变了她的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.64,0:13:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽改变了她？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.60,0:13:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.76,0:13:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为和数码兽一起经历了很多事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.12,0:13:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一下子长大了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.00,0:13:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼界也开阔了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.16,0:14:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真的非常的感谢他们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感谢让我女儿成长起来的数码兽们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.92,0:14:12.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.64,0:14:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说的我是不太懂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.24,0:14:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过这样的确很好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.12,0:14:18.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是真正的数码兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.68,0:14:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到我可以亲眼见到真正的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:23.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前 我跟着社团外出旅行并不在东京
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.60,0:14:26.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我看见了夜空好像有个影像浮现
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.52,0:14:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是太远了 我没有想到我弟弟也在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.56,0:14:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是很想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.96,0:14:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那些数码兽会出现在京都呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都自建都开始
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.88,0:14:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就和狐狸妖怪之类脱不了关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.72,0:14:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狐狸？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.20,0:14:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是指狐狸 狸猫之类的动物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.80,0:14:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我目前研究的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.60,0:14:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这些传说中的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.76,0:14:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真有其事或者只是人们捏造出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.08,0:15:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,京都之所以会成为国都
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.68,0:15:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为它是唯一适合四神的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.64,0:15:05.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种说法你听过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.96,0:15:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像没有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.68,0:15:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,北边的船冈山是玄武
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.08,0:15:11.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,东边的鸭川是青龙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.28,0:15:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,南方的巨椋池是朱雀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.52,0:15:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,西边的山阴则是白虎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.56,0:15:19.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说它位于山脚下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.56,0:15:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水路交通也很方便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.32,0:15:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整个地形向南边打开
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.32,0:15:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以它具备了各种适合建都的条件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.04,0:15:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此外 京都的鬼门和四方都建立了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.40,0:15:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重要的神社和佛寺作为守护
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据说不这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.80,0:15:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妖魔鬼怪就会一直来骚扰我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.36,0:15:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鬼门...妖魔鬼怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.56,0:15:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,教授
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.40,0:15:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉 我说的太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.24,0:15:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 京都和以前完全不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.84,0:15:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能再回到从前了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.68,0:15:54.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样 在现实世界中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.56,0:15:56.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,离魔界 灵界这些异次元空间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.80,0:15:59.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近的地方便是京都了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.68,0:16:01.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔界 灵界？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.72,0:16:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就拿你看到的数码兽来说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.68,0:16:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很可能数码世界的歪斜扭曲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.76,0:16:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对京都的影响远比东京要严重的多
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.68,0:16:11.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.72,0:16:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽好像是妖魔鬼怪的亲戚似的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.20,0:16:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说错了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.36,0:16:20.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为他们既然能够在那里生存
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.96,0:16:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就不仅仅是一些集合的资料而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.16,0:16:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪被称为九十九神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.24,0:16:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人们经常使用的道具
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.52,0:16:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,经过一百年之后也有可能变成妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.64,0:16:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许他们原本仅仅是电脑里的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.52,0:16:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是现在他们有了生命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.68,0:16:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不正好印证这一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.92,0:16:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们别走 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.84,0:16:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.84,0:17:04.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武士兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.59,0:17:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿着盔甲的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.83,0:17:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外形像一个落魄的武士
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.52,0:17:09.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是右手所拿的妖刀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.31,0:17:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白鸟丸所发出的「百物斩」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.20,0:17:12.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.11,0:17:16.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钝钝兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.04,0:17:18.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.35,0:17:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.64,0:17:24.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是数码兽的进化啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.11,0:17:25.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,羽毛回力刀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.48,0:17:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.68,0:17:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.44,0:17:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.32,0:18:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉涌般的纯真 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.04,0:18:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,红叶散落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.40,0:18:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.48,0:18:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我居然亲眼看到什么叫做进化了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.64,0:18:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,城...城户 我们快点跟上去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.96,0:18:17.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,教授 你这里有没有笔记本电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.04,0:18:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,百物斩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.12,0:18:32.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.00,0:18:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.92,0:18:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者兽 大门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.00,0:18:52.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请关上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.16,0:18:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.00,0:18:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 他不是不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.44,0:19:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是回数码世界去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.12,0:19:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.88,0:19:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 黑暗战斗暴龙兽他们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.08,0:19:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们都回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.20,0:19:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么会出现在现实世界呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.00,0:19:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底有什么目的？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.96,0:19:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来他们的这些行动毫无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.60,0:19:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对他们来说可能理由充分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.28,0:19:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在大门随时都可以打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.40,0:19:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此可以把他们赶回数码世界去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.96,0:19:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一他们那个时候却没有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.36,0:19:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.64,0:19:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.64,0:19:47.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然你会赶不上集合的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.68,0:19:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经这么晚了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.36,0:19:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.32,0:20:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽 我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.04,0:20:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.40,0:20:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想逃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.60,0:20:10.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可没时间陪你们这些小鬼玩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.32,0:20:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 你们可不要放心的太早
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.12,0:20:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的那五颗圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.04,0:20:18.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会完全破坏给你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.76,0:20:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.24,0:20:23.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他说还有另外五颗圣石
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.08,0:20:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是全部被她破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.64,0:20:29.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界的歪斜扭曲会变的更严重
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.24,0:20:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是光子郎他们所担心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.44,0:20:36.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果数码世界完全失去平衡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.92,0:20:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会出大事的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.84,0:20:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 你回到东京之后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.04,0:20:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,替我向空问个好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.44,0:20:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有阿丈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.76,0:20:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.20,0:20:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好慢哦 到底去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.88,0:20:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉 有点事...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.80,0:20:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.32,0:20:59.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绒毛玩偶  绒毛玩偶啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.92,0:21:00.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.48,0:21:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？ 好可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.44,0:21:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里买的 让我看看好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.56,0:21:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好玩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.56,0:21:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐一下 钝钝兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.52,0:22:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后一颗圣石了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.84,0:22:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都要早日找到并保护它
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.76,0:22:44.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅等人集合所有的数码兽进行保卫战
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.48,0:22:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳对黑暗势力极端痛恨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.48,0:22:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织却不知道原因何在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.80,0:22:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽对圣石的破坏会不会成功呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.88,0:22:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.20,0:22:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「圣石保卫战」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.82,0:23:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}圣石保卫战
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.24,0:22:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
