[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.08,0:01:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用笛子操控昆虫型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.84,0:01:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并给孩子们制造陷阱的神秘女子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.48,0:01:39.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被认为是人类的她的真身
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.92,0:01:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实际上是邪恶的亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.16,0:01:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此外新的敌人 木乃伊兽也出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.64,0:01:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事态更加紧急
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.52,0:01:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟亚基利兽和木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.92,0:01:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后会使出什么样的手段呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.88,0:02:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有 大辅他们会如何反击呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,150)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}黑暗究极体
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.61,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(350,365)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.32,0:02:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水温还行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.56,0:02:43.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.40,0:02:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.60,0:02:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,水温还行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.56,0:03:08.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 水温还行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.20,0:03:15.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 回答我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:19.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在想重要的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.04,0:03:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.64,0:03:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.48,0:03:41.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.76,0:03:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.88,0:03:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.36,0:03:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.84,0:03:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.60,0:04:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.12,0:04:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星光线
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.56,0:04:07.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.36,0:04:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,罗塞塔之石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.60,0:04:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.60,0:04:17.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺丁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.60,0:04:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位！先休息一会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.72,0:04:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.28,0:04:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,口渴了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.12,0:04:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.24,0:04:42.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边有果汁的自动贩卖机
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.20,0:04:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去买吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.56,0:04:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个主意不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.84,0:04:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.88,0:04:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.08,0:04:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去 我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.08,0:04:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我会把大辅的份也买回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.64,0:04:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想喝什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.20,0:05:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随便你们买什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.28,0:05:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在生什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.24,0:05:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.68,0:05:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 婆婆妈妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.92,0:05:14.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有烦恼的话 就说出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.72,0:05:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说没事就没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.40,0:05:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.04,0:05:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.32,0:05:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你加了个同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.20,0:05:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这么叫只会让我感觉不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.16,0:05:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦！真是的 每个人都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.48,0:05:31.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算了算了 比起这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.88,0:05:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有事情和你商量
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.60,0:05:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.60,0:05:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 伊织和一乘寺？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.20,0:05:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那两个家伙 故意分开坐吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.12,0:05:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊！ 让人放不下心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.72,0:05:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是 不能放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.40,0:05:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢 这个主意怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.92,0:06:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.64,0:06:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.16,0:06:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.16,0:06:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽的火焰飞弹都无法打倒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.96,0:06:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么...就凭黑暗之塔那种货色！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.32,0:06:24.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了让伊织和一乘寺的关系和好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.36,0:06:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.04,0:06:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是很厉害的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.44,0:06:33.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是很厉害的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.88,0:06:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺丁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.08,0:06:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大爆震
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.60,0:07:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.40,0:07:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然改善了伊织和一乘寺的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.52,0:07:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽的关系...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.44,0:07:18.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问题在于伊织和一乘寺本身却...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.84,0:07:28.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 都合力弄倒过黑暗之塔了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.52,0:07:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少握个手也行啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.36,0:07:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.64,0:07:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.64,0:07:35.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个只靠烈焰兽就可以打倒的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.76,0:07:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.56,0:07:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被你们这么一说...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.64,0:07:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请不要让我们无谓的浪费能量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.68,0:07:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 你这家伙啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.52,0:07:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.40,0:07:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然我会影响你们团队的气氛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.96,0:07:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.68,0:07:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.44,0:07:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.80,0:07:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.32,0:08:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊...真是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.00,0:08:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.20,0:08:10.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打倒被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.88,0:08:12.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能缺少强力且邪恶的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.88,0:08:14.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再往下一点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.23,0:08:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一座黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.52,0:08:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制造的数码兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.36,0:08:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十座黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.58,0:08:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,制造的数码兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.16,0:08:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是都输了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要打倒被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.80,0:08:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至少得使用一百座黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.08,0:09:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要利用一百座黑暗之塔就意味着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.40,0:09:04.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,需要亚基利兽拔一百根头发
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.72,0:09:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果亚基利兽拔了一百根头发...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.96,0:09:13.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在想象什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.80,0:09:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.48,0:09:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被亚基利兽打了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.84,0:09:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不但不觉得痛反而感到很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.64,0:09:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难不成我爱上亚基利兽了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.64,0:09:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,木乃伊兽你在干什么 要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.56,0:09:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.36,0:10:11.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了打倒被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.76,0:10:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了毁灭这个数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.64,0:10:16.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,强大的数码兽啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.56,0:10:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诞生吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.72,0:10:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来发生这样的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.60,0:10:56.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织和一乘寺都不够坦白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.72,0:10:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然也不是不能理解伊织的心情...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.12,0:11:13.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管是伊织还是一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.76,0:11:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果不能再成熟一点的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.96,0:11:25.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家也是这么想的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.84,0:11:34.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 我说了什么很可笑的话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.00,0:11:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.72,0:11:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家怎么了 这么沉默...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.00,0:11:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 背后！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.76,0:11:59.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个原来在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.16,0:12:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这里不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.88,0:12:02.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们来干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.56,0:12:04.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.68,0:12:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只不过带我创造的数码兽出来玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.68,0:12:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不吸取教训
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.92,0:12:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是才刚输给我们吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.08,0:12:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次...会怎么样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.88,0:12:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟上来吧 小屁孩们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.12,0:12:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.32,0:12:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.56,0:12:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.84,0:13:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.36,0:13:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.96,0:13:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.36,0:13:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.48,0:13:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.64,0:13:42.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.24,0:13:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.44,0:13:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.92,0:14:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.08,0:14:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.04,0:14:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.68,0:14:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和以前一样只是阵势庞大罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.52,0:14:29.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这个阵势
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.08,0:14:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天也会被扑灭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.56,0:14:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:37.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 小京 这次和平时不同
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.08,0:14:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有一种不祥的预感
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.92,0:14:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳他们是不是太快了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.68,0:14:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.44,0:14:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.76,0:15:06.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个家伙是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.80,0:15:08.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.24,0:15:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗...战斗暴龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.64,0:15:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.12,0:15:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和战斗暴龙兽有着同样的外形
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.76,0:15:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却是用黑暗之塔制造出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拥有黑暗灵魂的究极体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.48,0:15:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是集合所有负面能量再释放出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.84,0:15:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑盖亚能量炮」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.52,0:15:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙...出人意料的强...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.24,0:15:41.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会是...黑暗战斗暴龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.20,0:15:44.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.28,0:15:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你问我怎么办 当然是保护孩子们了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.24,0:15:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也只有这么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.80,0:16:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么会这么强大！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.72,0:16:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话 大家会...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.72,0:16:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能赢他的只有机甲龙兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.12,0:16:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快叫一乘寺来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.96,0:16:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 快来！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.52,0:16:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想破坏你们团队作战的气氛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.00,0:16:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是顾虑我们团队气氛的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.44,0:16:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就凭我们几个来战斗吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.12,0:16:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.28,0:16:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个都停止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.92,0:16:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我去把他带过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.44,0:16:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.96,0:16:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.24,0:16:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会把一乘寺带过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.04,0:16:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在此之前一定要坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.56,0:17:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.12,0:17:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真是压倒性的强大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.88,0:17:13.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 不去好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.07,0:17:14.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.88,0:17:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要装傻 大辅他们呼唤你了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.20,0:17:20.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫他们啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.48,0:17:22.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.04,0:17:26.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.04,0:17:27.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快来 亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.59,0:17:29.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,制造出非常强大的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.88,0:17:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贤！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.60,0:17:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是机甲龙兽的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.92,0:17:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.40,0:17:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.40,0:17:39.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.28,0:17:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤你这个大笨蛋！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.04,0:17:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.88,0:17:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.64,0:17:53.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在拼命的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.28,0:18:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,振作起来 飞虫兽一定会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.48,0:18:07.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.16,0:18:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点解决掉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.24,0:18:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的母亲 亚基利兽的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.92,0:18:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.80,0:18:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我把一乘寺他们带来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.92,0:18:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.00,0:18:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.76,0:18:32.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.76,0:18:36.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.28,0:18:40.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.08,0:18:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.24,0:18:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙让我吃了不少苦头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.36,0:18:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽 给我好好回报他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.04,0:19:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X刺钉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.60,0:19:10.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的确不同于亚基利兽以往创造的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.96,0:19:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全力攻击吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.40,0:19:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.52,0:19:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.48,0:19:35.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮居然没用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.08,0:19:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.80,0:19:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.20,0:19:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.92,0:19:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快逃啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.76,0:20:16.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做得很好 黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.40,0:20:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多事情要你帮我完成
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.84,0:20:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破坏这个数码世界 直到毁灭为止
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.00,0:20:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.36,0:20:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是生你的母亲 亚基利兽的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.16,0:20:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会服从任何人的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.76,0:20:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.04,0:20:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个不怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.56,0:20:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不配做我战斗的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.60,0:20:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要去寻找更加强大的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.68,0:20:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.92,0:20:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.56,0:20:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你抱着我做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.48,0:21:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.60,0:22:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,动摇了的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.16,0:22:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在森林中迷路的小光 小京还有小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易到达的黑暗世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.68,0:22:44.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及黑色的海
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.32,0:22:46.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紧握着的双手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.52,0:22:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢与黑暗战斗的小光和小京
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.68,0:22:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤也不再受制于黑暗力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.36,0:22:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的力量 新的合体进化出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.40,0:22:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.72,0:22:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「爱的狂风暴 人面战鹰兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.83,0:22:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,325)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}爱的狂风暴 人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.92,0:23:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
