[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.44,0:01:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔因亚基利兽等的原因出现在世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.96,0:01:44.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而大辅等人借助帝皇龙甲兽的力量来到各国
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.72,0:01:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒了黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.12,0:01:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且将数码兽们送回了数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.68,0:01:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.56,0:01:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.32,0:02:00.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此时正在着手进行着下个作战计划
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.53,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(600,0)}究极魔兽军团来袭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.52,0:02:12.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于可以回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.96,0:02:15.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿死啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.40,0:02:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真想快点吃东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.48,0:02:20.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,油炸包子！红菜汤！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.28,0:02:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.92,0:02:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 我的肚子已经饿扁了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.32,0:02:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 先回家再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.04,0:02:30.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.92,0:02:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.92,0:02:34.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点担心敌人的动向...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会善罢甘休的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.76,0:02:38.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.76,0:02:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.16,0:02:42.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟这次我们也非常的努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.40,0:02:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是先休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.00,0:02:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为了将来做准备啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.36,0:02:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊？我说了什么奇怪的话了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.00,0:02:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 没想到大辅也能说出这么有学问的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.40,0:02:59.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.08,0:03:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,单纯的笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.00,0:03:05.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 有什么好笑的！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.96,0:03:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.52,0:03:11.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我们和他回去的方向不同
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.88,0:03:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺很努力呢 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.64,0:03:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.72,0:03:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 你回来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.88,0:03:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然有事出去 所以回来晚了 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.48,0:03:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 我在新闻中看到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.16,0:03:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地都出现了怪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.88,0:03:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是在说数码兽的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.32,0:03:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和你们也有关系？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.96,0:03:39.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.48,0:03:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.28,0:03:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.12,0:03:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 有件事情我一直放心不下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.40,0:03:53.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之前我见到一个奇怪的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.96,0:03:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的男人？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.72,0:04:00.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么「三年前的事情并未完结」之类的奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.88,0:04:01.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.16,0:04:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说找我只想知道三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.60,0:04:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在光丘和御台场发生的事情的详情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.12,0:04:13.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我当时在想那个人是不是和这件事有关
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.92,0:04:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 那个人是人类吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.60,0:04:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是人类？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.72,0:04:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么 只是随便问问
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.44,0:04:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是木乃伊兽在...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.00,0:04:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 晚饭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.40,0:04:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了 你去哪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.28,0:04:32.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去哪都和你无关
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.96,0:04:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那什么态度！气死我了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.12,0:04:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着为你播报事件的后续动态
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.24,0:04:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地出现的怪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.44,0:04:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在今天傍晚五点左右全部消失
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.04,0:04:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,详细的情形目前还不明朗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.00,0:04:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的很让人火大！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.68,0:04:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.80,0:04:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你去哪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.76,0:04:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 和朋友去玩了...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.40,0:04:58.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和朋友一起？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.56,0:05:01.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你平安无事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.28,0:05:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.00,0:05:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从早上开始田町就一片混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.40,0:05:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为小贤一直都不回来 让我担心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.56,0:05:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次要晚回家 记得先告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.52,0:05:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.56,0:05:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.12,0:05:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下再吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.64,0:05:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 怎么样 我的速度很快吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.32,0:05:28.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.28,0:05:31.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 什么事都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.60,0:05:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.92,0:05:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸是怎么死的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.96,0:05:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么突然问这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.36,0:05:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是突然想问
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.36,0:05:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浩树是在保护外国的政界要员时牺牲的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.08,0:05:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以前和你提起过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.12,0:05:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.84,0:05:58.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有什么难以释怀的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.80,0:06:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没 只是在想「为保护别人而死」这件事...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.08,0:06:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.60,0:06:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你吃完了？那么帮我把爸爸他们叫来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.96,0:06:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.32,0:06:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 姐姐 去吃饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.72,0:06:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.84,0:06:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是和平啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.52,0:06:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就好像白天的事情没有发生过似的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.20,0:06:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.60,0:06:33.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去可不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.48,0:06:34.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.96,0:06:36.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然大辅他们说要战斗 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.96,0:06:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.44,0:06:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也只是破坏了敌人的黑色魔轮及黑色魔戒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.12,0:06:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒了黑暗的数码兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.48,0:06:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那帮家伙只不过长得像数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.96,0:06:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实际上是黑暗之塔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.68,0:06:51.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 所以他们才能毫不犹豫的打倒他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.28,0:06:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么认为的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.04,0:06:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像三年前的那样...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.68,0:06:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须真的打倒数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.16,0:07:01.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以打倒他们为目的的战斗即将来临
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.96,0:07:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽他们还在这个世界的某个角落呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.72,0:07:10.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果不制服他们的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.00,0:07:12.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.32,0:07:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 明天可以尽情睡觉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.96,0:07:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.24,0:07:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.84,0:07:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的那个黑影...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.08,0:07:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让人非常在意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.92,0:07:27.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.24,0:07:30.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.28,0:07:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快睡吧 你一定累坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.76,0:07:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.40,0:07:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.04,0:07:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.64,0:07:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干的好 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.96,0:07:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.20,0:07:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.00,0:07:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤！怎么了？振作起来！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.52,0:07:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是梦？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.80,0:08:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做了恶梦吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.92,0:08:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.16,0:08:04.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.20,0:08:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们两年前一起去数码世界探险的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.00,0:08:10.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.32,0:08:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候 我的脖子受伤了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.48,0:08:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我记得的...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.28,0:08:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时我还以为小贤会死 非常担心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.28,0:08:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候的事 我完全不记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.36,0:08:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又怎么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.08,0:08:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后 我怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.56,0:08:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时小贤的伤口很快就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.60,0:08:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后平安的回到了这个世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.67,0:08:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有这些？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.72,0:08:39.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想起什么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.44,0:08:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 虽然记忆非常的凌乱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.36,0:08:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仍然感觉当时似乎发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.76,0:08:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.28,0:08:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系 不用着急
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.56,0:08:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之我们先去报告他的位置吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后就世界各地出现怪兽异象做详细报道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.96,0:09:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接着播报下一则新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.28,0:09:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从昨天下午五点开始
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.16,0:09:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,市内有多名小学生陆续失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.16,0:09:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,警方怀疑是被卷入什么事件之中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.24,0:09:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在进行调查
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.92,0:09:21.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有小孩行踪不明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果平安无事就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.84,0:09:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真让人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤？怎么了？脸色好苍白！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.56,0:09:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.80,0:09:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...为什么心中如此恐慌？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.56,0:09:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.24,0:09:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.20,0:09:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.32,0:10:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.04,0:10:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.32,0:10:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是生活在深海里的兽人型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.40,0:10:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是发射剧毒的「罪孽黑毒」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.96,0:10:34.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.16,0:10:36.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是阿和发来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.76,0:10:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女恶魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.84,0:11:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女性堕天使型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是转化对手能量的「血蝙蝠」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.32,0:11:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,石田先生 好像东银座也出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.08,0:11:11.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.20,0:11:20.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丧尸撒旦兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.24,0:11:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,堕落天使型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.40,0:11:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为追求破坏力而变为极端堕落形态
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.60,0:11:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「堕落骨爪」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.68,0:11:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银座也出现了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.56,0:11:34.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在向谁发邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.08,0:11:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永不止息的诚实 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.40,0:12:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.40,0:12:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.64,0:12:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.00,0:12:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.32,0:12:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜行攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.48,0:12:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好强...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.68,0:12:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鱼叉机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.36,0:12:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.48,0:13:11.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.04,0:13:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祖顿兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.60,0:13:27.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊 祖顿兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.12,0:13:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重锤火花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.28,0:13:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快追 天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.04,0:13:38.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.68,0:13:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该先去救出船上的乘客
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.28,0:13:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正等着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.76,0:13:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,血蝙蝠
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.20,0:13:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.44,0:13:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 太危险了 快离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.76,0:14:00.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.40,0:14:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你逃不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.44,0:14:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.56,0:14:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.92,0:14:29.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.80,0:14:31.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点过去帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.48,0:14:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是什么东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是亚基利兽的同伙？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.24,0:14:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.16,0:14:50.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超比多兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.76,0:14:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.44,0:15:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙和往日所遇的数码兽不同
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.52,0:15:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「和往日所遇的数码兽不同」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是亚基利兽的同伙吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.40,0:15:12.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么到底是..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.64,0:15:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做的真够夸张的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.28,0:15:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗 让他们这么肆意妄为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.12,0:15:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随他们去吧 我们还来得及回去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.88,0:15:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了亚基利兽以外 还有人与我们作对？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.16,0:15:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.64,0:15:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟这个数码兽过于强大了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是并非是黑暗之塔变的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.76,0:15:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说没有被控制
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.28,0:15:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定有什么在蠢蠢欲动
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.80,0:15:38.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别再想了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.44,0:15:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迷茫的话会被干掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.92,0:15:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.68,0:15:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽 进化吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.44,0:15:51.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽 究极进化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.80,0:15:54.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.64,0:16:04.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极体...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.92,0:16:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,堕落骨爪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.32,0:16:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽！怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.36,0:16:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.20,0:16:19.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.12,0:16:21.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为敌人的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.48,0:16:24.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽的资料被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.00,0:16:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.04,0:16:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.56,0:16:36.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.52,0:16:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.84,0:16:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来啦 来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.44,0:16:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.52,0:16:48.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心 这家伙和往日所遇到的敌人不同
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.64,0:16:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,堕落骨爪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.44,0:17:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.31,0:17:06.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,动起来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.56,0:17:15.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,堕落骨爪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.92,0:17:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么变回来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.88,0:17:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从青龙兽那里得到的力量明明还有剩余的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.24,0:17:28.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.60,0:17:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道啊 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.04,0:17:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敌人去哪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.96,0:17:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这辆公车会怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.76,0:17:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！  偏偏在这个时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.72,0:17:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变回成长期啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.28,0:17:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽！ 清醒过来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.36,0:17:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 亚古兽他们...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.32,0:17:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重来没有在这边的世界待过这么长的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.08,0:17:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.84,0:18:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快些送他们回数码世界会很危险的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.52,0:18:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.96,0:18:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来要怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.16,0:18:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.20,0:18:07.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 大家赶快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.16,0:18:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 把剩余的力量全部给帝皇龙甲兽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.44,0:18:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.96,0:18:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.56,0:18:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是遗憾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.36,0:18:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了！动一下啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.68,0:18:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.36,0:18:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽 改变形态 战士形态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.60,0:18:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽 战士形态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.08,0:18:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为用两只脚行走 大大增强了战斗力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.84,0:19:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽...改变形态了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.24,0:19:01.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的交给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.92,0:19:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连同我们的份
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.08,0:19:07.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你们打算做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.92,0:19:11.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子镭射
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.24,0:19:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.16,0:19:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是把他打倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.92,0:19:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们把敌人打倒了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.20,0:19:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是不这么做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.88,0:19:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那辆公车上的孩子们就会...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.76,0:19:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候终于还是到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.88,0:19:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.48,0:19:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.00,0:19:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺能干的嘛 被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.48,0:19:51.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.92,0:19:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤 能不能请你跟我走？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.04,0:19:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你找小贤有什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.64,0:20:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在你的身体里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.88,0:20:04.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们所种下的东西已经长出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.00,0:20:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.12,0:20:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不想出现无谓的牺牲的话 就跟我走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.40,0:20:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不凑巧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.92,0:20:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.48,0:20:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没必要向你报上我们的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.24,0:20:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤 你必须跟我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.71,0:20:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.64,0:20:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不在乎这些孩子们会怎么样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.68,0:20:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你们绑架的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.20,0:20:30.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的真是难听
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.92,0:20:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些孩子可是自愿和我们走的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.16,0:20:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...为什么会这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.64,0:20:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.60,0:20:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这我们自然会慢慢告诉你的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.40,0:20:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你肯跟我们走的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小贤！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.20,0:20:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能去！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.44,0:20:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.12,0:20:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是打算联合黑暗势力？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.36,0:20:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪有啊 我可不敢和究极魔兽您老联手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.52,0:20:58.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在做我们该做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.20,0:21:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.52,0:21:04.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要给你们点颜色瞧瞧！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.64,0:21:09.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 小贤 小贤！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.40,0:22:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽的部下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.40,0:22:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女恶魔兽和人面战鹰兽在东京上空展开火拚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地面上 古神兽和海魔兽也在激烈的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.76,0:22:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且 伸向一乘寺贤的魔手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.92,0:22:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神秘的男子——及川的目的是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.96,0:22:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.32,0:22:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「与黑暗系数码兽大决战」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.62,0:23:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}与黑暗系数码兽大决战
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.44,0:22:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
