[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隐藏在孩子们体内的黑暗种子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.16,0:01:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们竭尽全力想找出取出它们的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.48,0:01:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.64,0:01:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在追赶及川的途中 黑暗战斗暴龙兽出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.36,0:01:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽与
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.04,0:01:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗暴龙兽以及帝皇龙甲兽展开了对决
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.96,0:01:58.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗中...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.44,0:02:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽领悟到了一些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.57,0:02:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}黑暗战斗暴龙兽的封印
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.44,0:02:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界中 加布兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.88,0:02:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了阻止像究极魔兽那样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.80,0:02:19.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可自由穿梭于现实世界以及数码世界的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.52,0:02:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在设法关闭光丘的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.40,0:02:25.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.56,0:02:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在现实世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.60,0:02:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目前 对舆论进行控制的政府
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.92,0:02:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就前几日发生的怪兽骚动给予了高度重视
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.84,0:02:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在日前举行的新闻发布会上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.64,0:02:39.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,官方发布了将怪兽当做不明生物处理的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.88,0:02:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,紧急时刻可以出动自卫队
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.84,0:02:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了尽早查明真相
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.84,0:02:47.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,政府方面还准备设立联合调查机构
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.60,0:02:51.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 请各方面全面做好准备
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.40,0:02:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应对突发事件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.12,0:03:04.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.80,0:03:06.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的确听到是从这里传出的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.72,0:03:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么在动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.84,0:03:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.60,0:03:17.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还说话了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.24,0:03:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果冻就在眼前 我忍不住了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.52,0:03:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.44,0:03:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷 一直以来瞒着您
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.28,0:03:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是非常对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.20,0:03:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.52,0:03:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.08,0:03:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？「果然」？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.40,0:03:33.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得这不是普通的布偶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.84,0:03:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫什么穿山兽的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.60,0:03:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是其他数字世界的生物吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.24,0:03:43.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷 你说的「什么数字的世界」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.72,0:03:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你知道数码世界的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.88,0:03:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是叫数码世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.60,0:03:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本来想找个合适的时机告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.68,0:03:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 早就应该告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.76,0:03:59.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实你已故的父亲曾经说过什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.44,0:04:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想去数码世界之类的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.40,0:04:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的父亲？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.92,0:04:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 你的父亲 浩树
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.32,0:04:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从小就对电玩中的角色很感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.68,0:04:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎可以看见别的孩子看不见的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.88,0:04:27.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他坚信一定存在让这些角色自由自在生活的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.00,0:04:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.12,0:04:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和浩树想的一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.40,0:04:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.08,0:04:40.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你今天难道也打算出去？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.64,0:04:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.44,0:04:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.72,0:04:44.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨天和前天也都出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.16,0:04:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生了那么大的骚动就待在家里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.76,0:04:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.04,0:04:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 对不起 但是我今天也...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.08,0:04:55.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,富美子 你担心过头了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.48,0:05:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织今天正打算和我一起进行剑道练习呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.88,0:05:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伊织 快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.48,0:05:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你让我们监视被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.80,0:05:08.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是仍然感觉很讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.28,0:05:12.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过被移植了黑暗种子的孩子们情况很好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.56,0:05:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.36,0:05:15.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.88,0:05:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个孩子想让她的黑暗种子提前发芽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.40,0:05:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该如何行事？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.88,0:05:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来的我都不是真正的我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.56,0:05:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在得到了移植来的黑暗种子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.72,0:05:32.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要让大家见识一下我的真正实力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.44,0:05:35.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,范子 你在干什么 学习吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.36,0:05:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能被肮脏的大人碰到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.52,0:05:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为以后的我将变的越来越完美
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.68,0:05:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 对不起 我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.64,0:05:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 没关系 反正放寒假了 有的是时间
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.68,0:05:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 我们稍微休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.96,0:06:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 那么我去买饮料
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.32,0:06:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉包子也拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.00,0:06:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 肉包子是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.24,0:06:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你放到哪里去了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.28,0:06:16.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明明放在这里的！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.52,0:06:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,范子 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.00,0:06:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉真不好 像在偷听一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.80,0:06:28.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么感觉黑暗力量越来越强大了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.40,0:06:30.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.40,0:06:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的种子好像生长的很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.76,0:06:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你们是被选召的孩子也无济于事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.88,0:06:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 很懊恼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把大家恢复成原来的样子！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.60,0:06:50.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 大家可是自愿接受黑暗种子移植的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.84,0:06:54.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过实现了孩子们的愿望而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.60,0:07:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 你不想成为被大家羡慕的优秀人才吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.72,0:07:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个人是否优秀 不是根据被多少人羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.24,0:07:09.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是根据是否能够帮助大家来决定的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.88,0:07:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说的那些都是错的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.04,0:07:14.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什么眼神啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.44,0:07:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火田...伊织  浩树的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.40,0:07:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么知道爸爸的名字...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.08,0:07:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.84,0:07:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我们不在的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.88,0:07:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家小心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.48,0:07:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我把你们收拾掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.56,0:07:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 走开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.28,0:07:35.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说走开！ 想违抗我的命令？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.72,0:07:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.68,0:07:40.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.60,0:07:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火田...浩树...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.76,0:08:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 我不是那么脆弱的人！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.96,0:08:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不脆弱！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.04,0:08:48.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火田
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.48,0:08:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想给你看这个人造生命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.88,0:08:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可还没来得及给你看你就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.04,0:09:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的遗传基因数字化后制造出的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.12,0:09:02.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.88,0:09:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.68,0:09:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是你真正的形象
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.68,0:09:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真正的形象..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.48,0:09:14.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很丑陋啊 你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.28,0:09:17.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...我很丑陋？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.28,0:09:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不想认同自己的脆弱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.48,0:09:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及自己丑陋的形象
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.68,0:09:24.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么制造出我们？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.00,0:09:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.96,0:09:27.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个异类
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.80,0:09:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.56,0:09:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才为什么不把那些孩子们干掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.00,0:09:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个好机会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.64,0:09:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.48,0:09:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 虽然是与此无关的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.04,0:09:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽说的话 你还记得吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.24,0:09:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽是数码兽而及川先生是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.44,0:09:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可他说我们两边都不是哎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.32,0:09:58.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要想多余的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.44,0:10:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样想下去就没个完了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.08,0:10:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.32,0:10:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.76,0:10:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.76,0:10:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸...不是坏人吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.44,0:10:18.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸怎么可能是坏人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.56,0:10:19.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.56,0:10:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨天遇见一个知道爸爸的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.64,0:10:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,认识浩树的人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.08,0:10:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是叫及川的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.60,0:10:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川？这个名字好像听过
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.24,0:10:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就是一乘寺？找我有什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.24,0:10:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟踪你是我的错 我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.12,0:10:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我希望你可以听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.52,0:10:58.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听你说？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.20,0:11:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要听你这种人说话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.84,0:11:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为你是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.12,0:11:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你现在只不过是个普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.48,0:11:08.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,的确是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.88,0:11:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我觉的现在比以前被称为天才的时候要好得多
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.76,0:11:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会想说什么你交到了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.28,0:11:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且父母也很高兴这种话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.00,0:11:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无聊 愚蠢透顶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.36,0:11:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗种子已经深入她心中的缝隙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.16,0:11:27.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个孩子却没有察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.72,0:11:30.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见 别再跟来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.32,0:11:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你像个跟踪狂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.32,0:11:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.96,0:11:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 那个孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.72,0:11:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.80,0:11:51.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.56,0:11:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.32,0:12:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西从头上出来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.92,0:12:18.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.72,0:12:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 小贤 种子发芽了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.96,0:12:23.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可我只能看见她在发光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.64,0:12:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 发生什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.48,0:12:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开花了...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.72,0:12:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.84,0:12:33.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那帮家伙...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.80,0:12:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.72,0:12:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们准备抢花！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.28,0:12:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.00,0:12:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.92,0:12:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.04,0:12:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.24,0:12:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.04,0:12:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.08,0:13:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.88,0:13:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.20,0:13:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.48,0:13:31.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 如果不把那孩子夺回来...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.84,0:13:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.88,0:13:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.28,0:13:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不准阻扰及川先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.88,0:14:02.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手 机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.40,0:14:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在攻击的话  那个孩子会很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.80,0:14:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你快逃啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.52,0:14:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我需要逃？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.48,0:14:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 已经被及川控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.04,0:14:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个都给我安静的待在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.00,0:14:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川大人 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.52,0:14:21.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 发生什么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.80,0:14:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.56,0:14:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花被吸收了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.88,0:14:27.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须有人去阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.24,0:14:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.40,0:14:28.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.88,0:14:31.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我无法原谅你的所作所为！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.76,0:14:33.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.16,0:14:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这全都是孩子们自己的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.60,0:14:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.04,0:14:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花的能量被吸收了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.80,0:14:48.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她已经没用了 给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.68,0:14:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不要再给我宣扬什么所谓的正义
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.32,0:14:57.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想想如何有效地使用自己的能力不是更好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.68,0:15:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是我父亲朋友的你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.44,0:15:03.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要利用数码兽做坏事！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.48,0:15:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.48,0:15:10.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太像了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.88,0:15:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这双充满正义的眼睛和浩树的太像了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.56,0:15:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浩树...那个家伙已经不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.60,0:15:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那才那孩子黑暗之花的力量变成了他身后的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.48,0:15:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能力大大增强了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.36,0:15:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.24,0:15:38.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.88,0:15:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你为所欲为的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.44,0:15:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑盖亚能量炮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.80,0:15:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这究竟是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.76,0:15:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笼罩着及川的影子的能力同
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.44,0:15:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽的黑暗力量相撞
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.52,0:15:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,形势有所转变
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.84,0:16:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽 你打算做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.04,0:16:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 我只是在用我的方式处理问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.84,0:16:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川 我找你有事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.72,0:16:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还在四处彷徨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.72,0:16:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正好 我正想利用造出你的黑暗之塔的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.32,0:16:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.60,0:16:21.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会再让你胡作非为了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.72,0:16:23.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要阻止你！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.04,0:16:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是个人造作品的你能做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.92,0:16:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么你又为什么制造出了亚基利兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.84,0:16:31.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么制造了木乃伊兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.84,0:16:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那么讨厌孤独吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.92,0:16:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 不是的不是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.20,0:16:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那么脆弱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 在苦恼些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.76,0:16:47.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说 那个家伙是伊织父亲的朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.04,0:16:48.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.16,0:16:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像发展成不可收拾的局面了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.16,0:16:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽打算对及川做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.68,0:16:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.16,0:17:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要力量吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.80,0:17:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要想从孤独的包围中脱身
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.84,0:17:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么做是无济于事的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.16,0:17:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你集合了所以的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.76,0:17:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以随意支配世间万物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.76,0:17:13.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也只是让你更为孤单
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.44,0:17:15.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.28,0:17:21.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思来晚了 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.68,0:17:24.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是及川悠纪夫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.44,0:17:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然以前你是寡言少语朋友不多的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.32,0:17:31.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.88,0:17:32.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.16,0:17:35.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织的爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.32,0:17:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或者说是你的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.88,0:17:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火田浩树的爸爸比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.60,0:17:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浩树的父亲？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.00,0:17:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们似乎坚信让游戏角色自由生活的世界存在着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.32,0:17:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我对那样的儿子感到不安
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.08,0:17:59.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并禁止他说那些不着边际的梦话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.28,0:18:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时他那悲伤的表情直到现在我还记得
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.80,0:18:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.72,0:18:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,长大后的你们仍然相信数字世界的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.76,0:18:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两个人做着自己的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.96,0:18:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而浩树却突然过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.72,0:18:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当时的你不是一般的消沉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.60,0:18:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想想这其实也是理所当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.72,0:18:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为对你而言 能称为朋友的只有浩树一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.80,0:18:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那时 我想尽我所能帮助你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.84,0:18:38.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在说这些也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.88,0:18:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能否成为我的朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.44,0:18:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想找个人陪我说说浩树小时候的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.68,0:18:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和浩树在一起的时光...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.88,0:18:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.96,0:19:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险！爷爷！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.88,0:19:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快逃！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.92,0:19:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.92,0:19:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保护了爷爷...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.28,0:19:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.68,0:19:24.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是你...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.76,0:19:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你...这个「你」到底指的是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.32,0:19:38.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 果然我只能独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.48,0:19:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来 并且今后也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.20,0:19:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以...被那家伙支配的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.88,0:19:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我必须收集所有的黑暗种子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.68,0:19:51.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了实现我的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.00,0:19:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了去数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.36,0:20:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行...绝对...不能让那家伙肆意妄为...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.00,0:20:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.28,0:20:06.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难...难道黑暗战斗暴龙兽被打倒了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.88,0:20:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的身体已经不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.12,0:20:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用黑暗之塔制造出的这条命也就此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.92,0:20:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 还有我能够做到的事！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.92,0:20:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别再说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.52,0:20:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这身体一定可以封印从光丘通往数码世界的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.24,0:20:26.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你打算干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.76,0:20:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽有没有找到他的答案呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.84,0:20:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 一定的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.92,0:20:46.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.20,0:20:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.84,0:20:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.84,0:20:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗战斗暴龙兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.12,0:20:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连接数码世界和光丘的大门被封住了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.96,0:21:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,封印是建立在黑暗战斗暴龙兽的牺牲上的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.56,0:22:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通往数码世界的大门被封印了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.60,0:22:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 被黑暗力量控制的及川把门打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.12,0:22:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在无人知道的现实世界及数码世界的夹缝中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.20,0:22:50.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色的影子苏醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.92,0:22:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是曾经的敌人 吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.40,0:22:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.60,0:22:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「恐怖！贝利亚吸血魔兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}恐怖！贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:23:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
