[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.52,0:01:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被选召的孩子们分散在了世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.72,0:01:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅去了美美所在的纽约
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎和小光去了香港
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.04,0:01:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遥远的其他国家里也有很多被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.04,0:01:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了让凶恶的数码兽复原
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.28,0:01:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,四个人和全世界被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.32,0:01:57.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功的将数码兽们送回了数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.88,0:02:01.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时 在悉尼和巴黎...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.28,0:02:09.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,330)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}大堡礁 凡尔赛大混战！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.62,0:02:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,435)}{\fn黑体}{\fad(600,0)}澳大利亚      黄金海岸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.92,0:02:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.96,0:02:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽 打倒黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.52,0:02:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鱼叉机关炮
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.04,0:02:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.96,0:02:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明是圣诞节 澳大利亚还真热呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.44,0:02:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和日本不同 南半球现在是夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.00,0:02:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.72,0:02:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 接下来我们用身子把它拉倒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.80,0:02:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.04,0:02:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.40,0:02:50.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真是和平呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.68,0:02:51.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.28,0:02:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,澳大利亚的人们并不知道地球陷入危机了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.32,0:03:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这样的东西突然出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.32,0:03:03.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道也不觉得奇怪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.60,0:03:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算像澳大利亚人人抱怨也没用啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.20,0:03:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 快点把黑暗之塔弄到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.60,0:03:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 阿丈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.92,0:03:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一二一二...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.52,0:03:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也来帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.60,0:03:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有黑暗之塔在这里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.56,0:03:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人们也无法过个愉快的圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.24,0:03:26.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿泳衣的圣诞老人！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.08,0:03:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 要开始拉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.60,0:03:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一二一二...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.08,0:03:35.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.16,0:03:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Merry Christmas！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.36,0:03:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.08,0:03:40.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能只顾着高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.00,0:03:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在澳大利亚的其他被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.00,0:03:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在努力把数码兽们引向大碉堡残余的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.40,0:03:50.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玄内先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.92,0:03:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是玄内的同伴 有加利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.64,0:04:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命...救命...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.52,0:03:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.32,0:04:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是在被鲨鱼追吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.84,0:04:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子带着数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:06.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多半是和你们一样的被选召的孩子们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.08,0:04:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是在被数码兽追赶！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.88,0:04:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墨鱼兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.68,0:04:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝壳兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.44,0:04:18.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龙虾兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.16,0:04:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墨鱼兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.00,0:04:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝壳兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.76,0:04:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龙虾兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.80,0:04:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是什锦海鲜吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.24,0:04:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 就用这个冲上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.76,0:04:28.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「就用这个冲上去」？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.32,0:04:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.36,0:04:31.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是要用什锦海鲜攻击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.24,0:04:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Oh！ My god
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.76,0:04:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢着！ 澳大利亚被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.00,0:04:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将由我们来保护！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.08,0:04:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,This is the digi-destiny Dingo of Australia
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.08,0:04:58.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他说他的名字叫丁戈 还有...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.36,0:05:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨蟹兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.32,0:05:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜好恶作剧的甲壳类数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.80,0:05:06.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「绞手处刑」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.76,0:05:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是自我介绍的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.12,0:05:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是哦 海狮兽 给我上！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.68,0:05:15.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,墨鱼兽！ 贝壳兽！ 龙虾兽！ 你们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.84,0:05:18.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等着被我做成数码兽什锦披萨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.68,0:05:19.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.48,0:05:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海鲜...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.48,0:05:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大杂烩...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.04,0:05:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,披萨？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.76,0:05:29.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 该你上了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.72,0:05:33.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你们做成数码兽什锦海鲜炒饭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.28,0:05:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.96,0:05:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海鲜...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.40,0:05:38.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大杂烩...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.24,0:05:39.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,炒饭？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.92,0:05:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.28,0:05:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊！ 我明白他们的弱点了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.24,0:05:48.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨蟹兽 你也上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.04,0:05:52.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要把你们做成数码兽什锦海鲜咖喱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.20,0:05:56.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽什锦海鲜咖喱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.32,0:06:00.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饶命...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.60,0:06:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站住 数码兽什锦海鲜...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.64,0:06:05.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,披萨！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.16,0:06:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,炒饭！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.00,0:06:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咖喱！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.48,0:06:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 他们正在向大堡礁的方向逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.64,0:06:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去我们可以追上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.88,0:06:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是大堡礁了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.44,0:06:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.56,0:06:31.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是黑暗之塔！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.64,0:06:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽什锦海鲜的事情以后再说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.20,0:06:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先集合大家的力量打倒黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.84,0:06:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回来吧 海狮兽 快回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.52,0:06:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得救了...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.12,0:06:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚路加兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.92,0:07:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚路加兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.92,0:07:06.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是完全体！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.76,0:07:08.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽 超进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.32,0:07:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海狮兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.12,0:07:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祖顿兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.04,0:07:35.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁刺杀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.96,0:07:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚礁会被破坏掉的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.08,0:07:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样子下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.04,0:07:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大堡礁的珊瑚礁会被弄的一片狼藉的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.04,0:07:51.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祖顿兽！去海里！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.48,0:07:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海里的话 就看我们的了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.92,0:08:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.04,0:08:09.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.28,0:08:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永不止息的诚实 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.44,0:08:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨蟹兽 你可别落后！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.32,0:08:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨蟹兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.76,0:08:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,西拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.76,0:08:38.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,西拉兽 拥有坚硬外壳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.48,0:08:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鳍和手脚一样灵活的古代鱼型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.60,0:08:43.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「多变夺命镖」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.72,0:08:47.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜鲨兽 把亚路加兽从珊瑚礁旁边拖走
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.12,0:08:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.12,0:09:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜行攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.56,0:09:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚路加兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.00,0:09:11.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来做诱饵 把那家伙引开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.40,0:09:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.16,0:09:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重锤火花
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.92,0:09:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高压氧气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.64,0:09:34.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.64,0:09:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的被打倒了吗？该不会...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.24,0:09:38.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.84,0:09:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是晕过去罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.72,0:09:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.96,0:09:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来只要打倒黑暗之塔就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.08,0:09:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多变夺命镖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.20,0:10:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其他澳大利亚被选召的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.68,0:10:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也把数码兽带到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.28,0:10:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把数码兽送回数码世界吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.60,0:10:27.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界大门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.48,0:11:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,435)}{\fn黑体}法国      巴黎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.28,0:11:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴黎的圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.84,0:11:08.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和东京比起来要冷很多呢 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.48,0:11:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.48,0:11:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他真的会来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.28,0:11:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那位住在巴黎叫米歇尔的法国人 就是阿岳的爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.84,0:11:20.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他让我们在凯旋门的前面等的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.12,0:11:21.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为他肯定会来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.80,0:11:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是「认为」可不行啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.32,0:11:27.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们对巴黎可是一无所知啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.32,0:11:30.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要一心想着解救地球的危机就没有问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.00,0:11:33.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是摩托车的引擎声
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.96,0:11:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是摩托车！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.48,0:11:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.48,0:11:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.72,0:11:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.84,0:11:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才是用法语和你说「圣诞快乐」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.48,0:11:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都说了现在不是过圣诞节的时候啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.84,0:11:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再不快点找到数码兽 会出大事的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.48,0:11:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的 是整个地球的危机吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.16,0:12:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 奶奶怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.40,0:12:08.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在圣诞派对中喝了太多葡萄酒醉的不省人事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.28,0:12:11.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也没有叫她让她睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.20,0:12:13.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷真是温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.16,0:12:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.48,0:12:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候夜晚的巴黎 真的很平静
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.44,0:12:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让人想不到地球的危机正在迫近
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.80,0:12:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到早上了就可以发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.28,0:12:25.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,煞风景的黑暗之塔耸立着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.20,0:12:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失去方向的数码兽们到处出没
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.80,0:12:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这会变成一个出人意料的圣诞节呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.92,0:12:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此 在太阳出来之前不把黑暗之塔打倒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.48,0:12:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并把数码兽们送回数码世界的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.00,0:12:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.92,0:12:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.88,0:12:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪...怎么都觉得...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.56,0:12:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.80,0:12:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,凡尔赛宫的门开着！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.08,0:13:02.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且都这个时候了 还开着灯...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.68,0:13:06.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是圣诞派对呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.40,0:13:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.28,0:13:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在凡尔赛宫谁敢开派对狂欢啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.28,0:13:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不用那么生气嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.20,0:13:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.00,0:13:14.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.32,0:13:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是快去找黑暗之塔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.40,0:13:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行！作为一个正直的巴黎市民
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:21.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能对这种事袖手旁观！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.72,0:13:23.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 地球的危机怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.20,0:13:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保护凡尔赛宫是法国公民的义务！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.88,0:13:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Vive Frances！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.96,0:13:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷！你这样可是非法入侵啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.12,0:13:32.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.16,0:13:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于在巴黎土生土长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.00,0:13:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从小把凡尔赛宫当自家后院玩的我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.56,0:13:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小菜一碟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.32,0:13:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.68,0:13:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.04,0:13:45.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然 不叫你爷爷过来是不是会好一些？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.84,0:13:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,额...这话...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 闭嘴给我跟上来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.84,0:14:02.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.52,0:14:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.88,0:14:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆豆兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.88,0:14:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身体很小却拥有恐怖的破坏力的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.20,0:14:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突变型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.76,0:14:20.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「微笑炸弹」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.04,0:14:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们醉的不轻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.16,0:14:24.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨大豆豆兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.24,0:14:28.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比普通巨大豆豆兽大数十倍的突变型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.56,0:14:30.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「巨大微笑炸弹」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.04,0:14:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些数码兽长的还真像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.04,0:14:34.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁豆豆兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.16,0:14:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是比豆豆兽还要强力的机器人型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「能量炸弹」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.52,0:14:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是豆豆兽三兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.60,0:14:46.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些就是使地球陷入危机的数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.72,0:14:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群混蛋...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.92,0:14:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然私自进入凡尔赛宫开宴会...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.20,0:14:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我记住！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.92,0:14:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷 冷静一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.40,0:14:54.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.36,0:14:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像还有其他人在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.40,0:15:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.00,0:15:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.48,0:15:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.24,0:15:14.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,带着数码兽 也就是说...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.08,0:15:17.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她是法国被选召的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.88,0:15:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩就由我 米歇尔来救出
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.80,0:15:23.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,豆豆兽三兄弟！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.16,0:15:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.92,0:15:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是几颗豆子 却闯入凡尔赛宫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.00,0:15:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太不像话了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.56,0:15:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种罪行我不会饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.24,0:15:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.04,0:15:36.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我 巴黎社交界的名士 米歇尔前来救你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.08,0:15:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 这个老头 一个人自言自语的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.48,0:15:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接招！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.60,0:15:45.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.32,0:16:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.52,0:16:11.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.12,0:16:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.88,0:16:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.96,0:16:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到外面决胜负！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.96,0:16:43.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不准破坏宫殿！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.20,0:16:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.28,0:16:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超级火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.84,0:16:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能量炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.68,0:17:04.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真壮观！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.72,0:17:07.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.40,0:17:09.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.92,0:17:11.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的非常感谢你们救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.35,0:17:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫卡特莉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.56,0:17:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是法国被选召的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.35,0:17:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你会说日语？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.83,0:17:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我会说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.92,0:17:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 为什么你会被抓住呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.24,0:17:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.16,0:17:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了打倒突然出现在塞纳河畔的黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.80,0:17:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和花拉兽刚到塞纳河畔...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.52,0:17:34.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过敏喷雾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.20,0:17:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,清醒过来 已经被抓并被带到凡尔赛宫来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.92,0:17:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.36,0:17:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了豆豆兽三兄弟还有其他人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.04,0:17:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.04,0:17:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,炮弹兽 机器型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.12,0:17:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是「死亡炮弹」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.88,0:18:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能量炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.92,0:18:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我揍我揍我揍我揍...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.08,0:18:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡炮弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.16,0:18:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨大微笑炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.04,0:18:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敌人是完全体 这样下去打不过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.64,0:18:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙兽 我们也变成完全体
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.92,0:18:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 冲啊 天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.00,0:18:22.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花拉兽也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.40,0:18:29.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.52,0:18:45.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.04,0:18:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.40,0:18:59.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.12,0:19:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花拉兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.84,0:19:15.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇鸟兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.08,0:19:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鸟啄击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.76,0:19:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快逃！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.48,0:19:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.24,0:19:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把这帮家伙赶到有黑暗之塔的塞纳河畔去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.04,0:19:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极破坏炮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.36,0:20:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.52,0:20:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 之后只需把数码兽们送回数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.32,0:20:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,法国被选召的孩子把数码兽们诱导来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.44,0:20:21.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地球的危机被解决了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.24,0:20:25.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.76,0:20:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.36,0:20:31.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.80,0:20:33.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.64,0:20:40.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,考试考的怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.12,0:20:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一般般吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.64,0:20:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全不行...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.88,0:20:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.52,0:20:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕 可是她似乎可以理解我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.44,0:21:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎可以实现我的愿望...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,留下的地点只有两个了 墨西哥和俄罗斯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.28,0:22:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿和与小贤把迷茫的数码兽聚集成一个庞大的数字
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.20,0:22:47.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京和阿空以及俄罗斯被选召的孩子组成了游击队
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.64,0:22:49.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是迎接他们的却分别是...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.04,0:22:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的女孩和暴风雪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.80,0:22:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.28,0:22:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「爱与红菜汤的大激战！」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:22:58.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}爱与红菜汤的大激战！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.52,0:22:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
