[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.16,0:01:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于开始行动的亚基利兽和木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.52,0:01:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅诱拐了许多孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.44,0:01:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还在大辅的面前带走了一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.52,0:01:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,另一方面
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.84,0:01:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来自于黑暗世界的究极魔兽他们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也把小贤当成目标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.16,0:02:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们的目的究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.99,0:02:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}与黑暗系数码兽大决战
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.52,0:02:14.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！把一乘寺还给我们！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.20,0:02:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为能追上吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.48,0:02:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.20,0:02:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.92,0:02:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 快点上车
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.24,0:02:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丈学长的哥哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.28,0:02:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.24,0:02:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要担心 我们一定会把一乘寺救出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.68,0:02:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.08,0:02:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这和约定好的不一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.16,0:02:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说的不一样指的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.04,0:02:51.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是约定好要把大家放了的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.44,0:02:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得有做过这样的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.68,0:02:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 你们想回家吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.28,0:03:00.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.80,0:03:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是一乘寺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.48,0:03:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.40,0:03:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然 我一直很崇拜你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.52,0:03:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,学习那么好 运动又万能 真是完美无缺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.40,0:03:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后来 这个叔叔说可以实现我的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.28,0:03:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.28,0:03:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人羡慕啊 能被大家崇拜着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.20,0:03:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.28,0:03:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.56,0:03:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.68,0:03:38.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是过分 我以为你还记得我的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.48,0:03:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在你哥哥的葬礼上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.08,0:03:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哥哥的葬礼上？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.80,0:03:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们见过面吧 不记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.80,0:04:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想起来了...但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.68,0:04:12.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货 给我好好开车！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.00,0:04:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.60,0:04:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么要求...                                         你在干什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.00,0:04:16.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么要求...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.12,0:04:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为可以逃出究极魔兽大人的手心吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.92,0:04:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.88,0:04:34.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是女恶魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.12,0:04:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请把车停下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.52,0:04:39.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 麻鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.12,0:04:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我想说「就算只有我一个人也要战斗」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.24,0:04:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是在刚才的战斗中失去了进化成天女兽的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.48,0:04:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以和我合体进化吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.52,0:04:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是无所谓...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.56,0:04:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 小京
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.92,0:05:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是阻止她...万一...又像刚才一样...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.16,0:05:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在无辜的人受到牵连之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.48,0:05:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.44,0:05:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们几个先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.48,0:05:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心一点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.04,0:05:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.48,0:05:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.72,0:05:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.40,0:05:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.60,0:05:34.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.16,0:05:36.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.64,0:05:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.24,0:05:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.92,0:05:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是及川
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.44,0:06:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川悠纪夫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.00,0:06:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你爸爸的同事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.48,0:06:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.52,0:06:10.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在葬礼上你悲痛动摇 这也是没办法的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这么说你觉得如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.00,0:06:19.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对你而言 你哥哥的死只是意外
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.84,0:06:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那封邮件...是你...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.72,0:06:29.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你终于想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.12,0:06:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我一直很担心你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.72,0:06:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底打算干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.48,0:06:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.72,0:06:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.92,0:06:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.00,0:06:53.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙是我的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也可以说是我的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.60,0:07:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们有些得意忘形了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.80,0:07:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.68,0:07:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.44,0:07:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川悠纪夫 你到底是什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.56,0:07:08.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 只差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.56,0:07:16.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.56,0:07:19.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的丧尸撒旦兽和女恶魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.96,0:07:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和亚基利兽他们到底是什么关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.64,0:07:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.80,0:07:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,血蝙蝠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.44,0:07:29.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.84,0:07:35.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是缠人的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.00,0:07:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像拍电影一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.24,0:07:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去万一出什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.52,0:07:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会被吊销驾照的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.96,0:07:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 还差一点点了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.24,0:07:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是平交道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.28,0:07:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马上会被拦住了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.36,0:08:08.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 快点！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.24,0:08:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来 等列车通过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.16,0:08:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.32,0:08:23.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 冲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.20,0:08:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话 还能追上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.12,0:08:28.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.28,0:09:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,移植一结束马上就出发 知道了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:02.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.20,0:09:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是我？为什么非选我不可？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.96,0:09:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在葬礼上第一次看到你的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.60,0:09:16.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,心肝震动了下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.40,0:09:19.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你的身上被种下了黑暗的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.32,0:09:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗的种子」？那到底是什么东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.36,0:09:27.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以让你的脑子变聪明 增强运动神经
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.84,0:09:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多作用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.68,0:09:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和这些孩子也谈过了 关于黑暗的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.92,0:09:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果大家都很想要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.28,0:09:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想要你来协助我们一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.72,0:09:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你身体里的种子也应该发芽了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.36,0:09:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要把苗拿走移植到大家身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.00,0:09:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.08,0:09:56.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这是询问 还是纯粹的命令？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.96,0:10:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 一点都不痛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.72,0:10:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的种子说到底也只是堆数据而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.88,0:10:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 就由不得你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.08,0:10:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.76,0:10:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫...虫虫兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.60,0:10:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.80,0:10:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音速二重击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.04,0:11:11.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 下一个是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.68,0:11:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.12,0:11:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 各位 你们都被骗了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.88,0:11:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以变成像我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.80,0:11:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有听见？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.28,0:11:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.20,0:11:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是星星的私语
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.56,0:11:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,星星在这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.92,0:11:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「可以和你在一起一定是今生的命运」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.04,0:11:40.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可什么都没听见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.20,0:11:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 亚基利兽 接受命运吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.40,0:11:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.04,0:11:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.16,0:11:49.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这广阔的世界中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.36,0:11:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你再也找不到比我更适合你的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.56,0:11:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到星星就自我陶醉的人不是我喜欢的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.20,0:11:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么你喜欢什么类型的男人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.76,0:12:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我吧 我会努力成为那样的男人的...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.68,0:12:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不变成那个样子也没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.28,0:12:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.44,0:12:18.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你该不会是害怕过山车吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.76,0:12:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是那个...那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.60,0:12:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.32,0:12:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是受欢迎啊 那么多人都想得到你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.76,0:12:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行 请掉头回去吧 前方禁止进入
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.80,0:12:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是因为工程吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.12,0:12:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 我们正在追卡车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.60,0:12:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请问你有没有看见呢 是这个样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.20,0:12:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是说这个的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.88,0:12:56.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快追啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.48,0:12:57.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 快点！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.08,0:13:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 这样子...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.24,0:13:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.44,0:13:05.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.60,0:13:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是海魔兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.92,0:13:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我去追卡车
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.24,0:13:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.28,0:13:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码之心 升级
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.48,0:13:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽 装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.96,0:13:45.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坚固的友情 雷龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.04,0:13:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽 跟我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.08,0:13:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们去解决海魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.44,0:13:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要杀掉他吗？我...那种事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.08,0:14:04.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的车！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.52,0:14:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的贷款！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.88,0:14:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.04,0:14:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.28,0:14:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.76,0:14:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.84,0:14:29.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.96,0:14:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.20,0:14:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.44,0:14:43.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.36,0:14:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事...怎么办...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.76,0:14:52.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.40,0:14:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发光了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.00,0:14:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.88,0:14:59.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又有了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.12,0:15:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.00,0:15:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,血蝙蝠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.96,0:15:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.80,0:15:21.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神魂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.12,0:15:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的战斗对手在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.68,0:15:37.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.04,0:15:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 可以阻止海魔兽的只有你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.24,0:15:53.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.00,0:15:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.08,0:15:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 快逃！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.16,0:16:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个姐姐的衣服好特别啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.04,0:16:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里很危险 请快点逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.48,0:16:09.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险？指什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.92,0:16:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.40,0:16:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要请你做我的盾牌唷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.72,0:16:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 有什么绝招尽管使出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.56,0:16:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个方向是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.00,0:16:35.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.32,0:16:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是光丘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.76,0:16:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光丘？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.04,0:16:42.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是小光和太一学长首次遇到数码兽的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.52,0:16:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里好像有通往数码世界的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.64,0:16:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道亚基利兽他们也知道这件事才...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.64,0:16:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光丘啊 真是讽刺的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.32,0:16:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不明白它的意思吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.32,0:17:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是发光的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.40,0:17:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如叫「暗丘」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.68,0:17:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个不好听
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.48,0:17:07.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 叫「黑暗丘」怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.40,0:17:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不不 「黑丘」怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:16.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那目光 是轻藐的眼神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.64,0:17:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们好好学着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.07,0:17:23.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精英俯视庸人的时候就是这种眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.16,0:17:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你给我反击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.32,0:17:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可不能对这个家伙见死不救哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.28,0:17:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 我不想死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.60,0:17:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不攻过来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.76,0:17:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么差不多该给你最后一击了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.52,0:17:50.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,血...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.36,0:17:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.20,0:17:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卑鄙的家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.56,0:18:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我见过的数码兽中 你是最卑鄙的一个！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.96,0:18:01.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最差劲！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.72,0:18:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 别乱来！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.40,0:18:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卑鄙！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.88,0:18:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是我生存的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.76,0:18:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且我非常冷酷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.96,0:18:15.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算对你这种孩子 我也不会手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.32,0:18:17.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.96,0:18:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.08,0:18:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不打倒她...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.44,0:18:39.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请理解我...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.52,0:18:42.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,杀了...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.72,0:18:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.16,0:18:46.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒了啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.24,0:18:53.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别哭了 已经没事了...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.12,0:18:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救了那个人的是小京哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.48,0:19:14.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,医院？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.16,0:19:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 里面可能还有行动不便的患者
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.00,0:19:22.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽 离这里远一点！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.56,0:19:28.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办...怎么办才好...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.96,0:19:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之 先做我们力所能及的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.56,0:19:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到放弃做医生的我会做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.04,0:19:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够救人的不仅仅是医生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.92,0:19:50.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是警官的爸爸 也救过别人的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.12,0:19:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.04,0:19:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒御魂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.80,0:20:04.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.92,0:20:09.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于还是打倒了敌人...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.76,0:20:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.04,0:20:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.96,0:20:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我还有急事就失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.44,0:20:17.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.00,0:20:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.84,0:20:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.68,0:20:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我这么做对吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.96,0:20:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！ 真是难缠！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.64,0:20:39.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷龙兽 加把劲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我把你们甩下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.32,0:20:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个抓紧我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.72,0:20:55.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是顽固的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.32,0:20:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.20,0:21:02.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙是...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.80,0:21:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.60,0:22:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖的黑暗世界的魔王 究极魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.08,0:22:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那压倒性的强大连帝皇龙甲兽也抵不过他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.32,0:22:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且他还可以自己打开大门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.24,0:22:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无路可走 近乎绝望的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.40,0:22:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的记忆苏醒 孩子们只能背水一战
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.52,0:22:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.72,0:22:57.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗的大门」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.82,0:22:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
