[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.92,0:01:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了自己想去数码世界的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.12,0:01:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于打开了大门的及川悠纪夫
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.92,0:01:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 那里并不是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.00,0:01:46.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从失意的及川身上破体而出的贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.92,0:01:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用意识的恐怖残杀了亚基利兽和木乃伊兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.40,0:01:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳等人被恐怖吓倒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.12,0:01:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仅有大辅和V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.96,0:02:01.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站出来勇敢地与贝利亚吸血魔兽战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.07,0:02:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}最后一次装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.96,0:02:18.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.44,0:02:20.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有V仔兽EX是不可能赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.52,0:02:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这种话 我们一定要赢！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.28,0:02:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来我们都坚信此事磨练过来的！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.88,0:02:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以现在在这里输掉！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.60,0:02:34.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 我们不会输的！ 绝对不会输的！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.16,0:02:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.80,0:02:41.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有效...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.84,0:02:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击有效！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.96,0:02:49.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量居然提升了...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.36,0:02:54.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊！ V仔兽EX！ 再来一次X光线！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.80,0:02:55.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.04,0:02:58.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,思忆幻象！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.24,0:03:06.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.88,0:03:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好慢哦 阿岳 来 快坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.76,0:03:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天爸爸和哥哥都回来的好早哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.36,0:03:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？这些蛋糕一个人独吞真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.48,0:03:34.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈 Bingo  Bingo  Bingo！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.52,0:03:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 这里是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.88,0:03:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和爸爸现在正一起在数码世界散步啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.28,0:03:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.20,0:04:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.40,0:04:04.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.84,0:04:05.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.44,0:04:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.28,0:04:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的猫猫兽能不能也快点变成迪路兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.16,0:04:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢猫猫兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.64,0:04:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常喜欢！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.28,0:04:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么没问题 一定很快就可以变成迪路兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.48,0:04:30.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.28,0:04:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？巴达兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:35.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳 这样就足够了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.56,0:04:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.32,0:04:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳还没有察觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.76,0:04:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你在说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.72,0:04:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难得家人终于聚齐...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.76,0:04:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 怎么了？ 大家要去哪里？我们一起！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.00,0:04:53.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.52,0:04:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是现实
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西不是现实！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.04,0:05:02.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.12,0:05:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.72,0:05:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你觉察到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.96,0:05:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯~~好吃~~幸福~~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.92,0:05:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.28,0:05:16.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就足够了吗 小京？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.92,0:05:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽也要吃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.72,0:05:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个人吃东西很快乐吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.32,0:05:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 当然很快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.12,0:05:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.00,0:05:36.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为小京有很多兄弟姐妹 一直很热闹
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.08,0:05:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以偶尔也会希望可以一个人安静一会儿吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.84,0:05:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 其实只是想一个人待一小会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.68,0:05:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并不是想永远孤独一人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.20,0:05:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽总是能理解我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.84,0:05:57.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次我好想多了解一下麻鹰兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.36,0:05:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.44,0:06:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这让我有点害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.64,0:06:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京 我来接你了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.80,0:06:11.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.60,0:06:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 你去哪里了啊？ 我刚才还在找你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.52,0:06:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织 不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.12,0:06:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「不是这样的」是指什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.76,0:06:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.24,0:06:25.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你今天好奇怪哦 穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.04,0:06:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.88,0:06:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.60,0:06:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让他去吧 伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.84,0:06:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.48,0:06:51.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然至今为止我都瞒着妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.32,0:06:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去后想把穿山兽介绍给妈妈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.72,0:06:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会不会大吃一惊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.28,0:07:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会吃惊的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.60,0:07:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.16,0:07:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.64,0:07:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在等呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.88,0:07:12.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.52,0:07:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.48,0:07:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在开心的和数码兽嬉戏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.00,0:07:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.76,0:07:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.48,0:07:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「但是」？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.76,0:07:25.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光必须要自己意识到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.24,0:07:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家...友好的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.56,0:07:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.88,0:07:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这...不是现实！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.56,0:07:49.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷龙兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.08,0:07:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来接你了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.36,0:07:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了让这样的生活有朝一日到来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.04,0:07:57.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们必须打倒贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.68,0:08:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.84,0:08:01.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.56,0:08:05.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的未来只能靠我们的双手去获取
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.76,0:08:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.44,0:08:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.84,0:08:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴龙改造者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.24,0:08:53.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该不会 该不会...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.32,0:09:00.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是个残忍的人！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.96,0:09:04.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你 令多少数码兽留下了痛苦的回忆！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.88,0:09:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们要鞭打你 因你而死的数码兽的痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.56,0:09:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你也好好尝尝！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.72,0:09:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智哥哥...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你已经足够痛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.36,0:10:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的赎罪已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.68,0:10:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不用赎罪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.68,0:10:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结束了...结束了啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.52,0:10:12.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 这样可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.44,0:10:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总是纠结于过去 可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.88,0:10:17.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是还有现在必须要做的事情吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.44,0:10:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在必须要做的事...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.72,0:10:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在必须要做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.20,0:10:26.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在必须要做的事！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.72,0:10:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊！ 现在不是因为过去的罪而苦恼的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.44,0:10:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要尽快想办法去救被移植了黑暗种子的孩子们！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.96,0:10:41.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为此我现在必须要做的事情是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.24,0:10:44.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒贝利亚吸血魔兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.04,0:10:45.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.88,0:10:47.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.36,0:10:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.80,0:10:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒那个家伙 一切都从这里开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.20,0:10:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.44,0:10:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.96,0:11:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道小贤一直以来付出的努力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.48,0:11:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以只差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.20,0:11:04.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.64,0:11:05.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.52,0:11:08.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经流逝的过去无法抹消
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.48,0:11:11.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是可以克服它
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.76,0:11:13.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.84,0:11:14.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.24,0:11:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起战斗吧 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.64,0:11:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.28,0:11:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是伙伴！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.76,0:11:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来了 贝利亚吸血魔兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.20,0:11:33.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.16,0:11:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰拳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.92,0:11:35.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蓝轰雷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.68,0:11:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.28,0:11:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击很有效...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.48,0:11:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时出现的V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.48,0:11:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽和雷龙兽不是幻觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.24,0:11:52.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是「想打倒他 想变的更为强大」的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.88,0:11:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后V仔兽EX就突然力量提升（Power Up）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.60,0:11:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽和雷龙兽就出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.88,0:12:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难不成是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.12,0:12:05.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界一定是以思想为力量的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.52,0:12:07.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要上了 巴达兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.32,0:12:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会输给黑暗力量！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.00,0:12:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽 装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.48,0:12:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽超进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.60,0:12:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巴达兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.68,0:12:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔的希望 天马兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.12,0:12:33.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.88,0:12:34.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.36,0:12:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.48,0:12:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天堂之拳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.16,0:12:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,流星光线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.80,0:12:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 我们也上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.00,0:12:44.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.48,0:12:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能输 不能输 不能输！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.24,0:12:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽 装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.24,0:13:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻鹰兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.52,0:13:07.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍动的爱心之翼 铁鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.47,0:13:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.68,0:13:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,泉涌般的纯真 忍者兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.72,0:13:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲击镭射
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.80,0:13:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴风之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.12,0:13:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,草薙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.20,0:13:22.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.24,0:13:24.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要大干一场
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.52,0:13:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夺取玩弄他人的心的人 绝对不可原谅！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.96,0:13:37.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽 装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.76,0:13:43.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,穿山兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.92,0:13:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永不止息的诚实 潜鲨兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.35,0:13:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.48,0:13:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢铁般的睿智 钢钻兽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.76,0:13:54.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金钻冲击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.00,0:13:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜行攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.52,0:14:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,锁链尾锤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.24,0:14:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.32,0:14:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了未来！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.84,0:14:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了未来 我们绝对不能输！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.36,0:14:14.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽超进化...\N迪路兽装甲进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.84,0:14:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光明的微笑 尼菲迪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.23,0:14:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天女兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.32,0:14:33.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,罗塞塔之石
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.84,0:14:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神圣弓箭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.44,0:14:42.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.40,0:14:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧 小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.20,0:14:49.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.76,0:14:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:14:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终结刺钉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.72,0:15:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些可恶的小鬼们...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.36,0:15:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我才不会就这么被打败！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.40,0:15:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经用愿望的力量取胜了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.32,0:15:17.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能在这里被你们打败！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.32,0:15:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无情融化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.16,0:15:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽！\N战甲兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.84,0:15:24.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.56,0:15:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.32,0:15:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.72,0:15:40.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.60,0:15:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽！\N亚古拉兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.48,0:15:45.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚古拉兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.48,0:15:48.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪路兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.40,0:15:53.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.64,0:15:56.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.48,0:16:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.68,0:16:04.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽！\NV仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.80,0:16:07.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.44,0:16:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.12,0:16:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.80,0:16:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.64,0:16:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.04,0:16:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来不会再让你胡作非为了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.16,0:16:34.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽究极进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.96,0:16:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们 为了未来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.44,0:16:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽 改变形态
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.76,0:16:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战士形态！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.08,0:17:05.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽！ 是你输了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.88,0:17:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.52,0:17:11.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是大家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.52,0:17:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借助这个世界不可思议的力量所创造的现实
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.00,0:17:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 若没有直到最后都深信
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.40,0:17:21.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决不放弃就不会输的 大辅那直率的心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.72,0:17:24.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有大辅那热切的心的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.64,0:17:27.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定不会得到这样的力量的！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.76,0:17:29.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 为什么是大辅？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.20,0:17:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是叫本宫大辅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.48,0:17:35.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那又怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.64,0:17:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你没有被我的法术迷惑？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.48,0:17:43.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道目前的你自己没有任何烦恼吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.60,0:17:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 没有烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.68,0:17:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在最幸福了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.12,0:17:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有亲人 有伙伴 有数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.52,0:17:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有任何不满或苦恼！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.56,0:17:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道这个世界上存在没有任何不满烦恼的孩子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.48,0:18:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 可是 拥有不满以及烦恼并不是坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.24,0:18:07.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望「比现在过的更好」是重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.80,0:18:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然想把这心愿用黑暗力量抹消
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.08,0:18:15.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在的愿望只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.92,0:18:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽 就是要打倒你 ！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.04,0:18:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子镭射
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.92,0:18:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.76,0:18:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,烈焰兽他们消失了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.76,0:18:48.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 衣服变了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.16,0:18:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 这里是数码世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.80,0:18:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊 难怪其他的数码兽消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.32,0:18:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.88,0:19:01.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾啊 小鬼们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.20,0:19:04.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差一点就能置我于死地了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.76,0:19:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是既然来到了数码世界 就是我的地盘了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.48,0:19:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能对黑暗力量随意支配了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.56,0:19:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.88,0:19:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在变大！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.88,0:19:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗 黑暗在迫近！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.40,0:19:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.52,0:19:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.64,0:19:56.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 怎么这点程度就倒下了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.76,0:20:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真正的力量可远远不止这些
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.44,0:20:20.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地...地球正渐渐被黑暗吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.60,0:20:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地球的人们会变成什么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.04,0:20:25.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸妈妈 还有姐姐们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.24,0:20:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这才...这才是你真正的目的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.56,0:20:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.00,0:20:37.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要把现实世界和数码世界统一为黑暗世界
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.32,0:20:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了成为王 我才复活的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.24,0:20:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.96,0:20:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前也说过同样的话！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.76,0:20:48.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和从前毫无变化
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.52,0:20:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,改变的只有那家伙的力量！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.40,0:20:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比以前强大了几十倍！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.52,0:20:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明只差一点孩子们就成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.40,0:20:59.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事态却出现出乎意料的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.92,0:21:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸收了黑暗能量而提升力量的贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.36,0:21:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.52,0:21:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现实世界和数码世界会变成黑暗世界
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.00,0:22:39.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直在战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.56,0:22:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也有不知道如何战斗的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.08,0:22:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过于悲伤无法再度站起的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.88,0:22:47.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的战斗究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.08,0:22:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后 所谓进化 又是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.52,0:22:54.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码兽大冒险 02 最终回
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.60,0:22:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「我们的数码世界」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.24,0:23:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}我们的数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:23:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 所有的大门都打开了
