[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.40,0:01:34.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅他们拼命追赶劫持了小贤的卡车
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.96,0:01:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而却受到一只接一只的黑暗系数码兽的阻挠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.76,0:01:40.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并展开战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.52,0:01:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅孤身一人追赶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.72,0:01:56.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在追上卡车的那一瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.28,0:01:59.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽出现在眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.53,0:02:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}黑暗的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.92,0:02:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我来拿黑暗的种子了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.76,0:02:23.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.84,0:02:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,率领众多恶魔型以及堕天使型数码兽的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.28,0:02:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔王型数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.68,0:02:31.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝招是超高温的地狱炼火「火焰葬礼」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.76,0:02:33.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽居然追的这么紧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.20,0:02:42.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究极魔兽亲自出马真是辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.72,0:02:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的部下怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.96,0:02:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被那群小鬼干掉了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:51.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,建议你说话谨慎一点 以免惹火上身
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.32,0:02:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 黑暗的种子是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.24,0:02:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.52,0:03:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之先观察情况找机会救出小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.72,0:03:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.92,0:03:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是大辅发来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.28,0:03:10.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在光丘...究极魔兽出现了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.96,0:03:13.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 请尽快去光丘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.28,0:03:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 光丘的话我很熟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.88,0:03:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗又要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.52,0:03:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.96,0:03:24.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在也只能战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.92,0:03:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果觉得痛苦的话 不用勉强自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.52,0:03:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用认为这是你的义务
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.36,0:03:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.84,0:03:37.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想这么做也是我自己的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.32,0:03:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 伊织 包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.36,0:03:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 还有我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.08,0:03:45.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.32,0:03:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光丘是我穿过吸血魔兽的大门后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.56,0:03:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到达的第一个地点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.64,0:03:58.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同时也是我第一次发现数码蛋的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:04:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的光丘怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.52,0:04:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次又会发生什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.68,0:04:07.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧 亚古拉兽 累不累
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.28,0:04:10.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没事 小京呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.12,0:04:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我？ 我也没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.92,0:04:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.80,0:04:17.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.68,0:04:21.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爽快的交给我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.00,0:04:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话 我就动用暴力解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.84,0:04:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 不要这么心急嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.20,0:04:29.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然这么想要的话就拿去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.44,0:04:36.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要把黑暗的种子移植到孩子们身上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.60,0:04:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在的一乘寺贤就是废物
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.44,0:04:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要杀要剐随你高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.28,0:04:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔头槌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.08,0:04:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黏黏网
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.56,0:04:47.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.36,0:04:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.56,0:04:55.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.00,0:04:58.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.16,0:05:03.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虫虫兽进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.12,0:05:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.40,0:05:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 把黑暗的种子交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.12,0:05:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 这里交给我 你快逃！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.08,0:05:20.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么能逃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.60,0:05:23.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些孩子都是...都是因为我才
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.64,0:05:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 其他的孩子们我也收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.68,0:05:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.48,0:05:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.48,0:05:41.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,V仔兽EX
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.48,0:05:45.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.20,0:05:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合体进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.88,0:05:53.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.36,0:05:59.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死亡火箭炮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.64,0:06:03.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.32,0:06:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒御魂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.68,0:06:37.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要设法打倒那只数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.84,0:06:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.04,0:06:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古神兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.52,0:06:46.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音速二重击
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.72,0:06:54.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.08,0:07:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊 人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.84,0:07:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 让我告诉你们力量的差距吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.24,0:07:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火焰葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.32,0:07:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机甲龙兽 究极进化...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.32,0:07:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.88,0:07:47.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子镭射
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.92,0:07:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒御魂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.68,0:07:59.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.84,0:08:03.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定成功
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.92,0:08:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们的绝招就是这种东西吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.40,0:08:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.52,0:08:17.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？这是为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.80,0:08:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们三个合力攻击也赢不了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.88,0:08:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天 从下午五点直到晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.12,0:08:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银座 竹之 池袋 练马等地
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.08,0:08:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接连出现怪物骚乱事件
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.20,0:08:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然现场一度陷入恐慌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.00,0:08:38.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底...发生了什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.20,0:08:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所幸的是并没有市民伤亡 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.47,0:08:39.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老公...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.24,0:08:43.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老公 果然还是应该报警吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要担心 怪兽在练马
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.64,0:08:49.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤又不可能去练马
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.56,0:08:51.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 万一他被绑架了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.68,0:08:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被装进卡车在途中被怪兽袭击了怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.68,0:08:57.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冷静一下 小贤还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.08,0:08:59.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定是在同学家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.00,0:09:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为电车停运所以回不来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.72,0:09:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明明说过晚回家的话要打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.04,0:09:12.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 你到底在干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.64,0:09:14.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你和这个事件有关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.40,0:09:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 打算过来了吗 一乘寺贤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.00,0:09:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能去 不可以去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.52,0:09:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我来帮你决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.56,0:09:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.36,0:10:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽 改变形态 战士形态
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.88,0:10:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.32,0:10:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们飞往世界各地时笼罩我们的光啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.76,0:10:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会再让你肆意妄为了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.76,0:10:35.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种骗人的小伎俩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.92,0:10:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能再浪费时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.72,0:10:40.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 大辅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.04,0:10:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你问我怎么办...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.00,0:10:57.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是一群死缠烂打的蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.16,0:11:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 怎么办才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.76,0:11:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.80,0:11:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要出现
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.40,0:11:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不能安分一点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.36,0:11:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗世界的居民就应该待在黑暗世界！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.40,0:11:11.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别随便出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.84,0:11:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可能有点晚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.72,0:11:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何能不能想办法送他回数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.08,0:11:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 说起来修的车里应该有笔记本电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.92,0:11:25.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要用那个把大门打开...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.68,0:11:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有那个必要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.52,0:11:37.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看 我可以随心所欲的打开大门
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.32,0:11:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够自己打开大门...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.84,0:11:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然你以为我们是怎么来到这个世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.08,0:11:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把我送回数码世界根本没有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.28,0:11:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时我都可以自由的出现
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.88,0:12:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.80,0:12:03.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 我们这次恐怕要失败了...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.52,0:12:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要灰心 不要放弃！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.60,0:12:10.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定还有打赢那个家伙的办法！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.04,0:12:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安慰的话就不要说了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.92,0:12:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 连伊织也这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.88,0:12:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明事实就是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.40,0:12:19.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帝皇龙甲兽 古神兽和人面战鹰兽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.24,0:12:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,联合在一起都打不过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.76,0:12:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就连打开数码世界大门也没有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.96,0:12:28.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都这样了 还可以有什么办法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.20,0:12:30.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经完蛋了...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.04,0:12:34.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要说这种话！一定会有办法的！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.08,0:12:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以让他无法回来的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.76,0:12:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既不是现实世界也不是数码世界的地方...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.52,0:12:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果送他到那种地方的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.44,0:12:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之海...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.40,0:12:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.12,0:12:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里和数码世界不同
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.56,0:12:52.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该是更深处的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.24,0:12:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果把他关在那片海里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.76,0:12:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他就无法轻易出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.44,0:12:58.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.60,0:13:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们能够打开通往黑暗之海的门吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.28,0:13:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那种方法真的存在吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.16,0:13:05.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.04,0:13:08.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.04,0:13:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与我自己的意识无关
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.84,0:13:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,直接被带去那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.92,0:13:16.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是用自己的意志打开大门的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.00,0:13:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然...是不行的...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.80,0:13:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说你们老实交出黑暗的种子不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.48,0:13:28.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们约定 拿到种子后马上回数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.76,0:13:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再也不会出现在你们的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.24,0:13:34.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你给我闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.72,0:13:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经通过神圣计划把门打开过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.92,0:13:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通向那片海的门
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.88,0:13:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川说过 光丘是大门的点（Gate Point）
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.68,0:13:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定这个D-3可以把门打开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.40,0:14:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:23.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.88,0:14:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能输给它
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.04,0:14:29.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波浪...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.64,0:14:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许会很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.36,0:14:34.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.32,0:14:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一乘寺贤 一乘寺在和黑暗的恐惧战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.96,0:14:48.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在竭力打开通往黑暗之海的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.84,0:14:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我却...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.28,0:14:53.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京你这个笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.64,0:15:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害怕 小贤正在和恐惧作斗争
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.60,0:15:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.04,0:15:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 小贤 坚持住！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.96,0:15:16.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经不是以前的你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.80,0:15:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是暴龙改造者了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.92,0:15:21.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那时虽然非常困难 也很痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.36,0:15:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可你毕竟战胜了黑暗的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.32,0:15:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是也为自己以前做的事情赎罪了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.64,0:15:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有什么可怕的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.44,0:15:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好温暖 这是大辅的心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.32,0:15:44.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤的恐惧渐渐消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.28,0:15:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信自己 不要败给什么黑暗的力量！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.76,0:15:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都在你身边！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.56,0:15:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把究极魔兽送回黑暗世界去！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.44,0:16:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...达高兽的海
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.64,0:16:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在！光子镭射！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲上云霄
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:18.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,荒御魂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.56,0:16:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货们啊 总有一天你们会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.12,0:16:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在就打开大门似乎为时过早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.08,0:16:41.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永别了 究极魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.92,0:16:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.20,0:17:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们啊 给我好好记住
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.36,0:17:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光丘这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.24,0:17:13.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.44,0:17:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.52,0:17:31.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了哦 现在就送你们回家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.12,0:17:35.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有人报警了 可以放心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.76,0:17:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊 不管怎么挤只能再坐一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.40,0:17:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就在田町
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.64,0:17:51.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 坐上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.16,0:17:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这样的话 你...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.36,0:17:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 我的父母知道真相的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.64,0:18:01.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.12,0:18:02.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.60,0:18:05.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.44,0:18:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来发生过这种事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.80,0:18:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个黑暗的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.84,0:18:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被种下种子的孩子们会怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.24,0:18:19.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,估计就是突然头脑灵活 运动万能
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.32,0:18:24.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家 想要变成以前的我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.24,0:18:28.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该不会大家都会变成暴龙改造者什么的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.16,0:18:31.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.68,0:18:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚失踪的孩子现已受到警方保护
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.40,0:18:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉泽孝 7岁 川田范子 10岁...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.52,0:18:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.32,0:18:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 给警察局打电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.36,0:18:48.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.36,0:18:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.36,0:18:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤...小贤...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.56,0:18:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.72,0:18:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.64,0:18:58.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再做让妈妈担心的事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.72,0:19:01.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.32,0:19:05.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 到底在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.96,0:19:23.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 等回过神来都已经这么晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.80,0:19:26.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.32,0:19:30.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪有哪有 还麻烦您特地的送回来 真是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.40,0:19:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.24,0:19:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就一路小心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.40,0:19:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.00,0:19:38.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个人是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.92,0:19:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊？城户修 是城户丈的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.20,0:19:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,几岁了？是大学生？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊 姐姐 脸皮真厚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.16,0:19:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是对阿和一心一意的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.04,0:19:51.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别再提他了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.04,0:19:54.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我看见了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.00,0:20:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,年龄比我小的不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.48,0:20:08.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是年长的好啊 年长的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.16,0:20:11.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 是叫城户修啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.68,0:20:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.68,0:20:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后 小贤对父母说了至今为止所发生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.84,0:20:25.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数码世界的事  暴龙改造者的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.16,0:20:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有 虫虫兽的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.40,0:20:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好 我叫虫虫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.96,0:20:39.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被劫走的孩子们平安的回到了父母身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.72,0:20:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然看上去没有什么变化
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.88,0:20:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然而孩子们体内的黑暗种子已经在生长了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.36,0:20:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样子所有的仪式都完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.88,0:20:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就只有等待时机了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.08,0:21:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗的种子正在孩子们心里的阴暗面发芽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.64,0:21:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当黑暗之花开放的时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.36,0:22:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被移植了黑暗种子的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.80,0:22:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他们看上去是回到了原来的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.84,0:22:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是数码世界的破坏却无法停止
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.40,0:22:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,次元的种子发芽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:48.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对着亚古兽的命运之剑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.20,0:22:52.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,割裂黑暗的流星
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.76,0:22:54.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.92,0:22:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「黑暗战斗暴龙兽 VS 战斗暴龙兽」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.03,0:22:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(250,150)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.03,0:22:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,375)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.60,0:22:59.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
