[Script Info]
;本字幕文件用 SrtEdit MPC播放版 Version 5.2 编辑制作
;Unicode SrtEdit Copyright(C) 2005-2009 袁卫国

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: *Default,Arial,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,0,2,3,2,20,20,20,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OP,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,12,1
Style: ED,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,30,30,11,1
Style: OP粤语,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------OP-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.33,0:00:19.38,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,故事开始全速旋转起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.38,0:00:24.18,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,大地侵染上赤色烈焰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:31.73,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,地球仪上那变的空空如也的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.73,0:00:36.40,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,用我们的双手去拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:43.02,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那永无止境的崎岖之路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.02,0:00:47.74,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 不顾一切勇往直前 Far away
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.41,0:00:57.29,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来吧！ 我的心中充满勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:01:03.76,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那高耸的目标 我们绝不认输
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.76,0:01:09.81,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧起来吧！ 跳跃着焦躁的心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.81,0:01:16.44,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,那已被遗忘的明天 誓要去夺回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:21.53,OP,,0000,0000,0000,,发起激烈的战斗吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------前集提要-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.84,0:01:35.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川在孩子们身上移植的黑暗种子中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.24,0:01:37.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经有一颗开花了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.16,0:01:42.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸收了花朵的及川身上出现了神秘的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.00,0:01:49.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它给予了无敌的黑暗战斗暴龙兽致命的一击
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,意识到即将死亡的黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.60,0:01:56.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用最后的力量封印了数码世界大门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:58.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后消失于无形
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------正式开始-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.53,0:02:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(300,0)}恐怖！贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.88,0:02:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟在干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.72,0:02:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像是在等什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.60,0:02:26.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个「什么」难道是指及川？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.88,0:02:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定和之前的事件有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.64,0:02:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许那个时候被下了什么暗示
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.16,0:02:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么要在光丘?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.48,0:02:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在光丘 大门有好几次都被打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.40,0:02:39.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定和这个有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.44,0:02:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根据和加布兽的联系
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.20,0:02:44.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多亏黑暗战斗暴龙兽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.24,0:02:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大门总算是被完全关闭了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.52,0:02:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.76,0:02:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 原来大家都来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.08,0:02:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太一和素娜呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.80,0:02:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去盯昨天那个女孩子的梢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不去真的可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.12,0:03:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一发生紧急情况我也帮不上什么忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.40,0:03:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是让带着亚古兽的太一去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.80,0:03:19.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.80,0:03:22.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光子郎？我现在在光丘的车站前
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.20,0:03:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么过来啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.44,0:03:29.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为...你看...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.88,0:03:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,石田先生 高石女士 一乘寺先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.24,0:03:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武之内女士以及城户同学的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.52,0:03:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都为了这件事付出了很多 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.64,0:03:42.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有我们家...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.96,0:03:43.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.76,0:03:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就当成慰问品吧 我做了饭团带来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.20,0:03:49.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饭团...啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.92,0:03:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想让大家一起吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.24,0:03:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.40,0:03:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就过去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.56,0:03:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请在那里等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.12,0:03:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,待会见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.00,0:04:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我要走开一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.44,0:04:02.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饭团耶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.64,0:04:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说 感觉事态变的越来越糟的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.44,0:04:08.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道只有我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.16,0:04:12.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨天看到的从及川体内出现的那个影子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.36,0:04:14.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.84,0:04:18.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我确定及川不是普通的人类...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.64,0:04:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能救出那些孩子呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.16,0:04:23.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.20,0:04:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们要相信自己并为此努力 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.24,0:04:30.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 说了奇怪的话 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:35.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收获的时候到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.76,0:04:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过还真是麻烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.40,0:04:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那群小鬼正在监视
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.12,0:04:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 小贤？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.76,0:04:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才感觉到了一种气息
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.60,0:04:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,气息？是及川？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.60,0:04:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 不过看来是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.04,0:04:55.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.20,0:05:00.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还以为被发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.72,0:05:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被发现的话 气数就尽了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.24,0:05:05.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么会？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.92,0:05:06.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,, 笨蛋 是说他们！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.16,0:05:09.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 当然是这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.88,0:05:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.56,0:05:14.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.60,0:05:16.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.12,0:05:19.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做了饭团带来 大家尝尝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.84,0:05:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,劳您费心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.00,0:05:23.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.72,0:05:25.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那您请回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.68,0:05:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我能多呆一会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.44,0:05:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我无法预料会发生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.60,0:05:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可我不想回家...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.16,0:05:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.60,0:05:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也请你理解一下光子郎的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.64,0:05:40.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为珍视母亲所以才这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.92,0:05:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我也明白...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.28,0:05:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那些孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.44,0:05:44.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.64,0:05:48.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些孩子的父母一定会很担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.64,0:05:49.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.76,0:05:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我去和那些孩子的父母谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.20,0:05:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让他们亲眼证实自己孩子的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.68,0:06:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真是个好主意！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.04,0:06:02.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:05.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么我现在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.88,0:06:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位再见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.40,0:06:08.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别勉强自己 光子郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.64,0:06:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.92,0:06:12.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,父母来了会有什么用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.64,0:06:16.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算双亲都来了也无法除去黑暗种子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.64,0:06:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你们不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.68,0:06:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感情的话会发生无法预知的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.44,0:06:25.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前经历过多次这种奇迹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.00,0:06:27.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.60,0:06:28.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.64,0:06:32.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啦对啦 据说我们人类无法看见黑暗之花
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.04,0:06:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们对于这个怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.56,0:06:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:38.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这多半不是物质性的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.92,0:06:40.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会不会是精神性的东西呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.20,0:06:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有证据
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.60,0:06:46.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我体内的黑暗种子停止生长就是因为
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.80,0:06:49.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我察觉到了我的爸爸妈妈对我的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.24,0:06:56.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 请看这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.24,0:06:59.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及川！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.08,0:07:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于出现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.72,0:07:05.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪物！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.60,0:07:06.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你们阻扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.04,0:07:07.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从那里让开！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.16,0:07:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不准碰孩子们！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:11.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.00,0:07:13.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不摘掉黑暗之花
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.00,0:07:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之芽会遍布全身
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.88,0:07:18.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最终整个人都将变成黑暗之树
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.40,0:07:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那样的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.52,0:07:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我那时不是这样的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.80,0:07:24.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然当时也非常痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.36,0:07:29.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的种子是最原始的 因此能够与你和平共处
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.56,0:07:31.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这些孩子的是复制品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.52,0:07:33.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是被强制移植过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.56,0:07:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果自然也不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.28,0:07:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明知如此却故意这么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.12,0:07:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此这些孩子还是很乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.36,0:07:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.64,0:07:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.04,0:07:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你又想干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.84,0:07:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然是去数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.68,0:07:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不...喂！别说多余的话啊 木乃伊兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.68,0:07:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.84,0:07:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.52,0:07:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为这些小鬼无法阻止我们的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.92,0:08:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你准备怎么去？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.68,0:08:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.84,0:08:07.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了我能送亚基利兽和木乃伊兽去数码世界了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.00,0:08:09.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是从这里传送的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.48,0:08:14.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个门的话已经被黑暗战...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:18.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当他发现去不了思维混乱的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.96,0:08:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是救出孩子们的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.28,0:08:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.84,0:08:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 在这个时刻任何问题我都可以回答
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.56,0:08:30.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我问你 为什么选了我？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.44,0:08:32.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么又是这个问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.32,0:08:35.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次见到你的时候我就明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.84,0:08:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道你是被选召的孩子之一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.44,0:08:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.03,0:08:44.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗之塔到底是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.24,0:08:46.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原本是在达高兽的海域里的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.64,0:08:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有很多用处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.28,0:08:54.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其中最有用的是可以改变数码世界的环境
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.32,0:08:58.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你改变环境的目的究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.20,0:09:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了让作为大人的我也能去数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.80,0:09:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「作为大人」？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.00,0:09:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可以打开大门却无法通过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.96,0:09:10.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为数码世界无法接受肮脏的大人的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.84,0:09:11.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别无他法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.04,0:09:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才用我的遗传基因制造了这两个家伙并送过去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.08,0:09:21.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是无论如何我都想亲自过去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.52,0:09:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才利用你建立了黑暗之塔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.04,0:09:28.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却被你们全部破坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.08,0:09:32.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算是现实世界建造的也是同样的下场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.96,0:09:34.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我改变了计划
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.92,0:09:38.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将在数码世界起到妨碍作用的黑暗种子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.24,0:09:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,移植到了孩子们身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.36,0:09:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后 今天...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.48,0:09:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有生以来第一次将要穿过数码世界大门
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.32,0:09:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一天 我已经等待的太久了...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.52,0:09:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙...哭了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.60,0:09:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 Boss？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.68,0:10:00.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为可以实现梦想了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.68,0:10:03.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浩树 如果你还在世的话也能去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.44,0:10:04.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.28,0:10:08.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家 一起唱歌吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.40,0:10:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 走吧 一起前往数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.84,0:10:16.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 一起前往数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.28,0:10:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 走吧 一起前往数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.72,0:10:22.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 一起前往数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.76,0:10:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是屏障吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.52,0:10:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.24,0:10:28.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们马上就会因为无法打开大门而慌乱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.52,0:10:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家准备采取行动！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.44,0:10:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.48,0:10:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好！ 最后就是这个！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.84,0:10:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.72,0:10:44.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧！打开了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.44,0:10:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.76,0:10:50.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有我们！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.72,0:10:52.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.92,0:10:55.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么打开了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.48,0:10:56.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.36,0:10:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...不可能！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.24,0:10:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们追上去！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.08,0:11:02.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！ 不要轻举妄动！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.80,0:11:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳！ 大辅！ 小光！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.80,0:11:09.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须要通知太一...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.12,0:11:31.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 走吧 一起前往数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.52,0:11:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 一起前往数码世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.20,0:11:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到了哦 这里就是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.52,0:11:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇！ 是数码世界耶 太好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.40,0:11:41.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高兴吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.56,0:11:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们高兴的话 叔叔也很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.44,0:11:46.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是 终于过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.44,0:11:50.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不相信我 在叔叔年幼的时候..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.44,0:11:53.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太早了 我出生的太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.76,0:12:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你不玩吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.36,0:12:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对 这里不对 这里不是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.00,0:12:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 这里就是数码世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.92,0:12:10.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.28,0:12:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.08,0:12:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道这里不是数码世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.68,0:12:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛吐丝攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.92,0:12:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,X光线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.32,0:12:27.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫拳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.80,0:12:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万吨压力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.92,0:12:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你称心如意的！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是 把孩子们还回来！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.24,0:12:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 为什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.00,0:12:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.04,0:12:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还以为终于过来了呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:43.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.00,0:12:47.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里啊...可以确定不是数码世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.52,0:12:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许因为黑暗战斗暴龙兽封印了大门
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.12,0:12:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以迷路到另一个世界了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.72,0:13:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是多么想去数码世界啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.48,0:13:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忘掉吧 数码世界什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.80,0:13:06.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.36,0:13:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有更好的世界 就是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.36,0:13:13.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是偶然闯进了的却是我梦寐以求的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.88,0:13:16.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.36,0:13:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可怕吗？是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.96,0:13:20.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闯进这里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.04,0:13:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看着同伴活生生的被黑暗吞噬的确很恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.84,0:13:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为知道自己无法逃脱从而绝望
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.04,0:13:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.84,0:13:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是究极魔兽的同伙？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.04,0:13:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是达高兽的？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.64,0:13:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪边都不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.92,0:13:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好像听见了自己的声音 是我的错觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.12,0:13:41.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没听错 我就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.84,0:13:42.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.04,0:13:45.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前我曾寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.76,0:13:48.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以让变成数据的我寄生的寄主
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.28,0:13:51.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那时我遇见了你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:52.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三年前？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.28,0:13:56.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为朋友浩树去世而痛苦万分的时候吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.08,0:14:01.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你并没有因为朋友的死而悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.12,0:14:03.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不如说你是恨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.20,0:14:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「明明约好了一起去数码世界」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.12,0:14:09.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「为什么你先死了？」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.64,0:14:12.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 我怎么会恨浩树！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.92,0:14:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.64,0:14:24.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能看见吗 浩树？ 是数码世界哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.20,0:14:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算别人都不知道但我却明白
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.44,0:14:29.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那时数码世界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.56,0:14:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是浩树 你太残忍了 扔下我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.00,0:14:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,留下我一个人...太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.36,0:14:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把我也带上吧！拜托了！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.72,0:14:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想去数码世界吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.36,0:14:54.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想去！如果可以的话 想去！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.04,0:15:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你可以扔掉良心我就带你去 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.80,0:15:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都愿意做 只要可以去 什么都...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.80,0:15:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.68,0:15:11.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.92,0:15:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以为那是我的心声 原来不是吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.64,0:15:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那之后的事我都告诉你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.16,0:15:23.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.96,0:15:26.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是谁了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.64,0:15:29.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是...吸血魔兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.72,0:15:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸血魔兽？真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.68,0:15:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.92,0:15:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是被你识破了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.92,0:15:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么顺带告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.92,0:15:47.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑色魔轮是复制了你的神圣尾环的数据后逆转制作的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.32,0:15:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前我就知道你是执着的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.12,0:15:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到会到这种地步
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.04,0:15:55.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这次一定要把你葬送在黑暗中！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.32,0:15:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.32,0:15:58.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不是以前的我了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.20,0:16:10.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.04,0:16:17.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 黑暗种子有妨碍的作用也是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那其实是我的饵料 为了让我重生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.08,0:16:21.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.68,0:16:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.00,0:16:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 我不会杀你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.40,0:16:32.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想要黑暗之花
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.24,0:16:33.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你成功的！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.72,0:16:36.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂！你们去阻止他？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.12,0:16:39.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛吐丝攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.88,0:16:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说了住手啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.60,0:16:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你捣乱的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.76,0:16:51.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.72,0:16:55.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经做完了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.60,0:16:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 现在开始做饭后运动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.36,0:17:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.32,0:17:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要变身了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.44,0:17:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是变成吸血魔兽还是究极吸血魔兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.52,0:17:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两个都不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.35,0:17:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请叫我贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.52,0:17:17.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸血魔兽超高级进化后的究极体数码兽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.96,0:17:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您要做什么？我是您的仆人...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.07,0:17:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我要做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.40,0:17:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:27.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好想想！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.84,0:17:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 那样也很好玩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.68,0:17:36.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.28,0:17:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做这么残忍的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.16,0:17:43.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我读了亚基利兽的心并照着做了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.88,0:17:44.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.16,0:17:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我是在想这个 但是我并没有祈求！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.96,0:17:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.56,0:17:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话说你知道我接下来要对你做什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.92,0:17:56.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 我也不想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.64,0:17:59.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不许撒谎 现在给我想
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.96,0:18:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.64,0:18:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.92,0:18:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 接下来你想被怎么对待？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.36,0:18:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 你不想被怎么对待？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.44,0:18:16.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你...求您了...放过我吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.76,0:18:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.96,0:18:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.80,0:18:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为她是女人 所以我手下留情了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.64,0:18:32.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她不想再痛下去 想死的痛快些
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.12,0:18:34.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我满足了她的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.88,0:18:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝利亚吸血魔兽 不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.44,0:18:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绷带蛇击！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.84,0:18:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也读了你的心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.96,0:18:47.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和我交战 你根本就没打算活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.68,0:18:50.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚基利兽不在了 我却活着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.52,0:18:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我死也没关系 但是要与你同归于尽！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.20,0:18:57.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再也没有比一心求死的人更加无趣的了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.08,0:19:00.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为不想死 恐惧才会倍增
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.96,0:19:03.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,废话留到地狱再说吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.12,0:19:06.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,游戏到此结束！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.28,0:19:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无情融化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.16,0:19:17.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 快点合体进化！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.76,0:19:18.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不...不行！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.76,0:19:19.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「不行」？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.56,0:19:21.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一迪路兽死了的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.16,0:19:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.72,0:19:24.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿岳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.44,0:19:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小京
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.20,0:19:25.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伊织
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.28,0:19:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有史以来第一次...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.40,0:19:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会害怕战斗...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.56,0:19:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要逃出去...不想再待在这里了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.56,0:19:36.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在做恶梦...快醒过来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.00,0:19:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 怎么了啊 你们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.12,0:19:41.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为认定会输所以才不行啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.68,0:19:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要想着「一定能赢！」然后战斗到最后取胜啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.48,0:19:45.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.32,0:19:49.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅 就算只有我一个人也要战斗！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.76,0:19:52.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是就凭你一个...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.88,0:19:54.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是认为我会输啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.64,0:19:56.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个...有一点...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.08,0:19:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信我！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.44,0:20:00.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信你自己刚才说过的话！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.96,0:20:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.20,0:20:10.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前也有过很多形势不利的战斗 可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.96,0:20:12.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,努力之后我们都胜了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.72,0:20:13.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.84,0:20:15.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 冲吧 V仔兽EX！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.48,0:20:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.00,0:20:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小贤 这样可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.84,0:20:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快让他住手 本宫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.48,0:20:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要战斗也要从长计议
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.48,0:20:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们合体吧 好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.44,0:20:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的手在颤抖
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.04,0:20:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是因为...刚才看到...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.84,0:20:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要是胆怯了的话 合体进化也是不能完成的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.36,0:20:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们会想办法的！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.96,0:20:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算我求你了 这种话题不要再说了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.08,0:20:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会扰乱我心绪的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.80,0:20:55.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我理解你 一乘寺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.96,0:20:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我也...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.20,0:20:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.88,0:21:03.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要输啊 绝对不能输！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------ED-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那通往明天的汽车啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,行走在断断续续的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,以及 只能回头注视那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,迷惘的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,互相手牵手地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,那样 我所拥有的巨大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会引发出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也能互相理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也要飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,永远的 永远的 无论何时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也有大家在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,一定的 一定的 无论是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一个人呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.15,ED,,0,0,0,,明日へ向かう汽車は
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:31.50,ED,,0,0,0,,とぎれたレールで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:35.34,ED,,0,0,0,,もう 振り返るばかり
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:38.95,ED,,0,0,0,,とまどう私
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:42.03,ED,,0,0,0,,手と手つなぎ合わせ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.04,0:21:45.48,ED,,0,0,0,,一緒に走ると
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.49,0:21:49.35,ED,,0,0,0,,そう 大きな力が
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.36,0:21:52.45,ED,,0,0,0,,出せるのはなぜ？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:59.84,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:03.10,ED,,0,0,0,,通じ合ってるから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:06.86,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも どこでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.87,0:22:10.10,ED,,0,0,0,,飛んでいけるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.11,0:22:13.75,ED,,0,0,0,,いつも いつも いつでも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.76,0:22:17.24,ED,,0,0,0,,みんなが側にいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.25,0:22:21.08,ED,,0,0,0,,きっと きっと 誰でも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.09,0:22:23.97,ED,,0,0,0,,ひとりじゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.60,0:00:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,----------下集预告-----------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.52,0:22:40.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,温暖的假象 在面前展开的幸福世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.44,0:22:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是那只是贝利亚吸血魔兽的幻象
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.56,0:22:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「大家快醒过来！」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.12,0:22:48.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大辅热切的心情将大家的心连结了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.56,0:22:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抗敌的坚定意志 前所未见的奇迹发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.72,0:22:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下集 数码兽大冒险 02
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.24,0:22:57.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「最后的装甲进化」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.78,0:23:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,320)}{\fscx95}{\b1}{\bord2}{\fs45}{\fad(500,0)}最后的装甲进化
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:00.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在 冒险之门敞开了
